you know what we should all do
go see a musical
sure and you know which one we should
see
the 1996 tony award winner
do you happen to know the name of that
one i don't know um
greece no
rent yes rent
okay so when do you want to go what oh
i'm sorry i can't i'm busy
hey man it is so hard to shop for girls
oh yes it is at office max
what did you get here
a pen it's two gifts in one it's a pen
that's also a clock huh
[Applause]
you can't give her that why not because
she's not 11.
and it's not the seventh night of
hanukkah
okay honey what he means by that is
while this is a very nice gift
maybe it's just not something a
boyfriend gives sure it
is she needs a pen for work she's
writing she turns it over whoa
it's time for my date with joey
all right look look what what did you
get for angelo del vecchio for her
birthday
she didn't have a birthday while we were
going out for three years
look it's too late and i got an audition
i can't
shop anymore
i will go out and i will try to find
something for her okay
thanks man and oh while you're at it
could you get her a card
would you like me to write her a little
poem as well
or just get a card that has a poem
already in it