[Music]
hey have you noticed they move where
they do the interview on Jeopardy now
yeah it used to be right in the middle
of single Jeopardy now they do it right
after single Jeopardy yeah it's much
better isn't it oh no comparison hey I
got to stop at the bookstore get my
parents one of those French English
dictionaries hey hey hey hey hey hey
what your parents are going to Paris
right yeah so I tell Alec that I have to
go to Paris for an undetermined amount
of time then all I have to do is buy
some postcards and have your parents
mail them from
Paris what about little Joey
who I think he's probably better
off I'm trying to get out of this Big
Brother program so when you get to Paris
all you have to do is drop them in any
mailbox but there are no stamps on these
well no not yet you got to buy French
stamps I'll I'll reimburse you of course
why are you doing this he wants this guy
to think he's in Paris why because
George is a deeply Disturbed
individually oh hey Helen uh could I uh
use some more of your hand lotion I told
you it was good it's from The saxs Fifth
Avenue in
Miami I'm going to remember that if I'm
ever in Florida yeah or if you're ever
on Fifth Avenue here in New York City
you could get some there yeah hey those
are nice pants I got a pair just like
them at home well that doesn't surprise
me yeah I bought these at Rudy's it's a
used clothing store see when people like
you
die the widows they bring in their their
wardrobes they make a bundle
really my father's got a ton of old
clothes just sitting up on the attic you
think they're worth something oh yeah if
they're vintage and you're a
widow but what happens if the husband
dies after the wife who brings the
clothing in then well I suppose the
children
do yes I suppose they
do all right I got at 10:00 I'll see
everybody later
[Laughter]
hey oh I just remembered uh my parents
really want to have you guys over for
dinner before you leave town what about
tonight tonight yeah they're making
paa uh oh I don't think we can make it
tonight but we have plans what plans we
have
plans where'd you get plans we have
plans well um what about tomorrow night
maybe
okay uh I guess I'll tell them that okay
hey give them our best though yeah I'll
call you later
yeah so what place do you have none so
how come you're not going over there for
dinner Jerry we don't care much for the
castanas we can't stand
them really since when since always
we've never liked them why well they're
so loud they're always fighting it's
uncomfortable you never notice oh I
noticed but they're from your age group
I didn't think you could detect abnormal
behavior among your own
kind well we
do
yeah it's us oh come on
up it's Elaine you don't have a problem
with her do you we adore Elaine she
wants to say hi she's with a new
boyfriend what's he like he's nice bit
of a close talker a what you'll see
well I really had no idea that you felt
this way about the castanas they're
exhausting it's like being in an
[Applause]
[Music]
asylum oh this is Aaron hello Aaron
hello Aaron so how long you folks in
town three more days three more days and
then we're off to Paris W we're going
with the select Charter group I love
France I was just last year in fact you
know I still have an envelope full of
French Franks I'll get them to you we
can't take money oh no it's a gift from
us oh that is so nice Aon isn't he nice
so listen has Jerry been showing you a
good time no I
haven't you know I have a friend who
works at the Metropolitan Museum of Art
how'd you like a behind the scenes tour
really really you could do that easily
it wouldn't be any trouble of course not
when could we go how about right now I'm
ready are you sure yes okay let me get
my coat El what do you
say well I don't think so Aaron uh I
have plans oh how about you
Jerry I'm s you sure can examine the
artwork up
close maybe I'll try and catch up with
you
oh yeah that all
happen number 49 you know uh my last
name is castanza That's Italian so you
and I are kind of like countrymen Banos
650 you change ah yes and I always take
care of my Pano so here's a little
something hey hey you steal my money no
no no you don't understand I wasn't
trying to take it out I know what you
now get out there don't come back again
ever
I got the Cal Jones Mr Stein Bren oh
beautiful I'm starving George so I
thought tomorrow uh maybe we try a
little corn beef corn beef man I don't
think so it's a little fatty don't you
think how about Chinese Chinese no too
many containers big mess big mess very
sloppy we're going to stick with the
czon from Panos that's the ticket I just
thought it'd be nice you know a little
variety no no no George let me tell you
something when I find something I like I
stick with it from 1973 to 1982 I ate
the exact same lunch every day turkey
chili and a bowl made out of bread bread
bowl George you'd eat the chili then
you'd eat the bowl nothing more
satisfying than looking down after lunch
and seeing just a
table hey
buddy I'm waiting for my shirt you got
your shirt in my oven yeah well you know
I didn't have enough quarters for the
dryer but this is better anyway and it's
more convenient oh for both of us and I
a lot more control I got a shirt going
for 10 minutes at
325 what's wrong with your oven a bacon
a
pie yeah yeah come up what you got
cigars huh yeah I got some cubin for
George's wedding it was more than I
wanted to spend but what the hell oh
baby
yeah a producto de
Peru Jerry if you think those are Cubans
you got another thing coming Peru I paid
300 bucks for these I could have got a
house in Peru for 300 bucks you got Rook
buddy I got to pay this Todd gak guy 300
bucks just so he has some excuse to see
Elaine again without asking her out
that's a nice name Todd
gak what is that
Dutch whoa baby here we
go oh mama
[Music]
hey George
hey well this is really bad now I really
am in a bad situation now so what's
Stein Brena going to do if he doesn't
get his calzone tomorrow what's he going
to do what's he going to do that's
exactly the point nobody knows what this
guy is capable of he fires people like
it's a bodily
function why don't you get somebody else
from the office to go to Panos because
before you know it he'll be having lunch
with him you know how these inter office
politics work
no I never had a
job decided to go with the brown
ones what the hell is this Grand's
cooking up some
coroy there's got to be some way to get
back into pisos oh pisos that's that
place by the stadium isn't it yeah
you've heard of it oh yeah Newman Raves
about it it's on his mail route he stops
by there every day I'll see you guys
later what kind of pie you cooking
huckleberry
Well you certainly are in a
bind yeah and I I thought since you'll
go by there every day maybe we could
help each other
out let me be perfectly blunt I don't
care for you
castanza you hang out on the west side
of the building with Seinfeld all day
just laughing it up wasting your lives
you're going to help me or not all right
all right I'll help you I will help you
but I will expect something in
return what well for starters I want a c
zone of my
own all right and a slice of pepperoni
pizza and a large
soda and three times a week I shall
require a
canoli it's steep don't you think you
know I hear the Mr steinbrener can be a
bit erratic I'd hate to see him when
he's hungry all right all right do we
have a deal just make sure you get them
to me by 1:00 he's very regimented about
his meals I know exactly how he feels
well ni's doing business with you do
come again
[Music]
oh