-Here's how it works.
-I'm gonna ask you
for some silly words --
nouns, verbs, adjectives,
et cetera --
and as we do that, they'll be
written on the cue cards,
and then, we're gonna act out
a very dramatic Mad Lib scene.
-Okay.
-Very dramatic.
I mean, have you seen my work?
-I have, I have.
-Really, very, yeah.
-It's excellent.
-Thank you.
-You won a Grammy.
-Yeah, I did win a Grammy
for my acting.
For my acting.
Thank you.
[ Laughs ]
All right, here we go. Ready?
-Yes.
-Name of a cute puppy.
-Uh, uh, My Little Cookie.
[ Laughter ]
-That actually is cute.
-Yeah.
-My Little Cookie.
-Okay.
-A silly word.
-Uh...
What?
[ Laughter ]
Pollywog.
-Yeah.
[ Laughter ]
Adjective.
-Amazing.
-A plural type of profession.
-Plural type of profession?
-Plural, it's even hard to say.
-Okay.
Plural type of profession.
How about sanitation engineers?
[ Laughter ]
-What?
Okay.
-I don't know.
-The cue-card guy's going,
"Are you kidding me?"
Type of '80s technology?
-Walkman.
-Oh, yeah.
-Isn't that '80s, right?
-Yeah.
Loved my Walkman.
-Yeah, loved that.
-Something you buy on eBay.
-Sneakers.
[ Laughter ]
Or vintage clothes.
Which do you look better?
-Vintage sneakers.
[ Laughter ]
-What you would shout if you saw
a spider crawling up your leg.
-Uh...
-Ew!
It's crawling up your leg!
-Come here, darling!
[ Laughter ]
What?
-Come here what?
-Come here, darling.
[ Laughter and applause ]
-"Come here, darling."
Oh, my gosh.
[ Laughter ]
Type of relative.
-Aunt.
Woman's name.
-Um, Ingrid.
-Ingrid.
[ Laughter ]
Number.
-1,000,256.
[ Laughter ]
-Plural objects.
-Uh...
Sofas.
-Curse word
a first-grader would use?
-Doodie-head.
[ Laughter ]
-It's classic.
Classic.
-Classic.
-Fictional character.
-Um...
Uh, Huckleberry Finn.
-Huckleberry Finn.
-Something you'd find
in the kitchen.
-Knife.
-These are all good.
Give me another number.
-Seven.
[ Laughter ]
-Celebrity name.
-How about...
Ingrid Bergman.
-All right.
[ Laughter ]
-Ingrid -- I don't know.
-Yeah, Ingrid Bergman.
A verb ending in -ing.
-Running.
-Another adjective.
-Uh...
Humongous.
-These are good words.
Plural animals.
-Lemmings.
[ Laughter ]
-That's fantastic, dude.
Lemmings.
What?
A verb ending in -ing.
Another one.
-A verb ending in -ing.
-You said running already.
-Yeah, I said running.
Give me another verb like what?
-Kissing.
-Yeah, kissing, kissing,
there you go.
Thank you.
-Favorite song lyric.
-Favorite song --
I don't know.
Uh...
[ Laughter ]
-Poopy-di-scoop.
-Poopy-di-scoop?
-Is that a lyric?
-Yeah, it's a lyric.
Yeah, it is.
-Poopy-di-scoop.
All right.
Yeah.
Thank you.
[ Laughter and applause ]
-It's good.
-Good.
-Okay. All right.
We've filled out the words
for our scene.
Are you ready to perform?
-Let's do it, man.
-Let's do this.
Here we go.
Let's go.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Both laugh ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
-Good evening...
My Little Cookie.
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughter and applause ]
Special Director Pollywog.
It's good to see you again.
-I'm here
with your next mission.
A criminal organization
of the world's
most amazing
sanitation engineers
hacked into
the government's Walkman,
stealing their top-secret report
on vintage sneakers.
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughter and applause ]
-Come here, darling.
[ Laughter ]
-I understand your reaction.
The group also kidnapped
your Aunt Ingrid
and is holding her for a ransom
of 1,000,256 sofas.
[ Laughter ]
-Where the doodie-head are
we gonna get 1,000,256 sofas?
-I don't know,
but we have to move fast.
-I have a plan.
I'll meet up with the group
disguising as myself --
disguising myself
as Huckleberry Finn.
Jesus...
[ Laughter ]
-So far --
So far, I'm on board.
-If they attack,
I'll fight back with a knife.
[ Laughter ]
-Great.
This disk contains sensitive
information that might help.
-What's on this disk?
-Seven photos
of Ingrid Bergman running.
[ Laughter ]
-Come here, darling.
I've already contacted my team
of highly humongous lemmings.
[ Laughter ]
-You're the best agent we have.
How do you prepare
for such tense missions?
-By waking up every morning,
going up on the roof,
and kissing and by repeating
my own personal mantra --
poopy-di-scoop, poopy-di-scoop.
[ Laughter, cheers, applause ]
-And scene!
-And scene.
My thanks
to Tom Cruise right there!
We'll be right back
with Parker Posey!
Tom Cruise!
[ Laughing ]