all right
[Applause]
[Music]
Brian Cox looks like a super Gruff
sophisticated ball sack
I would hate having a combo with Chris
Rock here's one loud ass black
individual
this person is a psychic
Matthew Broderick can eat it he peaked
at 17.
the bacon is what Ryan Reynolds would
look like if he did a ton of heroin
foreign
is
ugly there I said it
you they should cast me and all of Dan
Levy's Parts because I'm annoying and
gay but not
sufferable and I'm also hotter than him
nothing says gay rights like this tweet
Kirsten Dunst looks like if Jewel got
cosmetic surgery but then got hit
the day they removed the bandages
thank you Andrew Garfield has fast
people hands or at least the hands of a
creepy school custom
that is
untrue and Incredibly inventive and
creative also Jason Momoa is a creep
no one should feel anything in their
ovaries for him
George Clooney is selling loads of
tequila right now
I am
why is Salma Hayek trending is her
titties out
no where's the camera
Jon Stewart sucks China's
China doesn't have you're thinking of
Florida
why does Halle Berry's knee look like
the face of that guy who came out of the
book that Harry found in the Restricted
Section at the library at Hogwarts
you need to stop looking at my knees
like the show is up here from here to
here
the worst part about Curb Your
Enthusiasm is they portray Larry's Apple
Larry David
you know what I couldn't agree more
[Applause]