I used to bite my tongue and hold my breath
Scared to rock the boat and make a mess
So I sat quietly, agreed politely
I guess that I forgot I had a choice
I let you push me past the breaking point
I stood for nothing, so I fell for everything
You held me down, but I got up
Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice, you hear that sound
Like thunder, gonna shake your ground
You held me down, but I got up
Get ready cause I've had enough
I see it all, I see it now
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter,
dancing through the fire
'Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Louder, louder than a lion
Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
You're gonna hear me roar
Now I'm floating like a butterfly
Stinging like a bee I earned my stripes
I went from zero, to my own hero
You held me down, but I got up
Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice, your hear that sound
Like thunder, gonna shake your ground
You held me down, but I got up
Get ready 'cause I've had enough
I see it all, I see it now
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter,
dancing through the fire
'cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Louder, louder than a lion
'cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
You're gonna hear me roar
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter,
dancing through the fire
'Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Louder, louder than a lion
'Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
You're gonna hear me roar