who's there uh hello uh oh you sir yes
good
right High Hopes I don't
[Applause]
have what's your name sir David David
lovely and where are you from David
Australia do you live here now yes I do
I live in Su you live in Sur lovely part
of the world and what do you do in Sur
David I design and build exhibitions so
I'm an exhibitionist really
no no no nice good all right David I'll
you go with your story okay when I first
came over to England I had a uh a couple
of interesting moments with the English
accent and I had a blocked ear so I had
to go to the uh Walkabout Center to get
uh to get it uh
unblocked and uh after she'd flushed my
ear out the nurse said to me now I want
you to oil your ear and your Willie and
and I said to her Emma Wily she said no
annually
[Applause]
[Music]