-Jack, we talked --
I've seen you in concert.
-Yeah.
-I've seen you perform.
Please go see
Tenacious D in concert.
-Thank you.
-It's unbelievable.
And you do a -- you do a thing
with a thing called
the Sax-A-Boom.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-It's a toy, or -- What was it?
-Well, it's like a saxophone,
but it's a Sax-A-Boom.
It's a -- It's a different
kind of instrument.
A lot of people confuse them.
-People confuse them?
-Well, you know,
'cause they look similar.
But a Sax-A-Boom is
its own kind of instrument
that takes years to master.
But, yeah,
thank you for remembering
about my Sax-A-Boom days.
-Well, I was just wondering,
if we happen to have one here...
-What?
-...could you maybe just show us
what it's like to --
-You don't have a Sax--
Oh, my God!
[ Cheers and applause ]
-This is a Sax-A-Boom.
-Are you kidding me?
-This is a real -- This is a --
You know how hard it was
to find a Sax-A-Boom?
Could you show us
the -- the magic?
Could you give us
a little taste?
-Here it is.
Rare as a Stradivarius.
Yes, I will give you a taste.
[ Laughter ]
Are you ready?
-Yeah. Wow.
[ Laughter ]
[ Sax-A-Boom plays ]
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, mother [bleep].
[ Sax-A-Boom plays ]
One, two, three, four!
♪♪
[ The Roots join ]
-That is how you do it
right there, everybody!
That is Jack Black!
Go see "The House with a Clock
in Its Walls," opening tomorrow.
More with Jack Black when
we come back, everybody.
♪♪