[Music]
ladies and gentlemen we are gathered
here today to answer an age-old question
right what's Amy's deal is she single no
we're dating come on the question is who
here does the best impression of Captain
Raymond Holt you will be judged on voice
body language and overall lack of flair
everyone will perform the same scenario
Captain halt eating a marshmallow for
the very first time let the halt off
begin what is this glutinous monstrosity
before me sugar in this is quite sweet
that's your whole impression I can hear
him doing that looks like a stick a
sticky low I don't care for it classical
music
what's going on here what are you doing
Captain hey nothing just eating some
marshmallows care for one marshmallow
I know it hey Charles wanna grab a beer
before you go home oh a yeast never mind
no no I want to go it's just there's a
huge emergency I have to deal with first
oh no is everything okay it's about my
food truck I have to get a parking spot
oh that doesn't sound as intense as you
were making it out to be
what is happening we have to get there
by seven o'clock when they lift the
parking restrictions it
wants it get the hell out of the way
Charles I highly doubt the entire food
truck industry is racing to get into
this one spot it's not Mad Max we're
neck and neck with rice pudding you got
Korean Tacos on your six oh my God it's
real we're on the Fury Road
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God Rose is wearing pink Rosa's
wearing pink are we sure it's not a
white shirt that's just been bloodied in
a motorcycle crash well maybe it wasn't
her does she have a twin sister if Rosa
had a twin she would have eaten her in
the womb wait pull it stop how come none
of you teased her about it it's Rosa
she's scary you guys are unbelievable I
once wore a tie with a splash of purple
you guys called me Mr grapes for two
years oh Mr Grace I forgot about Mr
Graves if I wore a pink shirt you'd tear
me to shreds well yeah but you'd look
like a My Little Pony with a gun let me
guess your theater Club is putting on
grease and you're playing a pink lady
what are you guys laughing at if Boyle
was wearing a pink shirt I get it that's
hilarious what's happening Rose is the
one wearing pink
and
it's gorgeous wish I could pull that off
dream on Strawberry Shortcake yeah nice
try Mr grapes
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't believe they're waxing the floor
then we're all stuck in here I've never
seen them do this
we're going to Florida ah I don't listen
to so much stuff you all say well
frankly I pitied a lot of you you look
out there and see a problem I look out
there and see an opportunity I'm gonna
slide on that slippery floor all the way
from Holt's office to the elevator
you're gonna do the fbp that's right
Rosa
I'm doing the full bullpen
[Music]
here we go
thank you
the full bullpen
you can't take it from me you bastard
don't do this Skully you have to be
stronger right now what's going on
unit's being replaced come on that
machine's been here forever it's
basically part of the force take Scully
instead yes please take me to the land
of ending machines can we at least have
five minutes to say a proper goodbye
whatever
let me just start by saying that this
machine is the best restaurant in
Brooklyn and it always had a table for
me and you just were to punch it to get
free food you have to go back to
punching Hitchcock look she still has
the bags of baby carrots I requests that
they put in they're black now but
they're there goodbye beautiful machine
thank you for your service
okay
Squad salute
you can take her away now
well I think we handled that with
dignity
free candy
[Applause]
I've been going at it for six hours he
won't say a word the guy's a brick wall
not to worry Sarge I'll take it from
here hope you boys brought popcorn
because I'm about to put on a show
well well well I hear you don't like
answering questions Marcos that's fine
by me because I'm not asking him will
fill up
um
nope so looks like we're locked in
that's bad news for you
has anyone tried it from the outside
Lock's broken got to call facilities
copy that no rush as I said I got all
the time in the worst little warming
area do you feel any air coming out of
that vent I got nothing we got an ETA on
facilities at least 45 minutes I have
checked all this paint for lead right
and the room for asbestos I feel like
I'm sucking on a tailpipe in here Marcos
everybody get away from the mirror
hey calm down man I'll confess just stop
freaking out what I did it I robbed them
boom and that's how it's done I was
faking the whole thing to break them I
could have stayed in here forever good
because facilities gonna be a couple
hours we're gonna die in here
another cold brew don't mind if I cold
do nailed it I am loving this machine
that Charles brought in it is nice the
trick is to let the coffee warm up to
room temperature I'm already on my
second cup this is my third
too much wow what's going on Charles why
are you talking so slow
[Music]
oh my God if you're not going to sell
that means we're going faster we're
going fast can everyone tell if we're
going fast I think we're going past it
all in any way whatsoever I feel like
we're going slow and everywhere
whatsoever Captain how do you feel great
excellent amazing I feel better than
I've ever felt it in a moment in my
entire life so we're all fine yep yep
yep yep yep yep yep
hey you guys see the dude I brought in
today the drug dealer 81 years old I
think it's the oldest collar of my
entire career I once arrested a 96 year
old for flashing I was terrified he'd
die in my backseat flash me my oldest
collar was 78 but the PCP made her fight
like she was 20. what about 250 year old
twins does that count as 100 year old no
good no you talking all this bags
68. that's not that old yeah but I was
only 20 20. were you even a cop then no
man it was before I got into the academy
Charles isn't talking about his oldest
arrest
no yes yes I am yeah oldest arrest 68
like I said God you had sex with a 68
year old when you were in your 20s you
know how it is when you have a chance to
bed an older woman no that is not an
older woman that's an old woman that's
someone's grandma she was actually
that's how I met her grandson Marvin
don't knock it to your trick she had a
replacement hit with some serious torque
no like having sex with a Transformer
that is no one's fantasy good morning
everyone oh my goodness Sarge what are
the chances I say zero oh I mean when
Genevieve gotten these suspenders I
thought I'd lean into it and go for the
whole look but I didn't want to step on
your toes that being said you know what
this means don't do this Charles oh it's
already done
gather around y'all it's time to play
who wore it best I'd really rather do
that because you're a little chicken
who wore it best who wore it best who
wore it best
what come on you should change Boyle
not here sir you wanted to see me yes I
have an assignment for you I'm afraid
it's not a pleasant one oh my God please
tell me it's not yes it's Hitchcock
related
protective Hitchcock is set to testify
in court this afternoon it's an
important case and I'd rather not get
another call from the D.A saying he
showed up quote covered in condiments
unquote so you want me to keep Hitchcock
from spilling on himself for the rest of
the day we both know that's impossible
I'm counting on I won't do it there's
nobody else I trust what you're asking
is insane I'm not asked it's a suicide
mission prepare for death you've lost
your mind this is a direct order
detective get in line hey you guys
startled Hitchcock he spilled two full
jars of spaghetti sauce on himself
thanks a lot fellas
so again your Alibi is a mysterious
stranger handed you the gun made you put
your prince on it robbed the store and
then hid the gun in your underpants Well
yeah if you say it like that it don't
sound believable oh hey Captain did you
get my report on the Finley murder uh
yeah looked it over nice word good
thanks Dad
why is everyone staring at me you just
called Captain hold dad he said thanks
Dad what no I didn't I said thanks man
do you see me as a father figure Peralta
no if anything I see you is a bother
figure because you're always bothering
me hey show your father some respect I
didn't call him Dad no no no no Jacob I
take it as a compliment it's not a big
deal I called Vivian mom once and she's
my fiance guys jump on that Boyle has
psychosexual issues old news but you
calling Hulk Daddy hey Daddy is not on
the table here but you did call him dead
dude you shut up you've done nothing but
lie since you got here all right all
right I was lying about the holdup but
the dad thing that happened
admitted that his Alibi was a lie it was
a trap all part of my crazy devious plan
I believe you thank you son
you want to talk about it later over a
game of catch
I'd like that
oh yeah
I'm Phillip Davidson detective Jake Paul
to ask me to drop by
the dentist who murdered some
have fun in there thank you
[Music]
what are you smiling about how
uncomfortable this guy is jacked up the
thermostat got the table all sticky made
one of the chair legs too short and
worst of all I had Gina greet him what
did you however do be yourself of course
son of a [ __ ] yeah why are you wearing
a tuxedo Kevin and I are attending the
Opera oh the Opera is it the one Bugs
Bunny sings
yes so who's this this is Philip
Davidson what do we have on them clear
motive clear means and a non-existent
alibi but the da won't bring a charge
because he says it's all circumstantial
if we want to bring this guy down we
have to get him to confess right here
right now an interrogation with a
ticking clock and everything on the line
I better call Kevin and tell him I won't
be attending the Opera there's someone
else I'd rather hear saying oh damn
hello Kevin I won't be joining you
forever tonight
the tickets under my name h o l
I'm here I'm here I'm here
you can start the meeting now the
meeting is over you're late you missed
roll call and the tutorial on using the
new copier six years and no matter how
hard I try I still can't get you to
understand The Importance of Being
punctual maybe you should just give up
and accept me for who I am no I will
break you right now while you were out
being tardy I was hardly worked advising
a special punishment I've crafted an
intricate personal high five with
everyone in this office except you what
but you hate high fives yes every minute
of it was hell but it'll be worse for
you Squad dismissed
the body is
[Music]
that's the butt bump goodbye Santiago
double fist bump reverse explosion into
a Pete Townsend strum
all right that was terrible but it's
over now and I made it through goodbye
Leonard from Xerox what no no
the copy guy sir I'd like to talk to you
about the new task force here on the
hiring committee for the special
tactical operations and auxiliary
strategic response city-wide emergency
investigative unit for Emergency
Operations you know I had a hand in
naming it and it's great although you
might want to try shortening it maybe
using a cool acronym so the
s-t-o-a-s-r-c-e-i-u-e-o you're right
that is cool sure anyways I know some of
the best cops in the city are going to
be on that task force and I would
appreciate it if you consider me for it
here's my resume and I thought it would
be fun if I wrapped it
but then I realized that would be a
terrible idea so I just wrote it down
normally it'll probably rhyme a lot on
accident try not to focus on that Jake
Peralta is age 39 but professionally
he's still in his prime if you ask me
he's New York's fine ellipses asked
Charles
the lyrics we discussed either anyways
sir I really think that I deserve this
task force my clearance rate puts me in
the top two percent of all NYPD I am
aware of your qualifications Peralta but
I'm only allowed to recommend one name
for the sto asrci ueo and you don't
think the acronym's just a little clunky
look I really feel like I've got what it
takes I'm experienced I'm hard working
and I'm unflappable in the face of
that I've just received the email about
whether I've gotten the job as
commissioner
well from the look on my face I'm sure
you can guess what it says
no we have no idea at all just tell us
you monster really no one noticed the
slight tension in my labial Commission
my lips I'm smiling wait you're smiling
wait we're allowed to say labia again
wait you got you got it I got it
maybe a commissioner Raymond Holt labia
you got to stop right now Hitchcock we
need to celebrate we need music oh
gmcd for the wedding oh we didn't talk
about that it was gonna be a surprise
our first dance was going to be in a
Tootsie Roll oh no we didn't get to do
it I know all right nobody moved I'm
gonna go get the CD
I want to thank you all what an
incredible moment 30 years of struggle
and sacrifice but it was worth it
because I finally get to read the 10
words I have long to hear Raymond Holt
you are not the oops I misread the email
didn't see the knot
so I will not
be the new commissioner
[Music]
why is no one else dancing did I miss
something feels like I missed something
I'm just gonna keep going until someone
tells me all right good morning boy it's
Halloween
I'm surprised you didn't put on a
costume I was going to sir but then I
decided screw that jazz
well I'm the only one who ever dresses
up no one ever gets my costume and they
make fun of me so I'm done
these people don't deserve my dress-up
gifts
Charles
seriously no costume what
what have never once insulted you in my
life especially vis-a-vis your
appearance yeah man we always love your
costumes remember last year when you
came as that
person and or thing yes I do remember
sir permission is Sprint to my car and
get my emergency costume does it matter
if I say no no
[Music]
Bam Bam Boom
why are you dressed up you look like an
idiot but but yeah what are you supposed
to be
no come on he's clearly the rejected
Pop-Tarts mascot Harry Pop Tarts I'm
Squad that's enough you're making boil
for bad on purpose he's Elvis
Elvis stoico the Canadian figure skater
no
interesting
[Music]
guys Captain Holt has no pants on
um
what he has no pants on is what here are
the facts at 11 55 a.m Captain Holt
walked past us holding a hot bowl of
soup at 1203 PM I heard him yell
ouch then at 1207 he called Gina into
his office she entered holding nothing
one minute later she left holding an
opaque bag
Captain Holt's pants were in that bag
his knees are in the breeze he's in his
undies that
so you guys want visual confirmation no
no hey Captain I just need you to sign
something at my desk real quick just
leave it on the couch dismissed okay sir
you're gonna freak Yo-Yo Ma is in the
precinct and he's giving out autographs
Yo-Yo Ma is on tour in Australia right
now how would you know that
I'm choking on a lozenge I'm gonna die
hey hey there's another bowl of soup
since you spilled yours earlier but
you're gonna have to come over here to
get it all right I'm sick are you
wasting time so yes I spilled some in my
pants and I'm sitting in my underwear
happy yes
ah
sir I need you to sign off on look at us
just three people with pants on having a
normal conversation yep no story here
[Music]