[Music]
it's rude but she asked for privacy
thanks raj
okay so here's the thing
i was wondering if you could maybe teach
me a little physics
a little physics
there's no such thing physics
encompasses the entire universe from
quantum particles to supernovas from
spinning electrons to spinning galaxies
yeah okay cool i don't need the pbs
special
i just want to know enough so i can talk
to leonard about his job you know like
bernadette does
why can't leonard teach you because i
want to surprise him can't you surprise
him in some other way for example i'm
sure he'd be delightfully taken aback if
you cleaned your apartment
come on sheldon this is important to me
penny this would be a massive
undertaking and my time is both limited
and valuable
they're sitting here playing video games
all day
okay point
what sort of foundation do you have did
you take any science classes in school
sure i did the one with the frogs
the one with the frogs
yeah actually it was pretty cool a lot
of the girls threw up but i gutted that
thing like a deer i'm done i'm sorry
penny i don't think so no no the sixth
season is great we go to paris with
carrie and get our heart broken and then
mr big shows up we don't know if we can
trust him again
it's a wild ride
door
okay everybody and plie
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and releave
what you doing
last one holding the ring decides it's
fate i know it sounds silly no no no no
you are my boyfriend nothing you do is
silly to me thank you fyi
this
the bag from victoria's secret
i'm out
hey do you think the elastic woman in
the incredibles needs to use birth
control or can she just be a diaphragm
well that's it we're officially out of
things to talk about
we're home
it's ten o'clock where have you been we
stayed for the california adventure
water show it was pure disney magic
i was gonna see that with him how was i
supposed to know that it's all right
i'll see it again with you and i have
food here you said you were gonna call i
know i know i can still eat no you
already threw up once go put on your pjs
and brush your teeth
okay but just don't fight we're not
fighting just go
aren't you gonna thank penny for taking
you to disneyland thank you penny
you're welcome sweetie
want a cup of coffee
oh um
i should probably get going i need your
official answer well it's not what he
said then what is it i want a different
question you can't have a different
question formal protest denied informal
protest
denied
i need your official answer no i
declined to provide one well that's too
bad because the answer your teammate
gave was correct
that's your opinion
all right the winner of the match is
hang on
sheldon is proving that you are
single-handedly smarter than everyone
else so important that you would rather
lose by yourself than win as part of a
team
i don't understand the question
go ahead
the winner is pms
[Music]
my friends
[Applause]
[Music]
what do you want howard
i'm fine thanks for asking
i've come to call on missy
missy
[Music]
hi howard the amazing howard
do you like magic
not really no
then you are in for a treat
behold an ordinary cane
[Music]
no
okay
[Music]
missy
thank you i appreciate
oh honey is your medication wearing off
ah cutie pie
i was hoping you'd show up
[Music]
thanks shorty i'll take it from here
all right you people ready to have some
fun you have a basic understanding of
differential calculus and at least one
year algebraic topology
well here come the jokes
why did the chicken cross the mobius
strip
to get to the same side buzzing
neutron walks into a bar and asks how
much for a drink the bartender says for
you no charge
hello
i know you're out there i can hear you
metabolizing oxygen and expelling carbon
dioxide
it looks like we have some academic
dignitaries in the audience uh dr
randall from the geology department only
man who's happy when they take his work
for granted but uh
i've kid the geologist of course but
it's only because i have no respect for
the field
let's get serious for a moment
why are we all here
cause we're scientists
and what do scientists study
the universe
and what's the universe made of
i am so glad you asked
there's antimony arsenic aluminum
selenium and hydrogen and oxygen and
nitrogen rhenium i thought maybe after
we eat we could see an early movie i'd
love that
i love the way you say i'd love that
she says it the same way i do
i'd love that
everybody in india says it that way it's
not a big deal
rajesh don't be a child i'm not being a
child
leonard i swear to god if your sister
ever comes to town i shall have my way
with her
my sister's 38 and married
all the more shame that will fall upon
the house of hosta
oh i thought i smelled pizza that's
remarkable if pepperoni were an
explosive substance you could replace
german shepherds at our nation's
airports
hi benny right oh yes hi hi i'm sorry i
didn't know you had company i don't want
to impose
it's not an imposition
at this point in our ecosystem you are
akin to the plover a small scavenging
bird that eats extra food from between
the teeth of crocodiles
please fly into our open mall and have
at it
penny
what's up buttercup
you have to get rid of the chair nope
penny
what's the word hummingbird
for your safety please wait in my
apartment as i call the authorities so
they may remove the chair of death
no
penny
what's a gist physicist
under my authority as a self-appointed
member of the centers for disease
control street team
these premises are condemned
as a man
with a keen sense of style
i must tell you that chair does not work
with the room
penny
all right so i see here you're from des
moines iowa uh you're summa laude in
theoretical physics from stanford
university oh and two years ago you had
a persistent ear infection
i hope that didn't cause any hearing
loss no of course not
how did you know about that
well i did a comprehensive background
check media medical records credit
reports criminal history i trust you
paid off those parking tickets
yes i did hearing unimpaired good
look dr cooper i really want this
position it would be an incredible honor
to work for a man of your brilliance
flattery will not get you this job miss
jensen
it's not flattery if it's the truth
oh
well thank you welcome aboard
hey i wasn't expecting to hear from you
today everything okay uh no not really
what's wrong well remember that
soyuz capsule they were stunning to
bring us home uh-huh it's delayed we're
gonna be here at least another week
maybe ten days it's the russian so you
don't know
they left dogs up here on the sixth day
come on howard no one's leaving you up
there i don't know how much longer i can
take this i can't sleep
and zero gravity is giving me crazy acid
reflux
i'm down to my last three times
you're going to be fine you survived
that weight watchers cruise with your
mom
and they ran out of low-fat ice cream on
day two
just calm down and take a few deep
breaths okay okay
what am i doing i'm using up all the
oxygen
if i die promise you'll never have sex
with another man
[Music]