♪ Is this the real life ♪
♪ Is this just fantasy ♪
♪ Caught in a landslide ♪
♪ No escape from reality ♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ Look up to the skies and see ♪
♪ I'm just a poor boy ♪
♪ I need no sympathy ♪
♪ Because I'm easy come, easy go ♪
♪ Little high, little low ♪
♪ Any way the wind blows ♪
♪ Doesn't really matter to me ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Mama, just killed a man ♪
♪ Put a gun against his head ♪
♪ Pulled my trigger, now he's dead ♪
♪ Mama, life had just begun ♪
♪ But now I've gone and
thrown it all away ♪
♪ Mama, ooh ♪
♪ Didn't mean to make you cry ♪
♪ If I'm not back again
this time tomorrow ♪
♪ Carry on, carry on ♪
♪ As if nothing really matters ♪
(gentle piano solo)
♪ Too late, my time has come ♪
♪ Sends shivers down my spine ♪
♪ Body's aching all the time ♪
♪ Goodbye everybody, I've got to go ♪
♪ Gotta leave you all
behind and face the truth ♪
♪ Mama, ooh ♪
♪ As the wind blows ♪
♪ I don't want to die ♪
♪ I sometimes wish I'd
never been born at all ♪
(electric guitar solo)
(rhythmic piano solo)
♪ I see a little silhouetto of a man ♪
♪ Scaramouche, Scaramouche,
will you do the Fandango ♪
♪ Thunderbolt and lightning ♪
♪ Very, very frightening me ♪
♪ Galileo, Galileo ♪
♪ Galileo Figaro ♪
♪ Magnifico o o o o ♪
♪ I'm just a poor boy, nobody loves me ♪
♪ He's just a poor boy
from a poor family ♪
♪ Spare him his life
from this monstrosity ♪
♪ Easy come, easy go, will you let me go ♪
♪ Bismillah ♪
♪ No, we will not let you go, let him go ♪
♪ Bismillah, we will not
let you go, let him go ♪
let you go, let me go ♪
♪ Will not let you go, let me go ♪
♪ Never let you go, never,
never, never, never let me go ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Oh, mama mia, mama mia,
mama mia, let me go ♪
♪ Beelzebub has a devil put aside for me ♪
♪ For me, for me ♪
(energetic guitar music)
♪ So you think you can stone
me and spit in my eye ♪
♪ So you think you can love
me and leave me to die ♪
♪ Oh, baby, can't do this to me, baby ♪
♪ Just gotta get out, just
gotta get right outta here ♪
(energetic rock music)
♪ Ooooh, ooh yeah, ooh yeah ♪
(slow rock music)
♪ Nothing really matters ♪
♪ Anyone can see ♪
♪ Nothing really matters to me ♪
(slow quiet piano music)
(slow quiet electric guitar)
♪ Any way the wind blows ♪
(soft cymbal crash)