Will Ferrell is overrated
sorry but he just screams it's gotcha
Jon Hamm is a soft boy with a dad bod
hashtag truth you Chris Rock you are
grownups too
well if you lost all your money in
divorce
you'd be all grown ups too - I'd rather
plant poison ivy plants in my anus
before hearing another word about Kim
Kardashian and go ahead and do that
please
Maisie Williams looks like a very young
grandma
[Music]
hashtag David Harbour hey I'm ready to
be punched in the face bring it back
it's nice I just cut a fart that smells
so bad they added David Spade as a
supporting character that's not bad
hyukoh addition for that I didn't know
if I got it
Jake Gyllenhaal's smells like hot dog
water haiku like a beaut beautiful
beautiful things say a Benson dais feet
smell like Funyuns
let's check shall we know smells like
success to me kid only to grow up
looking like a creep yes Fred Savage I'm
talking about you that's true
Tiffany Haddish has a big-ass mouth you
can't bring ratchet ass like her
no we're just Shep well you know what
why don't you shut with your 14
followers but thank you for introducing
me to them you think Martin shorts had
sex
I bet Martin shorts never had sex
the older Mark Hamill gets the more he
looks like Yoda seriously
seeing that guy lately he's Yoda me and
burn this is Sarah Paulson you I
have mixed feelings about you right now
guess what mother flick I have mixed
feelings about you too cap cap says Jeff
Goldblum is starting to annoy me now
like okay dude you're quirky we get it
you have some weird sweaters good for
you I I know what you're talking about
believe you me if I was in your shoes I
might feel the same way like my new
shirt thanks for watching if you liked
that video click the subscribe button
and if you didn't like it will you hurt
my feelings