first there was PlayStation AKA PS1 then
there's PS2 PS3 and now PS4 and that
makes sense You' think after Xbox
there'd be Xbox 2 but no next came Xbox
360 and now after 360 comes Xbox
One y one maybe that's how many seconds
of thought they put in the naming
it can you get the butter please yeah
however with the Xbox one I can control
my entire entertainment system using
voice commands up until now I've had to
use
Leonard then get the other one pass the
butter get hang
on I don't feel like you're taking this
dilemma
seriously fine Sheldon you have my
undivided attention okay now the PS4 is
more angular and Sleek looking no way
it's true but the larger size of the
Xbox one may keep it from overheating
well you wouldn't want gaming system to
overheat no well you absolutely would
not and furthermore the Xbox one now
comes with a connect included included
yes not sold separately although the PS4
uses cool new gddr5 Ram while the Xbox
one is still using the conventional DDR3
memory why would they still be using
DDR3 are they
nuts see that's what I thought but then
they go and throw in an es Ram buffer me
to say who's they the Xbox you're
kidding no I am not and this es Ram
buffer should totally Bridge the 100
gbit per second bandwidth gap between
the two Ram types this is a nightmare
how will you ever make a decision you
see I don't know what should I do please
pass the
buyer I'm proud of you shelden you know
I'm proud of me too I've done all my
research I conducted an informal poll
and I've to the Rock Solid certainty
I've made the right choice well that's
got to be a good feeling oh it is
although oh
crap now I had the same feeling when I
made my dad buy a betamax instead of a
VHS you were just a little kid yeah a
little kid who picked the wrong format
to record the McNeil Lara
report I also was certain that HD DVD
would win out over Blu-ray how old were
you then old enough to know better
you know and now that I think about it I
stood in front of a case of iPods and I
bought a
zoom what's a zoom yo
exactly it's an MP3 player brought To Us
by the makers of
Xbox no no what are you doing no pick
that back up you know it's good you did
the research but what if I'm
wrong you know what how about I buy it
for you how about I buy you both both
you know I only have one slot available
on my entertainment center then I'll buy
you a new entertainment center yeah okay
sure but which
one how about this I've heard that if
you flip a coin it will tell you how you
actually feel because you'll either be
disappointed or excited by the outcome
interesting so heads it's PS4 Tails it's
Xbox
one all right I'll try
what is it a
quarter could have given it back to me
that was a
choice on the one hand the Xbox one has
a better camera but the PS4 has a
removable hard
drive
thoughts I can't feel my legs
oh I'm sorry guys but the store closed 5
minutes ago but I haven't decided yet
you have to come back tomorrow the
registers are
closed let's get you some food you
you'll feel better after you eat
okay what do you want like Thai food uh
a
burger I don't know
[Laughter]
[Applause]
hey look a
quarter I'm
back I'm sorry I yelled at you it's not
your fault what happened well I went
over to Mike's to make up with him yeah
no I know that
par but he had already moved on already
that was quick that's what I said to the
woman who had her legs wrapped around
his
neck oh Penny I am so sorry how could he
do that well you know you did throw an
80 gig iPod yeah no how could he do that
I swear to God I'm done with guys like
that you know Macho with the perfect
body and the hair and the money yeah
that must get old
quick you know just once I would like to
go out with someone who is nice and
honest and who actually cares about
me what about me what about you
what what about if you went out with
me are you asking me
out um yes I am asking you
out wow
I was just going off your comment about
the nice guy no I know and honest
totally so but it's no big deal
yes guess
what yes I will go out with
you
really yeah why not I mean what do I
have to lose
yeah that's the spirit
hi hi come on in thank
you you look very nice thank you so do
you I made an 8:00 reservation okay yeah
great listen um maybe we should talk
first
oh you're watching football there's no
fooling
you now what is this Sach statistic they
put up there all I know about Sachs is
my mother shops
there
sacks sack it's football nomenclature
for when a quarterback is tackled behind
the line of scrimmage huh
scrimmage the line of scrimmage is the
imaginary transverse line separating the
offense from the
defense
oh Sheldon knows
football apparently I mean quid it sure
but
football Sheldon how do you know this
stuff I grew up in Texas football is
ubiquitous in Texas pro football college
football high school football peeee
football in fact every form of football
except the original European
football which most Texans believe to be
a commi
plot unbelievable if you're interested I
also know all about frying meat that
isn't chicken as if it were
chicken so you could teach
me football or chicken fried
Meats football I'm going to Pennies on
Saturday to watch a game with our
friends and I don't want to look like an
idiot I want to blend in you want to
blend in with Penny's friends I think
looking like an idiot would be the
perfect
camouflage on sh please teach me
football it'll be fun that's exactly
what my father said come to the games
watch the games week in and week out
from the time I was five until I went
off to college longest seven years of my
life please I'm asking you as a
friend are you making this a tier one
friendship request
yes fine I really appreciate this yeah
yeah all right Point Dexter sit down
shut up and
listen I'm sorry that's how my father
always began our football
conversations and if you'd like after
the game I'll take you outside and teach
you how to shoot close enough to Raccoon
that it craps itself
oh look how cute you were Amy please of
course I was cute look how I turned
out hello Sheldon hello
Sheldon if you're watching this I assume
something bad has happened something
unfortunate and
unforeseen something that's making you
question
everything I'm so
smart now just make sure it's really you
watch list not an
impostor what am I thinking of on the
count of three 1 2 3 Robot Monkey
Butler okay
good should I leave you two
alone no this is going to be inspiring
you should watch Sheldon never forget no
matter how bad things seem you can all
what what no no my dad taped over at one
of his stupid High School football games
sorry you know it doesn't matter nothing
matters is there anything I can do yes
you could build me a time machine so I
can go back and tell my younger self to
give up because nothing's going to work
out the way he
wants just thinking a nice cup of leaf
soup you're looking for a job a menial
job
like
yours well thank you for
noticing my menial employee of the
month do you have a particular field in
mind I do for thousands of years the
lowest classes of the human race have
spent their lives laboring to erect
monuments under the Lash of their bers
until finally they dropped down and
became one with the dust through which
they
trudged do you have anything like like
that
no shouldn't you check your
database
[Applause]
no you didn't really
type I didn't really have
to so how about construction oh that
would be good is sawing hammering eating
out of a lunch pail as my working class
fellows and I sit PCH precariously on a
gerder high above the
Metropolis no no this is putting up
sheetrock at a housing project in Rose
me I could do that good one question yes
what's
sheetrock moving
on how about doing deliveries for a
florist that seems acceptable do you
have your own car I don't
drive of course you
don't Mr Cooper let me just ask you a
question what was your last job senior
theoretical particle physicist at
Caltech focusing on M Theory or in
layman's term String
Theory I
see just give me a
second
security hey Sheldon
hello oh my God you look amazing I find
you guilty of murder because you are
killing
it well technically the Supreme Court
wouldn't determine a defendant skilled
or innocence in a criminal matter they
could only reverse or revamp a jury's
conviction based on a constitutional or
statutory
issue why are you
laughing his statement was was factually
correct you're sitting in my
spot you don't have a spot what is wrong
with you today maybe it's cranky because
he's off his bathroom
schedule Oh I can understand how that
would make someone
irritable interesting fact irritable
comes from the Latin susceptible to
anger just because I used a word doesn't
mean I wanted emology interesting
factology comes from the GRE you are
being so annoying stop is and why are
you two
laughing tell he's being you he's
dressed as you for
[Laughter]
Halloween
oh well so you're not laughing at him
you're laughing at me we're not laughing
at you we're laughing with you but I'm
not laughing
thing then the first
one let's go over our emotional
responses one last time okay Professor
tupperman is dead and that makes us
sad the fact that there are so many
people here tonight doesn't make us
cranky and claustrophobic it makes us
glad giving Mrs Davis the box set of
roots was
bad you however fine
B
unbelievable you have some nerve showing
up here just to Smo with the tenure
committee you're here excuse me I'm here
to pay my respects to Professor dare or
whatever his name is so am I his passing
makes me feel
bad well well well shadon fancy meeting
you here I guess the train store in
Glendale wasn't having a catian after
all
and you you said you weren't coming here
either I would take accent you don't
know what I
said I'd like to know why Penny's here
I'm here to support my man just like you
what are you going to do take people's
drink orders and get them
wrong do it
[Applause]
what did she do it
yet she plans on flirting with members
of the tenure committee to further
Leonard's cause well that's a fine how
do you do don't just St on there take
your breaths
out oo mere cat
fight you're all wasting your time
Sheldon is the most qualified for the
job and no amount of gravity def spying
bosom's going to change
that seriously is that tape like how are
they staying up like
that wa to hit him with both
barrels you two should be ashamed of
yourselves using women to advance your
cause with sexuality and whatever Amy
plans on
doing are you implying that my
girlfriend has no sexuality to exploit
yes okay because that was not clear
what that was ambiguous but well now
it's ambiguous what are you going to do
about it um you can talk some smack
about his mother yes of course he
wouldn't like that at
all last night I was feeling in need of
sexual release when I happened to come
across your
mother okay okay guys what are we doing
here I don't know what you're doing but
I was about to insinuate that I had
quitus with Raj's mother for a dollar
no you do what you want but I don't want
to lose my friends over tenure friends
are forever so is tenure
F I'm just going to go home and let my
work speak for itself you're right this
is beneath me like your mother was last
night how about it
Sheldon what do you think I should
do well you'll always be an academic
success
but I see seriously question whether you
make any more
friends well I don't want any more but
let's go are you kidding I would love to
babysit for you I could not ask you to
do that nonsense children love me
something about me just makes some W and
W no we cannot lose to that jerk yeah
screw it I'm going in you hold on I
believe screw it I'm going in is what I
said to your mother last
night don't worry I didn't really say
that I I find the concept of kius
ridiculous and
off-putting should have taken my breasts
out while I had the
chance Mrs Davis Mrs Davis Mrs
Davis I know you're in there I saw your
car in the parking
lot what I just found out that you
recommended myself Dr hoffstad and Dr
cther ply to be on the short list for
tenure well despite your quirks the
three of you are very accomplished in
your respective Fields I don't know what
you mean by quirks but
um I do want to express my gratitude you
didn't bring another gift did you no no
no I learned my lesson I understand that
was inappropriate
good anyway thank you you're
welcome why are you up am I supposed to
sleep been married less than 24 hours
and my wife isn't speaking to
me perhaps you can think of this in a
more positive light in one day you've
managed to do what it takes many couples
decades to
achieve hiy hey you couldn't sleep
either of course not me neither but I
just had a tickle in my
throat not profound marital
problems what are we going to do I don't
know please tell me how I can fix it I'm
glad you
asked as I see it there's a simple
solution your lips had a diance with the
lips of another woman it seems only
logical that to restore balance to the
relationship you should find find
another man and Dally with him and by
dally I mean some hardcore mouth on
mouth action okay that is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard actually think
he's on to
something well you can't be serious cuz
I messed up and made out with a girl
you're going to do the same with a
random guy I'm currently
single that's true you
are what is happening
I will tell you what is happening I am
saving my best friend's
marriage Amy is the one constant I can
count on and now she's changing it's
just a haircut and some clothes no it's
the last straw I can't take anymore
[Music]
believe it they finally fixed the
elevator this is a
nightmare what's with him he want a
Nobel Prize and his wife looks amazing
oh yeah got it
how did you get down here the elevator
it's really
fast I I need to be alone right now
don't try to follow me all right you
need a ride that'd be great thank you I
was thinking without Sheldon most of us
would have never met but Penny would
still live across from him and with
Leonard out of the picture we all know
what that would mean we
do hey Sheldon hello
doing
laundry of course I'm doing laundry
Saturday night is laundry night and I'm
in a laundry room so I believe your
inference is Justified my inference is
Justified Sheldon you are so
funny anyway I need to do my laundry too
because these clothes are so dirty
almost as dirty as the dirty girl who's
wearing
them okay that's enough disagree keep
going so what do you
think a tad asymmetrical but nothing to
be concerned
about please Sheldon I need you to
what to take me I'm not taking you any
till you put on a
shirt come on Sheldon you and me right
here penny for the thousandth time I'm
saving myself for someone special yeah
perhaps a cute bespectacled
neuroscientist with hair the color of
mud I think I know how to change your
mind that's
enough I was okay with it
how's it going Sheldon actually much
better oh good is the baby born yet I
don't know I just got back where'd you
go my mother asked me to get some towels
I took advantage of the vague request
and went to Bed Bath and
Beyond excuse me I'm on the
phone so rude
here's another one penny if it weren't
for Sheldon you never would have met
comic book Legend Stan
Lee
great well at least Leonard Howard and I
would have always been friends hey how
come you three never got an apartment
together we talked about it but Howard
was in a pretty serious relationship
with his
mom I lived with her to save money yeah
you didn't have to buy Gres cuzz you
were
[Laughter]
breastfeeding so I guess if it weren't
for me you'd still be living with her
huh not exactly what do you mean not
exactly well things would be a little
different how one with my lunch I'm
starving I know you're starving the
neighbors know you're starving they're
starving people never go know you're St
right that's it there's not enough food
well you cleaned out Earth I don't know
what else to
do how is he any different he didn't let
me
finish here you go
mother you're a good boy
how such a good
boy wait did she die or did you kill her
H tomato tomato the important thing is
she's
dead hey so how come you two didn't move
in together no this guy wanted a place
of his own because he was sure he was
going to be a ladies
man yeah I was
wrong but I do think you and I would
have had a great time come on Leonard
dinner com in
hang on why would I be
fat you'd have no girlfriend to see you
naked you'd try to fill the void with
food and I'm an enabler who wants deep
fried a
pancake why can't you be fat
too what do you want to do for
dessert I think there's still half a
cake from
breakfast no there's no
[Laughter]
hey
guys what are you doing
I just wanted to be in anyone's
[Music]
[Applause]
story yeah