I feel like if you went to lunch with
Natalie Portman she would only order a
hot tea with lemon and maybe some toast
definitely not an entree
though you're
wrong oh look at me I'm Ryan Gosling I
have perfect bone structure and kind
eyes go yourself Ryan
Gosling Samuel Jackson has resting fart
face yes I do I'm going to wipe balance
my TV on Jessica Chastain's
chest I don't even know what that
means are we all just ignoring the fact
that Eddie redm and Felicity Jones have
the same
face dear EDD redm I hate your stinking
guts you make me vomit you're the scum
between my toes love
aena Tanner raised his arms and my dad
looks at his armpit hair and says you
look like you have whoopy Goldberg a
headlock really that's it V Manel
Miranda looks like he's getting a 1996
NVC sitcom with his
haircut Casey Affleck is the real life
version of Billy Bob Thorton's character
Sling
Blade Emma Stone looks like a crack
in every role she
plays great Miles Teller has the face of
a guy who would request Gangam Style at
a wedding where he doesn't know either
the bride or
groom fair enough now is probably a good
time to remind everyone about this dog
that looks like Tilda
Swinton I think Jeff Bridges wears pants
a lot less than we all think he
does oh that's actually
true Robert denero is too old to be
making gangster movies still dude needs
to start uh playing grandfather roles or
something yeah I am playing grandfather
roles and pretty soon I'll be playing
great-grandfather roles
you do you love clicking buttons and
subscribing to things then click the
button to subscribe to my channel and
you'll finally be happy