I heard
that you're
settled down, that you
found a girl and you're
married now.
I heard that your dreams came true.
Guess she gave you things
I didn't give to you.
Oh, friend,
why are you so shy?
Ain't like you to hold back
or hide from the light.
I hate to turn up out of the blue,
uninvited, but I couldn't stay away. I
couldn't fight it. I had hoped you'd see
my face and that you'd be reminded that
for me it isn't over.
Never mind, I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you.
Don't forget me. I think I remember you
say sometimes it lasts and loves but
sometimes it hurts instead.
Sometimes it lasts and loves, but
sometimes it doesn't stay.
You know how the time flies only.
Yesterday
was the time of our lives. We were born
and raised
in a summer haze, bound by the surprise
of our glory
days.
I hate to turn up out of the blue,
uninvited, but I couldn't stay away. I
couldn't fight it. I had hoped you'd see
my face and that you'd be reminded that
for me it isn't over.
[Music]
Never mind. I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you,
too. Don't forget me. I beg I'll
remember you say sometimes it lasts in
love, but sometimes it hurts instead.
Nothing compares. No worries or cares.
Regrets and mistakes their memories
made. Who would have known how bitter
sweet
this would taste?
Never mind. I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you.
Don't forget me. I bet I remember you
said sometimes it lasts in love but
sometimes it hurts instead.
Never mind. I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you,
too. Don't forget me. I begged. I
remember. You say sometimes it lasts in
love, but sometimes it hurts instead.
Sometimes it lasts in love, but
sometimes it hurts instead.
Yeah.
[Music]
Heat.