so there you have it a shockingly
unshocking press conference in which a
recently unemployed woman said nothing
of importance I'm heard happily and I
just realized I'm not holding my
microphone
Chris I'm dying I was dying earlier
today and then I died now I'm dead I had
to cancel a date with SH mway tweep and
I really like her you think she to like
me now that I'm dead what is this it's
food
poisoning I have it too I did not sleep
for one second last night and I cracked
the bottom of the toilet bowl oh God
don't say that has anybody talked to Tom
I can't even imagine what that tiny
little man must be feeling like I have
voided more than Tom's body weight in
the last 12 hours alone he might have
just disappeared off the Earth we need
to call him we must reach out to him
I can't do
it
Ben extension
7820 hello fellow ponant as you know the
founders week festivities kick off
tomorrow um one small announcement due
to a tragic misunderstanding the
prettiest Pig beauty pageant has been
replaced by a pork rib barbecue
competition oh no yeah everyone before
everyone else gets here I'd like to make
a little toast my romantic life has been
a bit of a mixed bag lately and when
that's the case it's hard not to be
cynical about love and relationships but
it's couples like you that give hope to
the the rest of us Leslie you deserve
the best and you found it Ben don't you
dare hurt
her I won't don't laugh she means it I I
won't seriously son don't hurt her okay
I'm not planning on hurting her you
better not be I'm not hey Ben you best
watch yourself why would any of you
think I would hurt lesie you're all my
friends
[Music]
too you're really shouldn't have dug
that out of the dumpster I had to also I
had a banana on the way over here sorry
and I get why you don't want anyone to
know about Duke silver and you don't
have to worry your secret is safe with
me to even it out I'm going to tell you
all of my secrets oh no that's not
necessary I once forgot to brush my
teeth for 5 weeks I didn't actually sell
my last car I just forgot where I parked
it I don't know who Al Gore is and at
this point I'm too afraid to ask when
they say 2% milk I don't know what the
other 98% is when I was a baby my head
was so big scientist it experiments on
me I once threw a beer at a swan and
then it attacked my niece Rebecca
that'll do Andrew hello everyone we are
here today to discuss Grizzle and
whether or not they are invading our
privacy they sent my husband three boxes
of genital cream to his office my
husband's splotchy genitals are no one's
business except for his mine and his
many genital
doctors they sent me a bunch of toy pigs
dressed like movie stars that's my
private hobby no one knows I collect toy
pigs dressed like movie stars except now
all of you people which one is that this
is actually Hamel L Jackson from the
movie pork Fiction it's extremely rare
and I am keeping it but still they have
no right to give me something I will
treasure the rest of my life I opened my
box in front of all my friends and it
was a bunch of Virginia wolf novels now
Miley and Haley know I like to read what
if they tell Evan I like their phones
but they've gone too far sending this
stuff to our houses Grizzle has no right
to search our private data so wait you
guys are not against us on this we're
not against you on this we're not
against you on this we're not against
you on this forever young i w to be hey
Tom um what's up do you want to go to
lunch uh no I don't really feel like
going to JJ's we can go anywhere your
choice I'm I'm buying can I get abson
desserts desserts are what I call
desserts tray trays or Entre I call
sandwiches samies sandles or Adam
Sandlers air conditioners are cool
blasters with a z I don't know where
that came from I call Cakes big old
cookies I call Noodles long ass rice
fried chicken is fry fry chicky chick
chicken parm is chicky chicky parm B
chicken catch aori chicky catch I call
eggs pre- birds or future Birds root
beer is super water tortillas are bean
blankies and I call
Forks food
rakes yeah you can get as many zerts as
you want well let's get in my Gogo
mobile car I would like to be president
someday so no I've not smoked
marijuana I ate a brownie once at a
party in college it was intense it's
kind of indescribable actually I felt
like I was
floating turns out there wasn't any pot
in the brownie it was just an insanely
good brownie I hate it here this place
is evil I think these are the only two
films that say sweds on the label yeah
well let's take them both we might find
something interesting here just stick
them under my shirt just walk out they
have sensors just check them out it's
free hi Marcy
lesie are they finally teaching you
Parks people how to read oh I guess not
it's a movie you're pretty cocky for
someone whose job is obsolete because of
the
internet let's see hm you seem to have a
$40 late fee on a book called Mysteries
of the female orgasm no I don't yeah you
do and grab the mar go go go go p g book
jockey okay listen up folks we have a
security situation here as you know when
we reach a location I will be conducting
a security sweep also from now on we'll
be using code name you can address me as
Eagle One and code name Ben there done
that April is currently doing that Donna
is it happened once in a dream Chris
code name if I had to pick a dude Ben is
Eagle 2 oh thank God hello I'm here for
the interview about tonight's Gala yeah
listen I'm a little under the weather
when on a boo Cruise last week just
finished up an hour ago on a completely
unrelated note
I have horrible allergies sorry to hear
that yeah but I do need to promote this
event well don't worry about me I'm a
true professional The Show Must Go On
two hello I'm Joan Calzo Today's Show
will not go
on seems like her allergies are kicking
in my name is Ron Swanson
I'm here to tell you about a black tie
Gala fundraiser for pawy Commons
happening tonight all proceeds will go
toward building a park it will be
enjoyable oh take a take a a phone call
now I will take your calls
apparently yes hey Joan settle a bet for
me who's the sexiest couple in history
our Pats and casew or
Bieber now Jerry is turning 64 this year
he's only 64 64 divided by 4 is 64 so
we're going to throw him a sweet 16
surprise party it's going to be very
special the usual cake and pop no April
the unusual fish and pop no cake and
fish no no fish Jerry only gets a real
birthday every four years and four years
from now who knows he might be retired
or dead let's start a pool who wants
retired who wants dead dead no I got one
dead no I need a few more volunteers
Andy will you be Iceland the bad guys
from Mighty Duck 2 don't think so okay
how about Japan the bad guys from Karate
Kid too even worse how about Germany
they've never been the bad guys why
don't you be Finland okay okay and I'll
be the moon no you're going to be South
Africa or Pakistan I'm the moon or I
quit April moon or quit man fine you be
South Africa and then you can also
secretly run the Moon the Moon accepts
your ridiculous proposal Ron you want to
join us look I'll let you be
America and teach kids that not only is
government good but that there should be
a worldwide super government I'd rather
sand down my toenails every 3 weeks I
have to sand down my
toenails they're too strong for Clippers
ah look who hasn't had Gay Thoughts who
you okay yeah I'm fine I'm fine I mean
you know sometimes I feel like I might
need glasses is there a bird in here I
swear I keep seeing a bird in the studio
maybe that's all to it he was fine until
purd started asking him about the boy
Mar stuff what's wrong with you you look
psychotic I was 18 when I was elected
mayor okay so excuse me for that Cindy
eert had just turned me down for senior
prompt you know how that feel I should
call her I should I no I shouldn't and
I'm not going to and I'm proud of myself
for that
girl and then he talked about feeling up
Cindy eard for the first time for about
5 minutes and then the show ended as did
our careers and probably Harvest
Fest boom sadness that's the one support
for pawy Community radio comes from the
Wendel G and Muriel faite coralan
foundation and Sweden's cares a
nonprofit group that puts umbrella hats
on homeless people when it
rains welcome to thoughts for your
thoughts I'm Derry merbles filling in
for David Parker who took off for 8
months to study the migration patterns
of our nation's squirrels we have not
seen him since my guest today is author
Leslie nope the book py The Greatest
Town in America Leslie could one say
that a book is nothing more than a
painting of Words which are the notes on
the tapestry of the greatest film ever
sculpted one could say
that but should one join us next week
when David be and will be filling
in for Richard ch Jefferson who will be
filling in for me Leslie would you like
to take us out
okay please enjoy a song from the
lesbian afro Norwegian Funk Duo
Nefertiti
Fjord oh wow they are terrible oh yes
they're they're quite awful but they are
lesbians
so now I know your gentleman had a long
flight but I have prepared a welcome
party in your honor excellent I like to
party well my job is to see to your
every need do we just uh select the
woman we
desire I will take the large black one
interesting choice what did you have
some kind of a book with photos of the
women available to us if not I will also
take the sexy black
one I am not surprised at all I've been
to South America I did very well there I
think there might have been a
translation problem when I said party I
meant one that did not include sex for
pay but one that had food and drink and
dancing that sort of thing so no women
no this ain't going to
work okay you did not just swivel away
while I was talking to you this
spaceship keyboard is driving me crazy
I'm down to one word a minute and the
word is perlus club because I can't fly
spaceship
Leslie I appreciate what you're trying
to do but once you go in there you will
see things you cannot unsee I'm a
feminist okay I would never ever go to a
strip club I've gone on record that if I
had to have a stripper's name it would
be equality but I'm willing to sacrifice
all that I've worked for just to put a
smile on your perverted little face so
don't blow this all right okay lap
dances are on me I mean I'm paying for
them they're not going to actually be on
me got it I kind of feel like Jane
Goodall studying The Chimps you know cuz
there are some feminist Scholars who say
that stripping is a feminist
act smile on your face I do not like the
way you went back on your deal with
councilwoman nope it reminds me of what
the settlers of paon did to my ancestors
taking their land without permission he
really plays white people like a fiddle
wow it's amazing to watch you and Leslie
had a deal if that deal is not restored
well I believe there are six punch
burgers in the wapo casino perhaps it's
time that we Revisited those contracts
is that a
threat why yes I I thought that was
obvious take the sign down we'll wait
until everything's official in the
spirit of fair play I suggest we put on
these authentic W pooke headdresses and
dance around the table absolutely not
that sounds highly offensive does it
white man
no it's not offensive so let's do it you
first so clearly this is not offensive
it is offensive I am very
secret eyeballs rats bats vampire teeth
boom vampire teeth good spider webs done
mhm fake blood capsules oh they didn't
have any
really that's gross I love it we are
throwing the Halloween party at our
house this going to be the greatest
thing ever someone will die of fun and
of murder there's going to be beer
pumpkins bloody goblins fake ones it's
going to be awesome we have decorations
dead people that we just murdered not
murdered but pictures of dead people
from TV or movies util bodies but fake
ones Candy dancing tequila all kinds of
food and snacks blood orphans no blood
orphans I I don't know what that is I
have done nothing wrong ever in my life
I know
this and I love you I love you too Daddy
money
please my
Ron
Ron last name
done is that your name or are you
telling me you're finished talking
both done and
done I like
on Leslie go home no I can't I can't go
home I have to get ready for the Chamber
of Secrets Commerce if this meeting does
not go perfectly then the Harvest
Festival is going to be over before it
began I cannot go home okay then who is
your doctor an's my doctor and she's the
most beautiful nurse in the world come
on oh God now I'm hot now it's really
hot here okay well that's your fever
lesie I typed your symptoms into the
thing up here and it says you could have
network connectivity
problems 100 4.1 Leslie you're
dehydrated I'm admitting you if I was
sick could I do
this what are you doing car
wheels am I not doing them no look don't
worry I've done presentations like this
before and Tom will be with me so you're
in good hands it's not that I don't
trust
Ben it's that I don't have faith in
Ben and also I'm starting to forget who
Ben is maybe we should get the sweet
here for them okay Ben Wyatt hello uh hi
lesie good to see you too wow you're
really burning up can I get some money
for the cab that I took over here please
sure how much I'm not sure I looked at
the meter and it had Egyptian
hieroglyphics on it do you know the
exchange rate so should we do this oh
boy hold on be careful what the floor
and the wall just
switched okay
walk very
carefully you might be thinking what
does an adult film star know about
politics well I produced and starred in
over 400 adult films this year alone
thank you and just like Leslie I know
what it's like to be the only woman in a
room full of men so as we know spring
hunting season is upon
us uh anyway here's the
about the new licensing
system um Jerry I don't I don't think
your computer is plugged in I'm sorry
guys just got to power up first thing we
should have is my graph about the season
what wait a minute no that is not the
graph that's a picture for my vacation
to Muny you went on a vacation and you
chose Muny Indiana yeah my wife and I
have a time share is M Tom m is a lovely
City
anyway hunting and fishing season is
winding down okay and we all know that
it's already close season on TW so
now I said twout instead of trout it
happens to everyone my marbles are full
of mouth
today you know what has anybody seen my
glasses I don't even think I
[Music]
can hey good morning why there's six
people outside who say they're waiting
to meet with me so you know how you love
me because you haven't had a single
meeting with anyone since I became your
assistant that's because every time
someone calls and requests a meeting
with you I always schedule it for March
31st why because I didn't think March
31st existed 30 days has September April
March and November June and
November today is March 31st I know so
then how many meetings do I have today
93 okay okay well you know what to do
right to me this situation is a blood
soaked nightmarish
hellscape however to Leslie nope oh how
fun yay and so when I finally cleaned up
the vomit I found the toe I forgot about
the toe so did we crazy right that story
is awesome indeed thank you for sharing
Jenny Ann was getting a little chummy
when people get too chummy with me I
like to call them by the wrong name to
let them know I don't really care about
them that's a genius move thank you
you're welcome Lester
oh