Mitchell's mother has a problem with
me last Christmas for example she gave
me a piece of exercise equipment and a
lettuce dryer so to recap I gave her a
gorgeous pair of diamond earrings and
she gave me a
hint my mom started drinking these
cocktails called horny Colombians with
some of Gloria's uncles whom apparently
the drink was named after oh come on
they were
funny
they kept patting my butt somebody's
full of herself it's a it's a Colombian
wedding tradition they
said I'm Gloria Kiss Me Oh Heiss
me Nana is really
strong it's totally supervised oh really
by whom by Spencer Pen's Uncle who was
Spencer ptin
you know Spencer the guy with the arm
wait what kind of arm what does that
even mean his uncle is Uncle Toby oh
Uncle Toby I'll be sure to include that
in my Amber Alert okay now everybody
calm down let's start from the beginning
what's wrong with Spencer's arm honey I
would love to let you go to the concert
are you kidding me I think concerts are
rad hello I was a hall raiser a what I
followed Hall and notes around the
country One Summer rich girl just spoke
to me I was dating this girl not
not dating I guess I was following her
too kind of Dad no who's dad who's Dad
I'm I'm Marcus from biology hey Haley
how's it going with you and Dylan has he
tried anything inappropriate with you
girl well I'm I'm moving to a far and
Dangerous Place Canada but uh she met a
man named Chaz he's a logger like a like
a lumberjack no he logs blood samples
into a cholesterol study anyway until
I'm past this whole wedding debacle I
can't be intimate with him we do things
to each other we use our
hands what that that is so not true if
if anything you're the one with a
screwed up relationship with Mommy with
with Mom Mommy no I didn't say damn it
so you brought the axe yeah yeah I just
came from practice sweet miss those days
oh you were in a van could have been but
in high school it's really all about my
magic so oh my God I just I I want to
rip
your I got glor I got glor he writes
some great
songs play something bro well I guess so
if you want me to could all use a nice
tune right now this is uh actually a
song I wrote for Haley it's called in
the Moonlight love Lely title tillan
thanks the stars are fall from
the and you're the
reason
why place cuz baby baby I just want to
do you do you do you want to do me I do
me underneath the Moonlight the
Moonlight baby
baby maybe I will steal you I seal you
just so I can feel you I feel you maybe
that would heal you I heal you on the
[Music]
inside she's so not going not a chance
on hell they don't see mind moon is
shining on your
face and it finally feels is founded
Place baby baby I just W to do you do
you baby you could do me do me and I
will do you do you maybe it would heal
you heal you from the
inside from the inside from the
inside from the
inside never good at harmonizing that
was good Luke come on we're
late there's a first inside out and
backwards at least isn't zipped into
his there it is he's got this almost
scientific mind with the thirst for
knowledge he's like this little Einstein
some people ask why Luke asks why
not I ask why a
lot do you think I really loved home
pickle making yeah cuz you did for a
week until we became the weird guys who
gave everybody pickles oh thank you
Marvin for inviting us into your lovely
home here would you care for a sack of
pickles look I wouldn't worry they're
good kids It's just tough when one kid's
a little different yes
yes you heard how she said that right
jce she thought Luke was the weird one
Luke her kid gets his head stuck in the
furniture and money is the different one
I will tell you what's weird our son is
not weird what's weird is that her kid
wears after shave dresses like a count I
just hate it when my two girls aren't
getting
along how exactly is she your
girl hey for you it's nice to see you
Gloria two times today okay Phil she
means we've seen them two times today
from the beginning I feel like Manny and
I are not welcome in this family that is
so crazy no it's not so crazy it's how I
feel what
he said you were a cold Digger okay I
think we can move on who said I was a
cold digger that's what my mom told me
what's a cold Digger sweetheart you
heard it wrong it's cold Digger so if I
was in one of your bars
and rightous brothers are on you know
would you uh I don't would check me out
from the minute we get up at 7:00 till
we drop them off at school it is go go
go I get up at
6 I get up at 5 seriously I get up at
six that's you I I thought we had a
raccoon well we got your Poncho here I
thought you said it made me look like my
neckel wearing a dress that was a joke
oh good it's still in the pocket what do
you got there buddy my panh flute I'm
going to play some Colombian folk music
for my new classmates huh
great I've never been more proud of you
I'm sure your friends are going to love
it break the flute what the poncho by
itself is fine the Poncho plus the flute
plus the stupid dance my son will die a
virgin that's
right hey sport can I take a look at
that
whistle oh jeez look at that and now you
stepped on it what oh darn well what's
wrong with me I'm breaking the window
emergency assistance this is help we we
lost our baby in the car and people are
judging us I swear to God I'm going to
break it do not break the window you get
glass on her sir please tell your wife
to relax everything is going to be okay
that's a man really don't worry Lily
Lily daddy's coming for you sir we just
sent the signal the door should be
unlocked now check the door check the
door check the door it's not unlocked
oh okay that is amazing I don't believe
it Daddy wins do you believe in miracles
USA us ow no oh
Jesus Oh wait what was that was that a
person Dad I'm good honey you I'm good
okay Woo you're getting better
sweetheart he
[Music]
heyyyyy