[Applause]
GTH paltro you ugly ass big bird looking
shut the
up unpopular opinion Lena Dunham's boobs
are dog
noses does Gerard Butler have a massive
student loan or something is that why he
does all these films I don't have a
student I just do all these films Ty
Bell looks like John Ham if John Ham was
a crack
addict how old is Bob newart now
about
120 I feel like britne Spears is
stalking me on the radio quit forcing
your suckage on me you
tired Gina Davis is a real man's
man
Chloe morrettes or whatever her stupid
name is looks like
my seriously she is not decent looking
whatsoever you must have a really
bleached off CHR
PR I hate that Scandal cast Scott Foley
he is TV poison for one thing and he's a
creep with Raper
face what Raper Raper face
Michael chicklas looks like a
scrotum Ted dancon sucks donkey balls
he's right guys John Stamos has a gross
belly
button I
[Music]
[Applause]
don't he's right I hope you all have a
great weekend except you Lisa cudro you
if an alien landed here and demanded a
famous person to eat I drive straight to
Adam Sandler's house with a net
[Applause]
now Nick offerman's hands seem crazy
small compared to his
head David Blaine looks like his voice
is putting his face to
sleep had a good chuckle over that one
I'm coming after you TX Grizz