When your legs don't work like they used
to
before and I can't sweep you off of your
[Music]
feet. Will your mouth still remember the
taste of my love?
Will your eyes still smile from your
cheeks? Darling, I will be loving
you till we're
[Music]
70. And baby,
my heart could still pull us hard at
[Music]
23. And I'm thinking about how people
fall in love in
mysterious
ways. Maybe just the touch of a
hand. Well, me I fall in love with you
every single
day. And I just want to tell you I
am. So honey,
now take me into your loving
arms. Kiss me under the light of a
thousand
stars. Place your head on my beating
heart. I'm thinking out loud. Maybe we
found love right where we
are. When my hair's all but gone and my
memory
fades and the crowds don't remember my
name. When my hands don't play the
strings the same
way. I know you will still love me the
same. Cuz honey, your soul could never
grow. Oh, it's ever
green. And baby,
your smiles forever in my mind and
memory.
I'm thinking about how people fall in
love in
mysterious
ways. And maybe it's all part of a
plan. Well, I'll just keep on making the
same
mistakes, hoping that you'll
understand. But baby, now
[Music]
Take me into your loving
arms. Kiss me under the light of a
thousand
stars. Place your head on my beating
heart. I'm thinking out loud. Maybe we
found love right where we are.
[Music]
La.
So baby
now take me into your loving
arms. Kiss me under the light of a
thousand stars. Oh darling, place your
head on my be
heart. I'm thinking out loud, but maybe
we found love right where we are. Or
maybe we found love right where we
are. And we found love right where we
are.