-And I'm very, very excited
that you're here tonight.
-I'm excited to be here, man.
You know, Jimmy,
first and foremost, dude,
I'm too pumped up.
You know I've been telling
everybody about this,
but there's one person --
there's one person
I forgot to tell.
Do you mind if I -- if I make
a FaceTime real quick?
Just real quick, I promise.
-You're gonna FaceTime somebody?
-Yeah, I just forgot
to tell one person.
-Who you gonna FaceTime?
-Oh, you know,
just a close friend of mine.
Somebody I'm very close to.
You may know him --
Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson.
[ Cheering ]
-I'ma FaceTime him.
-I know him.
We love Dwayne Johnson.
-Listen, he's not gonna be able
to believe that I'm here.
Watch this. Watch.
He's gonna be so pumped up
that I'm here tonight, man.
Wait -- Wait until he picks up.
I know he's gonna be pumped up
about it.
Hold on. Wait a second.
Hold on. One second.
Let me thank you --
Let me just try him.
-Maybe he's driving or
something.
-No, he's not driving.
He's got a chauffeur.
That guy's -- He's got a lot
of people to drive for him.
He's just --
He probably didn't see it.
Give him 2 minutes,
he'll pick up.
Watch, he's gonna pick up.
Wait a second, I'm gonna try him
again, watch this.
Watch this.
He's gonna --
He's gonna go crazy, watch this.
As soon as he picks up -- like 2
seconds -- he's gonna go --
He's gonna go crazy.
The fact that I'm here...
-We can edit.
-That you're here.
-We can edit all this out.
-No, you don't have to --
-You don't have to edit it out.
Just give me a second.
That's crazy.
That's honestly crazy, 'cause
normally he picks up...
-I have his number.
-...in like 2 seconds. What?
-You know Dwayne like that?
You got his nu--
-Yeah, I can --
-Well, he's not gonna pick up.
He's busy.
You can try, but I doubt that he
picks up the phone.
He would've picked up for me.
I'll text him. I'ma text him --
-Hey!
[ Cheering ]
-[ Laughing ]
Hey, buddy!
-Hey!
Dwayne! What's up?
What's up, pal?
-What's going on, Jimmy?
How you doing, brother?
-Everything's great, man.
I just, uh...
Yeah, I just -- I just figured
I'd --
I'm doing the show.
I just figured I'd FaceTime you,
see what you're doing.
Are you busy.
-Aww...
-Are you busy?
-Well, I'm just getting ready to
head to work.
I'm going to shoot the
"Titan Games", which you know.
-Oh, that's right, "Titan Games"
on NBC.
That's great.
-Yeah, on NBC. It's cool.
I wanted to make something that
was big and fun.
By the way, like our nickname,
'cause we're best friends.
Big and Fun, you know what I
mean?
-Absolutely.
-[ Chuckles ]
-That's right.
-Man, but hey, it's crazy --
It's crazy you were just
FaceTiming me.
Kevin Hart was FaceTiming me.
Just -- He continues to text.
He just FaceTimed me like two
times.
I'm like, "Dude, end. End it."
[ Laughter ]
You know what's crazy?
-Yeah?
-Look -- about Kevin -- and I
know you shooting the show
and the audience will love, too,
'cause they probably feel the
same way.
Kevin, to me, is like a little
gremlin that...
[ Laughter, applause ]
...I just want to take him and
throw him into oncoming traffic.
-[ Stammering ] Oh, yeah,
Dwayne, it's good
to talk to you, buddy, and we
love you.
-Aww, I love you back.
-I was just checking in on you.
Just wanted to make sure
everything's cool, man.
-Oh, hey, one more thing, dude.
Of course, the most important
thing.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Ah!
♪♪
-The best!
You're the best, buddy!
Thank you so much.
-Yeah!
-I'll talk to you later!
-Alright, man! Love you, man!
-Bye, buddy. Bye-bye.
[ Whoo's ]
Uh...
[ Laughter ]
He wasn't there.
It went straight to voicemail.
[ Laughs ] It wasn't --
-I heard the whole conversation!
-Oh, yeah, give it up for
Dwayne Johnson, everybody!
We'll be right back with more
of "The Tonight Show"
with me and Kevin Hart!
[ Cheering ]