do you ever give a perm to someone and
ever regret it uh an has told me
repeatedly not to get a perm but Ann's
not here so when the Ann's away the mice
get
perms the vote is in an hour okay we
need to have an emergency strategy
session now what about the perm the perm
must wait Autumn the perm must wait yeah
love the
hair do you hear that galloping M what
oh my look at that Joe Biden on a horse
shirtless that's
amazing hello Orin thank you so much for
applying now leave hey give him a chance
what makes you qualified for animal
control I studied zoology in college and
I can control animals with my mind get
out I made you say
that I liked them you undercook fish
believe or not jail you overcook chicken
also jail undercook overcook you make an
appointment with a dentist and you don't
show up Believe It or Not jail right
away we have the best patience in the
world because of
jail D do I look like I drink water one
question hold on oh my
God sorry April is the best but she's 20
when April was born I was already in
third grade which means if we were
friends back then I'd have been hanging
out with a
baby I don't know anything about infant
care my God I could have killed her
Pan's police chief is retiring and I'm
trying to get his endorsement before he
goes I'm really nervous because I need
this for my campaign and Ben is really
nervous because he is afraid of cops I'm
not afraid of cops I have no reason to
be I never break any laws ever because
I'm deathly afraid of cops I bought this
mackerel this Supermarket I've been
standing in the water with the fish on
my hook for 30 minutes I saw it an
episode of I Love Lucy pathetic maybe
but feels pretty good to have a bunch of
little boys be super into me that came
out wrong imagine what Tom would have
said damn Jerry you jumped in a creek
for burrito what' you do for a clondike
bar kill your wife
NOA it's like whatever you want like $10
it don't matter well I reckon it's just
like Grammy Mera told me and my cousins
you can't eat the biscuits if you don't
pay for the
flow and my husband Ben is a progressive
champion of women's rights babe the
oven's ready Chop Chop time to get bacon
daddy want
pie hi Ben
Wyatt thank you all for being here let's
get started wow great attitude
Ron sorry I was talking to these ribs
okay so the Valentine's Day dance is
planned prepped and under budget this is
my friend Madison she's amazing and she
drove me here
okay this ain't going to
work okay you did not just swivel away
while I was talking to you this
spaceship keyboard is driving me crazy
I'm down to one word a minute and the
word is perlus club because I can't fly
spaceships there are three acceptable
haircuts ion tight crew cut buzz cut are
the scissors broken in your house son
like this what's this Tom um those are
of course Tomatoes or Soulja Boy TMS
whenever Leslie asked me for the Latin
names of any of our plants I just give
her the names of rappers and those over
there uh those are some diddies got some
uh Bone Thugs and harmoniums right here
growing beautifully those ludres are
coming in great hunting trip we're doing
a trail survey like you're literally
listening to turkey calls is this is
this not
rap you fallen into a classic trap
Christopher trying to fix a woman's
problems instead of just listening to
what they are why are you yelling Tom
put all my records into this
rectangle the songs just play one right
after the other this is an excellent
rectangle then there is a horrifying 512
o version that they call child size how
is this a child size soda well it's
roughly the size of a 2-year-old child
if the child were liquefied it's a real
bargain at
159 oh yeah give me your booze I am
nourished by your hatred take out your
guide book oh I didn't bring a guide
book oh I brought you one you did yeah
thank you now throw it away does Leslie
nope is your guide book I
didn't I mean literally some notes in it
okay grab the book and let's hit the
National Mall there's the mall that's
awesome I need to get some flip-flops so
you've had soy milk and almond milk now
try the hottest new
craze beef milk it's like almond milk
that's been squeezed through tiny holes
in living
cows
milk no no okay Ben Wyatt hello uh hi
lesie good to see you too wow you're
really burning up can I get some money
for the cab that I took over here please
sure how much I'm not sure I looked at
the meter and it had Egyptian
hieroglyphics on it wow do you know the
exchange rate now is this part going to
have a playground or you know maybe a
pool for the kids oh uh how old are your
kids no kids uh-oh I'm going to put him
down as a yes don't do that also is the
park going to be at least 1,000 ft from
my house because you I really can't move
again April please stand behind me
that's it that's all that's all we got
no flyer nope
we live together and work together and
we are so in in syn that we finish each
other's
sentences we rehears that at home naked
in
bed we've been on a couple of dates I
really like them the problem is he's
like a perfect human man I can't find
one
flaw there was one time I thought he
farted but it was
me I have a press conference about the
pony comments in 2 hours so I need go
through every email that I've ever sent
ever I need to know what they might use
against me you can't hack into a
typewriter that's all I have to say can
it uni bomber this is an
[Music]
emergency is that what happened per none
of that happened that is exactly what
happened oh boy here it
comes 911 and we're walking okay I
brought some burgers and
fries eat up the protein soaks up the
sugar first you take the cow to The
Killing Floor you know in Russia they
could pretend that pit was a park bring
their kids down there hey Vlad uh look
at these rocks let's pretend they're
potatoes Nicholai
do you want to swim in the
dirt she did make a stop by the Sho
shine stand before we left because she
wanted to drop something off for Andy
she had a real bad crush on him oh babe
you had a crush on me that's
embarrassing we're married still I've
never taken the high road but I tell
other people to cuz then there's more
room for me on the low
road yeah well the flange was a little
warped so I just goose it with the
triple 3 bolts Mac that was nonsense I
know but it's so fun to talk like that
luxury dog
park do you want to tell us anymore
poodles only no
pooping these waffles make great dog
laxitives don't you dare feed that
waffle to that dog to get it to
poop SIM can need to make there you go
Leslie how dare you get her Leslie
[Applause]
this place is
outstanding great call Lesly no look
even Ben's dancing I had to pull a lot
of strings to get this meeting so please
no one embarrassed me Ben put on
something decent like a tux Andy You're
hopeless just take a shower I already
took what I call a dwire shower I rub my
armpits with air
fresheners new car
I have enjoyed parts of our time
together oh God
Ron that was really
something this is a map of all the
atrocities the pon settlers inflicted
upon the wamapoke
Indians the atrocities are in blue Dr
Sabin your son is my best friend he's
like a brother to me but he's a disaster
and your daughter seriously needs to be
locked up in some sort of insane asylum
on an island oh in
space is this everybody an took a cab
Tom's in the trunk Jerry's on the roof
all right we two first your mother's
butt I'm so alone if even one of you
thinks about dry hav in my car you're
all walking home
[Music]
yeah she died like 20 minutes after that
oh come on Ron I'm just a little puppy I
ain't done nothing wrong I'm just a
puppy I like your mustache I wish I
could have one but I can't cuz I'm just
a little
puppy I mean I'd do anything for Ron
even spend a whole night fighting his
crazy
ex-wife but I think I'm safe she's got
to be tired by now
hi I was getting kind of sick of
listening to Tom and an talk about the
relationship but then I remembered that
alcohol existed
thank you
alcohol it's going well so far but it's
too early to
tell he was pretty far
gone oh
no oh no I have to move
right yeah I'm going to leave the
country bye everybody bye Chris and Tom
offered to help me train to become a
police officer the physical exam is
about 3 months away and I am in terrible
shape but I can already do
this
so getting there there are two things I
know about white people they love
Matchbox 20 and they are terrified of
curses personalized leopard printed robe
pink feather cuffs and on the back in
rhinestones you can get it you know why
tonight's fun cuz everyone's so gay and
they know how to have fun and the
dancing just it's everyone is just who
they are and who they are is just Stone
Cold gay I will also take the sexy black
one I am not surprised at all I've been
to South America I did very well there I
passed up a gay Halloween party to be
here do you know how much fun gay
Halloween parties are last year I saw
three Jonas Brothers make out with three
Robert Patterson
was
amazing I have tried to achieve external
goals run a 4minute mile climb Mount
Everest but before I can do that I need
to climb the Mount
Everest of my
mind I loved Andy loved him loved Andy
he was a totally helpless baby when we
met I dated him for 3 years now he's an
adult the
job and some other girl is going to reap
the rewards of my hard
work that's
bullsh Joan has always been kind of a
train wreck but the last 3 years she's
gone off the deep end she did a string
of shows from rehab Victoria Herzog you
were a successful attorney from
Wilmington Delaware then you hit rock
bottom this is supposed to be anonymous
she once gave every member in her
audience a car one car that they all had
to fight for oh and last year she did a
show where she called all of her
ex-boyfriends while sitting on a washing
machine well Eric if you didn't give it
to me then who did I love her so much I
hope she's my real mom an was getting a
little chummy when people get too chummy
with me I like to call them by the wrong
name to let them know I don't really
care about them that's a genius move
thank you you're welcome
Lester who are Gregory and Winona I've
never heard of them before are they
better Winona rocks my world seriously
you need to get me in there like that's
a must must must she's the worst person
I've ever met I want to travel the world
with her 364 days a year they wake me
over the coals today I take those
burning coals I shove them back down
their throats and I watch their melting
flesh drip off their worthless faces I
enjoy government functions like I enjoy
getting kicked in the nuggets with a
steel toe boo but this hotel always
serves bacon wrapped shrimp that's my
number one favorite food wrapped around
my number three favorite food I'd go to
a banquet in honor those Somali pirates
if they serve bacon wrap shrimp excuse
me I ate a brownie once at a party in
college it was intense it's kind of
indescribable actually I
felt like I was
floating turns out there wasn't any pot
in the brownie it was just an insanely
good brownie so sister soul sister going
to get your phone sister Sweet Lady M
[Laughter]
[Music]