[Music]
well you only need the light when it's
burning low only miss the sun when it
starts to snow only know you love her
when you let her
go only know you've been high when you
feeling low only hate the road when
you're missing home only know you love
her when you let her
go and you let her go
[Music]
staring at the bottom of your class
hoping one day you'll make a dream last
but Dreams Come slow and they go so
[Music]
fast you see it when you close your eyes
maybe one day you'll understand why
Everything You Touch surely
[Music]
dies but you only need the light when
it's burning low only miss the sun when
it starts to snow only know you L when
you let it
go only know you've been high when you
feeling low only hate the road when you
missing home only know you love her when
you let her
go staring at the ceiling in the dark
same all empty feeling in your heart cuz
love comes slow and it goes so
fast we you see her when you fall asleep
but never to touch and never to keep CU
you L her too much and you dive too
[Applause]
deep where you only need the light WIS
burning low only miss the sun when it
starts to snow only know you love her
when you let her go
oh only know you've been high when you
feeling low only ha the road when you
missing home only know you love her when
you let her
[Music]
go and you let her go
oh and you let her go
[Music]
oh we let her
go cuz you only need the light when it's
burning low only miss the sun when it
starts to snow only know you love her
when you let her
go only know you've been high when you
feeling low only hey the RO when missing
home only know you love her when you let
her
go cuz you only need the light when it's
burning low only miss the sun when it
starts to snow only know you love her
when you let her
[Music]
go only know you've been high when you
feeling low only hate the road when
you're missing home
only know you love her when you let her
go and you let her go