[Music]
it's been a long
day without you my friend and I'll tell
you all about it when I see you again
we've come a long
way from where we began oh tell you all
about it when I see you again when I see
you
[Music]
again damn who knew all the planes we
flew good things we' been through that I
be standing right here talking to you
about another path I know we love to hit
the road and laugh but something told me
that it wouldn't last had to switch up
look at things different see the bigger
picture those were the days hard work
forever PID
now I see you in a better place see you
a
place how can we not talk about that we
got everything I would do you was
standing there by my side and now you
going to be with me for the last ride
it's been a long
day without you my friend and I'll tell
you all about it when I see you again I
see you again we've come a long way yeah
we came a long way from where we began
know we started I'll tell you all about
it when I see you again tell you when I
see you
[Music]
again
yeah first you both go out your way in
the vibe is feeling stronger with small
turn to a friendship a friendship turned
to a bond and that Bond will never be
broken the love will never get
lost and when Brotherhood come first and
the line will never be crossed
established it on our own when that line
had to be drawn and that line is what we
reach so remember me when I'm gone
I'm how can we not talk about faing with
fings all that we got everything I would
through you was standing there by my
side and now you going to be with me for
the last r light guide your
way yeah hold every M as you
go and every road you
take
over s you
home oh
W it's been a long
day without you my friend and and I'll
tell you all about it when I see you
again we've come a long
way from where we
began oh I'll tell you all about it when
I see you again when I see you
again yeah
see you see
you uh-huh
[Music]