What I want...
What's most important to me
is that I have a guarantee.
No more attempts on my father's life.
What guarantees can I give you?
I'm the hunted onel
I missed my chance.
You think too much of me, kid.
I'm not that clever.
All I want is a truce.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Is it all right?
When you got to go, you got to go.
He's clean.
Don't take too long.
I've frisked a thousand punks.
This isn't like the army! You have to get
close and get their brains on your suit.
You're taking this very personal.
Tom, this is business
and he's taking it personal.
- Where does it say you can't kill a cop?
- Mikey...
I'm talking about a cop who's mixed up
in drugs, a dishonest cop.
A cop who got mixed up in the rackets
and got what was coming.
That's a terrific story. We have
newspaper people on the payroll, right?
- They might like a story like that.
- They might.
It's not personal, Sonny.
It's strictly business.
It's as cold as they come.
Impossible to trace,
SO you don't worry about prints.
I put a special tape on the trigger
and the butt. Try it.
Is the trigger too tight?
My ears!
I left it noisy, so it scares away any
pain-in-the-ass innocent bystanders.
You've shot them both.
Now what do you do?
- Sit down, finish my dinner.
- Don't fool around.
Let your hand drop to your side
and let the gun slip out.
Everybody will still think you've got it.
They'll stare at your face,
so walk out fast, but don't run.
Don't look anybody in the eye,
but don't look away either.
They'll be scared stiff,
so don't worry about nothing.
You'll be all right. You'll take
a vacation, nobody knows where,
and we'll catch the hell.
- How bad do you think it will be?
- Pretty goddamn bad.
All the other families will probably
line up against us.
These things have to happen every five,
10 years. Gets rid of the bad blood.
Been 10 years since the last one.
You have to stop them at the beginning.
Like they should have stopped Hitler in
Munich, not letting him get away with it.
You know, Mike, we were all proud
of you. Being a hero and all.
Your father too.
Michael, you lousy bastard!
You killed my husband.
You waited until Papa died,
SO nobody could stop you.
You blamed him for Sonny.
Everybody did.
But you never thought about mel
Now what are we going to do?
Connie.
Why do you think
he kept Carlo at the Mall?
He knew he was going to kill him.
And you stood godfather to our baby.
You lousy cold-hearted bastard!
Want to know how many men he had
Killed with Carlo? Read the papers!
That's your husband,
that's your husband!
No! No, no...
Take her upstairs. Get her a doctor.
She's hysterical.
Hysterical.
Michael, is it true?
- Don't ask me about my business, Kay.
- Is it true?
Don't ask me about my business.
Enough!
All right.
This one time.
This one time
I'll let you ask me about my affairs.
Is it true?
Is it?
No.
I guess we both need a drink. Come on.
Don Corleone.