shab sholl my name is Kevin that is my
name they call me Kevin yeah cuz that's
my
name this
Plantation we're running low on on green
backs and we're having problems uh
paying the people who give us the
sads KN who's there KGB KGB we asked the
question what the hell was that what are
you doing what are youing hey hey you
stop
it not everyone jumped okay everybody
jump in the air this time please here we
go one two
three still some people not jumping you
got to be kidding me who isn't jumping
yes but don't expect any
cookie but what if I'm
hungry no
cookie do you wear boxers briefs or
pantaloons oh well you're very saucy
yeah call my baby sister an assho and
told her to eat dog food we thought that
she was you why would you think a lady
is
me are you are you serious good
afternoon Iris it's a pleasure I'll get
straight to the point is your paper
toxic no the paper is not toxic thank
you Sandra unless it's exposed to oxygen
then it becomes extremely toxic
wow that Carol is one smart cookie come
on my goodbye goodbye my
friend cannot believe a pipe burst and
left that there there's no burst pipe
how do you know that what is it then hey
guys somebody making
soup
[Laughter]
gentle
will not believe I was so nervous but
now now I have a boyfriend all
right I hooked up with her on February
13th um
blue
yellow red how about green I think green
is kind of horish right well it's really
nice to meet you Brian uh it's actually
Ryan oh Ryan yeah
could you scoot over you're on my
dress I thought you're not supposed to
wear white to a wedding I know but there
was an
emergency I look really good in white
Andy and Dwight are rocking the sales
team I feel very
[Music]
blessed at first I drove myself crazy
thinking about the things I should have
done differently I never should have
played that joke on Aaron never should
have hollowed out this damn pumpkin in
the first place but my huge whopping
penis is right here and I'm not afraid
to use it so stop looking at my breasts
and start looking at my
penis what Andy Andy what should I tell
them don't tell them I'm floating away
obviously I don't understand what you
want from me and you were directly under
her the entire time that's what she said
excuse me that's what she said Miss
levenson told you that she was your
direct
Superior what okay well that still
leaves a 30% chance that I'll Attack you
from the front uh yeah but it'll be
easier to stop I can always block the
blow or I can counter it with
it that is Northern Lights cannabis
Indigo
no it's
marijuana
okay you can expect these kind of
repercussions as long as you keep trying
to poach our people I'm taking Stanley
then we will burn udica to the
ground oh my God what's happening and's
running over Dwight with his car
whoa hey hey hey oh what are you guys
doing this girl was really rude to me at
the mall so I created a fake IM account
from a hot guy at her High School and
now I'm trying to make her anorexic tell
her everyone in Home Room thinks she's
fat oh my God what wrong baby what wrong
baby this is not our baby this is
estabon another cleaning man he doesn't
speak English either estaban El
floro this is no get
together there's a
[Music]
[Applause]
party
through beep beep no ow I didn't see you
you should have yelled Crossing I'm
sorry it's whom when it's the object of
the sentence and who when is the subject
that sounds right well it sounds right
but is it how did Ryan use it as an
object as an object Ryan use me as an
object this is your big sister Kelly did
you color this pretty picture no so then
this means nothing to
you you are never going to find them I'm
going to enjoy this give me the lead
where the lead give me the lead I'm
still enjoying it we I want to thank
God because God gave me this
dundy and I feel God in this chilies
tonight do you hear me Mr Ash you look
at
[Music]
me this is getting weird do you
understand boy have you lost your mind
cuz I'll help you find it what you
looking for ain't nobody going to help
you out there Jesus can come through
that door and he's not going to help you
if you don't stop sniffing after my
child okay attach Scranton business park
there will be complimentary pretzels
available in the lobby from now until
4:00 as a thank you to our
loyal so you worked at your last job for
15 years as assistant to the regional
manager assistant regional manager
assistant to the regional manager
regional manager what is it assistant
regional manager oh that's my mistake
sorry about that pregnant Pam and I we
get hungry at the same times so we've
been eating together a lot second
breakfast lunch second lunch and first
dinner so I am
utterly and completely
alone Angela you still have your son I
guess mat what are you doing hey I have
a question who do you think is really
the best salesman in this office stupid
question obviously Mr James Albert
corporate need you to find the
differences between this picture and
this
picture okay I already see one give him
okay they're the same
[Music]
[Applause]
picture get what Ral fting
Michigan the president of the United
States is POTUS this bartender in
Stanford who uh you know what you just
have to be there wish I was I love
inside jokes love to be a part of one
someday Jim Halpert said there was an
abandoned infant in the woman's room
when I went to save the child I saw
Meredith on the
can wow look at you you are uh you're
like the new and improved pam pam 6.0 oh
oh look oh
hey I
declare
[Music]
bankruptcy by any chance did you see
Battle Star Galactica last night no I
did not is that any good actually not it
is really so so
okay what do thinking about that story
where you R into the girl used to
babysit I don't know what I'm going to
do please call me back please I'm not
going to be okay will what's a seven
letter word for
purse hatel no starts with an H
handbag thank
you no no no no no no oh my God oh my
God no
no they love a good crotch yeah they
sure do you should take that as a
compliment oh I
do we have a day honoring Martin Luther
King but he didn't even work here I
understand how you feel Michael I really
do Karen filipelli sent me an email
asked me out I said no because I was
committed to our relationship well I
hope you're still committed because I'm
pregnant
ball's in face it's not a race
qu I came up with a new thing this
summer I act like I'm telling someone
how to do something I go on with a long
description and then I say and shove it
up your
butt they call me prison Mike do you
really expect us to believe you're
somebody else do you really expect me to
not push you up against the wall
Bach all right Ryan started the fire it
was always burning since the world
returning ran started the fire it was
always burning the Gaba gou I I don't
really know what that is you know Gaba I
don't I don't I don't have to have that
what he's trying to say is g g guys
everyone everyone can I just have your
attention has anyone seen a small stop
that tiny blond woman she stole my
baby what are you doing we can go to
lunch pick up Babes smile if you love
men's
prostates what are you doing what those
are my keys good luck Jim damn it no Jim
let me out Jim
let wait like something that you have to
look
for sort of a where's Waldo
[Music]
oh a 15minute round of applause I like
it followed by a 15 minute moment of
silence I don't
know is it classy enough has it really
been 10 years local businessman pledges
College tuition to third
graders really looking forward to
sitting down with you and finding out
more about what you do here anytime yeah
what do you do
here excuse me
me
beautiful he is
beautiful this big fat pig is
[Music]
beautiful
yes Jan
we need to
talk Ryan just out of curiosity how much
you get paid here $60,000 a year you get
paid by the year at the bowling alley
what do you make secretary back to work
shoe
[Music]
yeah is a part of sa is a part of
sa there's a lake there knows where it
is going the machine know stop yelling
at me it's there's no Road
here I want my baby back baby back baby
back I want my baby back baby back baby
back I want my baby
back come on who's that
girl who's that
girl it's
Andy
bears eat beats oh Bears beats
Battlestar Galactica bears do not what
is going on what are you doing I love
meat what's your blood type oh negative
universal donor universal
donor hey are you okay I'm fine I'm
totally
yes Twi Jim sorry oh crap I'm just
twight do you know her last name yet
Toby I'm going to tell you her last name
tomorrow because she's going to be
screaming at tonight she's going to be
screaming her own last name hey
and come on did that did that just
happen we should write a movie or
something I'm
serious
blood alone moves the wheels of
History
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
for