oh hey Captain did you get my report on
the Finley murder uh yeah I looked it
over nice work good thanks Dad
why is everyone staring at me
[Applause]
[Music]
Amy fun thing about working cases you
meet people from all over the world okay
basal body temperature is optimal let's
do this quickly oh Amy I'm not some
faucet you can just turn on and off you
got a romance me Foster Tom Let's uh I'm
gonna call halt you want to come yeah
too bad you're not invited I'm in charge
bye
I've been chasing this guy for three
months I've got him dead to rights
fingerprints Witnesses it's in the bag
so I'm just gonna grab a healthy
breakfast are those gummy bears wrapped
in a fruit roll-up
breakfast burrito but yeah I pity your
dentist ah joke's on you I don't have a
dentist then we figured out how to be
good parents TV and cake
where are my parents
come with me hey me to the dumpster me
and Amy go and dive in in the dumpster
no not some point maker shot taker
making girls hot like oats the Quaker
hey man you're wrapping yeah I had to
see where it was going where's the good
Drive-In in a car destination drug
dealers bar pass the mic right over to
Charles we forgot Charles
but we can't turn back cause we've gone
too far we have to turn back though we
can't leave them it was a good rhyme
though Die Hard is the best cop movie of
all time One Cop heroically saving the
day while everyone else stands around
and watches it's the story of my life so
Kevin I hear you're a professor at
Columbia that's right yes I had the
classics Department ah interesting
Classics Zeppelin Hendrix die hard total
Classics head over here
I'm joking obviously I know what the
classics are the Odyssey and the one you
said when we got here the wolf one
Globes are for a 25 year old Port seems
appropriate I would have gone 10. I
don't know what poor it is destined
it's been a while mind if I asked you a
few questions well well well
if it isn't joke Peralta
so you're under arrest
removable
[Music]
police tactic Sarge cover every exit it
was a sealed window on the fifth floor
you could have just gone in the door
with Charles yeah but then what would my
catchphrase have been knock knock who's
there Justice ooh that's actually
amazing Charles write that down already
did Sam straight up depressed Amy's been
doing her best to cheer me up she gave
me the sticker this morning just for
waking up yeah it's like you're dating
your teacher I know it's so hot
meanwhile Holt won't even talk to me how
is he by the way honestly terrible I've
only heard from him once this week and
that was to tell me he'd finally come up
with a new non-threatening term for task
forces y'all ready for this do groups
wow that sucks tremendously
can I have another Port you're still
drinking that stuff yeah Hulk got me
hooked on it I even got a bottle for my
house it's really classing up the booze
and take out menu's Shelf
wait a minute
I think I just figured something out I
gotta go aren't you forgetting something
uh
no pay your bill
damn who raised you you just called
Captain hold dad he said thanks Dad what
no I didn't I said thanks man do you see
me as a father figure Peralta no if
anything I see you is a bother figure
because you're always bothering me hey
show your father some respect well when
you finally change lanes an hour from
now you should go talk to Jake super see
if there was a power outage what
oh why would you do that I just broke
into your car and then popped up without
warning not cool two three four
[Applause]
wait have you never been to therapy no
don't need it not even after the time
your wife shot you nope what about when
you were held at gunpoint and had to
write your own suicide note that was
crazy I forgot about that or when you
were falsely accused of bank robbery and
went to prison was that a big deal you
joined a gang and tried math I didn't
want to be anyone's let's keep it
a scap cat boo but it happened Jazz
Jazzy jazz
jazz
[Music]
that's all you prepped yeah I just
searched my heart and then wrote down
how I was feeling I'm Gonna Eat You
Alive you dumb son of a cool and
then we'll have kids together yeah it's
gonna be great okay the topic today here
are two pictures
one is your locker the other is a
garbage dump in the Philippines can you
tell which is which
that one's the dump they're both your
locker I should have guessed that he's
good five years instead of 20. oh that's
tough but fair I can see why you have
such intense daddy stuff with him oh
yeah the guy without a daddy is the one
with daddy issues explain that logic hey
Sarge large and in charge like El
Debarge quick question
Mario is doing it with Theresa Teresa is
doing it with Paulie I knew that Paulie
is doing it with Lisa and Lisa's doing
it with Anthony I really like this song
did you come up with the melody I'm
pretty sure I did Freddy is cheating
with Bianca G but also with her younger
sister Valerie no thank you sir I'll
take it from here very poetic
if I might offer a counter Toast of
sorts captain dozerman and I we weren't
together for very long
in fact his co-workers our relationship
was only six days
but that's not nothing
it was long enough for me to know that
we had something special
and sure there may be obstacles him
having passed away for example
but I'm not giving up on us and I don't
care if I get demoted
I just
care about being with you
captain dozerman
an adult man
who's passed into the Netherworld number
one could you please sing the opening to
I Want It That Way really
okay
you are
My Fire
number two keep it going the one
desire number three believe when I say
number four I want it that away tell me
why ain't nothing but a heartache tell
me why ain't nothing but a mistake now
number five I never wanna hear you say
[Applause]
ah chills literal chills it was number
five number five killed my brother oh my
God I forgot about that party so how did
you two finally get together after all
these years oh uh you know I just been
crazy about her forever and then one day
I picked up my battered old guitar and I
sang her a song
how did it go oh you don't want to hear
it yes I do well I don't have my guitar
here sing the song Rosa Rosa Rosa Rosa
Rosa Rosa d s t s d s d s d s d s d s d
s Rosa Diaz Rosa Diaz Diaz Rosa Rosa
Diaz Diaz you are so cool sounds better
with a guitar what is that smell that is
the absence of urine you gotta leave
Brooklyn to get that no urine I could
get used to this oh yes and that's just
the beginning my friend just wait till
you're sitting Fireside sipping on a
premium Chinese scotch and smoking a
sweet Rwandan cigar okay okay I probably
could have done without the countries of
origin but that sounds great yeah what
else do you have planned ah so much I'm
talking fishing I'm talking poker I'm
talking frisbee boy what else am I
talking Wildflower picking so we can
make our own cologne nope I was talking
bonfires and s'mores but that's my fault
for throwing to you how much to take
this bad boy home actually that's one of
our more reasonable models yeah holy
Moses that is much too much money
well you spent twice that for Mr Met to
come to your birthday party yeah and it
was worth it Mr Met used my bathroom
number two that's a memory I will
cherish forever I left food everywhere
this drawer is completely full of
maggots now
want to get a drink no I think I'm just
gonna stay here and stare into the
maggot drawer
hey that's a good name for a death metal
song stare into the maggot draw
please don't call me there okay fine
I'll just call you the Mish no wait
Missy Elliot no wait Mitch's doubt fire
oh my God what what is it look atomi
Plaza
it's the most important monument in all
of America the building from Die Hard
can we go in can we pair our specs oh
our flight leaves in three and a half
hours and
but it's like what is time even hashtag
Legalize It can we go in sir fine just
make it quick yes pull it over there
Argyle before this is the name of the
driver in the movie we're going to Dr
Tommy Plaza there's gonna be role play
Amy Santiago
I want to change mattresses for you
that's the best thing I've ever heard
I'm sorry I didn't do it sooner I think
I was just
scared that you were gonna realize
you're way better than me like
your Orangina and I'm orange soda are
you kidding you're Orangina ugh don't
say that Jake Karen is a grown woman
with a pretty respectable credit score
I'm sure she knows what she's doing Amy
I know that you have a binder But You
Don't Know Her Like I Do she's too
trusting for her own good she's fallen
for more Nigerian scams than Scully
she's fallen for 20 Nigerian scams 20
that's insane no she's fallen for two
scully's fallen for 20s got bad guys
it's barley and James barley and jams
are on the case please hey everybody a
couple things about my management style
number one don't nobody ask me about
what's in my cut we ain't gonna have no
problems
uh two I believe in the power of
nicknames smile face senorita swag
and you my friend we will call Mr Fart
seems rather unprofessional he called
you Mr Fart Mr Fart thanks Kahuna guys
can I get real with you for one sec
I used to work for a real stickler
type of guy that just got off on telling
me what to do one time he invaded my
private space and stole my stuff why
would he do that perhaps he had a good
reason wrong Mr Fart he was a jerk and
he sucked but he was the one who
motivated me to get off my ass and get
this job so in a way we really have him
to thank for all this happening
give it up how great is this guy Greg
wait that's Greg the stoner yeah look at
him he's such a roster oh total roster
hey Bob sweet Bob Bob and the mob mob
bub
fine he's still on the case
and Jay got cops with the wise truck and
kept it all over the ride they'll have
the pictures wherever they go the
talking dog flies in outer space
hey everyone sorry I'm late so what's
this secret meeting all about you guys
know I'm not medically cleared for
another week it's not a secret meeting
Jake
it's an intervention the tips have to go
what why take we're worried about you
and you look very stupid come on guys I
think they're kind of cool retro no
they're terrible Amy come on you're
digging the tips right no I feel like
I'm kissing Vanilla Ice there was a time
you would have jumped at that chance you
have to go all right you guys got me I
did it as a joke I kept them ironically
pretty funny right I'm just gonna head
out
yeah
[Applause]
thank you okay okay wait wait wait okay
I'll admit it I went too deep down there
at one point I think I forgot where the
tip of me ended and the base of the tips
began before we just chop them off would
anybody like to say some final words no
that was one word that counts thank you
Rosa okay I'm ready
sorry I'm late everyone but trust me
it's worth it me and Jake are chip buds
what no
[Applause]
no you know what I do see it it's bad it
looks bad uh
I wish you were alive dog today
God will give you a high five
oh he gave himself a keychain
[Music]
look your dead friend in the eyes and
say his name Robert
okay maybe
say his full name Robert his middle
name's Henry Robert Henry Tupper his
wife called him Rob work that in robbed
up work it in the full name Robert Rob
Henry tough now say it with a frown on
your face Robert Rob Henry now try not
to Blink so tears come into your eyes
Robert Rob Henry tough man this guy is a
good murderer there's gonna be some way
to break him wait a minute
I just had an idea two three four
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I really gotta stop trying that it
never works he's gonna transfer out of
the Nine-Nine that's what this is all
about he's still trying to undermine the
man what no the opposite of anything I
want to see him succeed I'm trying to
over mine him oh you know I hate it when
you make up words Peralta are you still
mad at me for saying snack accident yes
very so you heroically fought off three
guys and that puts you in a bad mood if
I did that I would literally write a
song about myself it would be like Jake
the hero abs of steel
remember what you gonna do with all that
hunch all that hunch inside your brain
we're gonna solve this case solve this
case right in your face
should probably leave this prison you
see the food in prison was inedible all
I thought about day and night were the
things I wished I was eating and you Amy
I thought about you a lot sex with you
just us doing sex with foreplay great
safe babe thanks you're right
thanks Terry
oh my man what are you doing whatever it
takes to make Amy happy you told me to
do this now let's get these gift bags to
the menu
oh my God why did you do that because I
care oh it feels so good why'd you bring
a second window fool you know you're
really stepping on my moment here Terry
I love Amy
baby names
I like that I thought you would Doug and
Jake rolling down the street PB and J a
tasty little tree two cool dudes making
sandals for your feet what I was going
for the rhyme but now I kind of feel
like it's a good idea love it making
sandals that last is our ideology Made
Real by our patented strapless
technology it's magnets oh okay yo you
can wear him on the beach wear them on a
hike wear them on a Peloton exercise
bike Doug and Jake
all right
that was crazy he never even rehearsed
it just did it perfectly all right so
I was unable to get the CDs however I
can sing you a very soothing tune
something like going to get that feeling
I need Sexual Healing oh boy
[Music]
no applause wow okay so we are way
behind picking out napkins took up a
shockingly large part of the day which
is funny because of my regular life I
don't use napkins ever that's gross but
the good news is your groom gut is all
fired up she sure is and she's hungry
for tasks your groom gut is a woman yeah
why I think it's really cool oh thanks
all right let's crush this list calla
lilies do you think I'm planning a
funeral I want dahlias
oh no no Brown sprinkles at the ice
cream bar do you think I'm planning a
funeral give me rainbow mini lamb shanks
do you think I'm planning a funeral swap
them out for some tiny tuna tacos
understand a few funeral thing because
my groom gut has a catchphrase
look at this I cleared all my alarms
we're amazing should we start a business
where we just become professional
choosers we could call it pro-choice
industry you're right that name is
needlessly political but the business
idea is solid no I'm not talking about
that all those decisions you made you
are way over budget oh no
break my heart
say you love me again
you know what I like this song
wait shut up shut up the nerve
unbelievable
[Music]
do you think he killed her and dumped
her body in the park sounds like couples
counseling is going really great for
them sorry my partner doesn't believe in
therapy oh that's fine it's hard for
some people that title you're sex tape
are you normally so Cavalier around
murder investigations yes we see a lot
of darkness in our line of work and
humor is one of our coping mechanisms
it's self-preservation through
disassociation
and another thing you should appreciate
Amy Moore because she's amazing and
another thing when you come to visit us
you don't have to bring your own coffee
our coffee is fine and another thing I
know enough Spanish to understand what
idiot what that means and another thing
when you say I have an interesting nose
I know you mean big I got lost in it
Methodist hospital called this morning
apparently a 38 year old investment
banker was admitted last night with a
broken penis it looks like whoa whoa
there's a finance guy with a broken dog
uh me think some Wolf of Wall Street
style shenanigougals have taken place
this day anyone care wager guesses to
how this happened yeah I bet he dipped
it in a pile of cocaine got a real numb
and then hit a croquet ball with it
totally possible he probably sat on it
got under his butt happens all the time
sure do you guys are horrible and you're
wrong because he was clearly driving his
Bentley naked tried to pee out the
window and was then struck by a goose on
the Wang is that what happened sir was
he struck by a goose he was actually
struck by a female co-worker who claims
he attempted to sexually assault her
I remember saying it can't be Henderson
remember we made up that little song
Can't Be Henderson Anderson's not the
one back to the drawing board
Henderson's on the Move Santiago is
running perimeter control Peralta you're
in charge of the man hunt for the
shooter oh my God it's a man
boy
I'm gonna look strange into the camera
and say if the shooter is watching I
hope you like living between Saint
Charles Place and Connecticut Avenue
I don't get it it's for Monopoly that's
where jail is whatever it was a good
line keep briefing every Hotel safe has
an override code in case guests leave
them locked that code is kept on the
concierge's computer do you know who
this is this is Matt Daniel the most
popular male ASMR performer on Twitch
ASMR performer someone who speaks real
soft
we're trying to stream and the noise on
the eighth floor is unacceptable
I'm so sorry I can't hear you
he says that's the point Georgina this
is taking too long make a video tell
your 25 million subscribers to never
stay at this crap Hotel no no I'll take
care of it let me talk to my general
manager
restrain your beautiful voice number
eight number eight way to stay alive
number eight still live number eight
still alive moment of silence for the
first seven though
will you join me in Terry's office
private Rendezvous it's still trying to
make a baby thing it's got you super
freaky Terry what's up dude what did you
think was happening he clearly thought
you were gonna have secret sex in here
what what inappropes much I did not
think that Amy did she texted me about
it see proof anyway
what do we have here it appears a crime
has been committed and no one will
confess doing a German accent I was
going for Belgium if I can murder on the
Orient Express you sound like a Nazi
okay not a great note to hear I'll just
use my normal voice
oh we gotta put that behind us because
my friend Charles the horse was a great
idea but we don't have time for you to
have a heart to heart with us just a
very emotional Jake take care of my
friend four-legged bastard
you know now that I'm up here I realize
I don't know how to ride a horse it's
probably pretty self-explanatory right
[Music]
and so on to the briefcase goes the
crown didn't sing it with me beefer's
birthday start and then a bunch of Mets
are here present day or 86. both I'm
gonna escort him back well they stole
their own books it's plain to see but
who's on the case The Adams Family
Terry is Gomez I'm cousin it you are
Wednesday let's do this okay we should
go you guys probably don't know this but
my parents got divorced when I was a kid
and it really messed me up yeah why do I
talk about it a lot it doesn't matter
the point is we can't let that happen to
Daddy Holt and daddy Kevin so we're just
dispensing with subtext now yes this
workplace is my family was that not
clear Holt is my dad you remind me an
older sister Amy's my mom what what
Franzia disappears into these crazy
underground tunnels should we have to
switch over to night vision and Charles
it's all so awesome but I actually have
to stop you because I gotta go I have to
feed this baby some mushed up avocado oh
my God what happened is Mac okay
let's pulled himself
so I wake in the morning
[Music]
thank you