ladies and gentlemen welcome to the most
anticipated event in this Precinct
history the auction
for the suitcase of mystery exactly
Jacob this puppy's been in the lost and
found since
1976 no one alive today knows its
contents I'm happy to say captain Holt
has finally given me permission to
auction it off I'll let you give me a
spray tan any shade you want Jake
willing to sacrifice his dignity who can
top it massage I'll give massage Charles
going in the wrong direction and getting
himself disqualified interesting
approach orange Jake going once going
twice I'll show you a picture of me in
high school there is side pony oh Rosa
coming in hot Rosa coming in hot I'll
also give you full control of my hair
and wro I'll go on a date with you sold
to Jake not to skoly that really freaked
me out and I just want this to end now
so there's this suitcase I don't care
yeah Squad Bullpen now is everything
okay sir no it is not I went to a
meeting and when I returned my pie was
gone which one of you took it calm down
there's no need to point fingers at us
it was clearly Hitchcock and Scully how
dare you you have no proof there's
crumbs all over your desks well these AR
pie crumbs bread cookie pizza sandwich
blint and one good oldfashioned potato
chip no pie here I just humiliated you
hey so you doing okay not really I
waited outside that restaurant for 2
hours and he never came out cantaloup
I'm good Amy all so good all so good I
spent the whole night riding my bike
just thinking and riding riding and
thinking also I drank some water from a
stream and what did you figure out I'm
going to dump his ass he should be here
any minute oh you're going to do it at
work that's great there you are babe
I've been looking for you all night you
didn't come home because I knew if I did
I would stab you in the face oh Terry we
have the thing in the other room phone
yeah meeting uh work PR lunch y so is
this a sexy stab in the face or an angry
stab in the face don't play dumb with me
I know about your mistress I know about
laaa I know about the FL bab wait oh
I've been waiting I waited all night to
do this we're done it's over what
no I don't have a mistress that woman's
name is Senora Rees she's my Spanish
teacher oh please no I'm serious the
only reason we were even at laala is I
can practice ordering in Spanish and by
the
way it
did oh my
God oh my God Adrien I'm so sorry you
must be so mad at me what of course I'm
not mad at you are you kidding jealousy
is like the hottest emotion let's do
this okay let's do it
you're not going to apologize Sergeant
no I was trying to lighten the mood the
squad's been stressed since these drills
started plus you ordered me to act like
a seven-year-old seven-year-olds like to
have fun that's true when I was seven I
used to sneak into my father's office to
see his collection of antique Globes sir
it's hard to motivate the squad when we
don't even know why we're doing these
drills this hasn't been announced yet
but there's going to be a new
commissioner of the nyp
we're all going to be under a microscope
and I want us to be prepared for
anything you should have just told us
that I was trying to Shield you do you
know how much stress I've been under
lately my husband says he hasn't seen me
smile in weeks how much did you smile
before that constantly I don't know
what's going on down at Police
Headquarters and no one will tell me
anything so you're saying that not
knowing what your bosses are up to is
driving you a little crazy you've used
my logic against me well played Timmy
well played thank you sir look at that
youve helped me find my
smile what are you looking all whistful
about just thinking about relationships
and love and how I'm way better at them
than I thought I'd be should I do a Ted
Talk on it doesn't seem any dumber than
all the other TED Talks I mean Amy was a
wreck and I fixed her the weird thing is
I love her so much I don't even feel
like bragging about it clearly you get
it all right two things one we're out of
chips how you skimped us and two Amy
left and asked me me to give you this
note what' she say did she go out to get
some more chips no the practice test
freaked her out she's not taking the
Sergeant's
exam damn it before we get into your
pitch what are you calling the product
the handless lighting system or hls
sounds like a genetic disorder how's
about shoulder Nova I love it amazing
it's perfect now let's talk presentation
what's your
opener hi I'm Amy Santiago and my
product will make a real difference it
is the shoulder Nova my only note is
make it 1,000% more captivating very
good note okay okay I got
it
ding oh hello I'm Amy
Santiago is that captivating enough
weirdly it might have been a scooch too
captivating here's what I'm thinking
okay and you can take a seat
okay until this moment there was only
Darkness but
now there
is
light I am Vanessa Santiago and I'm
about to blow your
minds you want me to change my name to
Vanessa desperately sir can I get $350
in petty cash I need to throw an ice
cream party for Terry with than I make
sure there are no hard feelings why she
gets it with a misunderstanding she's a
Terry and you're a Terrence who even
though he's not a child still goes by a
nickname ending in a why I mean don't
people call you Ray how dare you sir I
don't want any tension between the squad
and the uniformed officers I'm just
thinking about the precinct you're lying
you're upset because Terry with an eye
called you arrogant and you have a
pathological need to be liked what no I
don't I just happen to be a great person
who's naturally loved by all despite my
personal ambivalence well if that's true
then you won't mind walking across the
bullpen without saying hello to anybody
no problem no nods allowed what okay
it's going to be okay you're a busy
Sergeant they can't always expect you to
be
friendly time to go to Brown Town let's
do this Jeffs hey AR Bill what up
man you were right Terry loves to be
loved hey Monica
hey Doug who want a
KN Gina I know you like champagne with a
drop of pomegranate juice I like to say
it's Nature's classiest alcohol mixed
with its nartist fruit and foral I hope
this will do it's a can of orange soda
from when some other children visited
it's perfect thank you for inviting us
in yes I invited Gina in you were with
her okay look everyone's blaming me for
the captain's horrible mood because of a
small thing that happened Wednesday
morning when you flooded his office with
cider well the water actually flooded it
The Cider just caused it but I swear he
was already upset when he got to work he
was anger articulating coat coat jacket
coat is this a police precinct or a
Turkish
Bazaar yes I dread those annunciated
denunciations yeah I hate those dations
the vert but so my question is could
something have happened at home before
he left for work well I remember that
morning he left this house at 7:00 and
was in a great mood in fact he was still
chuckling about the previous nights
Charlie Rose fine so your marriage might
not be the problem but he didn't get to
work until 10:00 that means whatever
ruined his mood happened in those 3
hours we have to retrace his steps we
I'm not going to investigate my own
husband uhhuh totally well that was a
great chitchat don't you think Gina
seemed like it went real bad for you
chat you know Kevin maybe if we figure
out what caused Raymond's bad mood we
could fix it great idea do know I
suppose we could look into it yes great
let's go right now no time to lose don't
look just run you're trying to get me
out of here before I see the orange soda
you spilled on the chair aren't you I'm
already out the door it worked a lot of
infighting not too late to ditch Amy and
team up with this cat burglar
please boil your only value was you had
a doppelganger which no longer matters
since Bill died in that
accident I can still be useful without
Bill no holes too tight for these tiny
tips for stealing stuff ladies and
Gentlemen please welcome to the precinct
Escape convict number
one Terry where's the music that was a
que I didn't have that Queen song on my
phone and I wasn't going to pay $1.99
for it nice work man you can put your
Pur in holding with the other three
convicts wait other three yeah Santiago
and Bo brought them in that's right it's
3 to one guess you won't be needing this
anymore since you'll be moving in with
me a towel yeah your
towel why won't it burn because it never
fully dries the towel lives and so do we
officer Holt I thought I stationed you
not here right I'm just here in the
plaza looking for
um this a half eaten box of McNuggets
yep it's my lunch uhhuh and what type of
food is a McNugget some type of uh paa
you had to know that was a bad guess
well the point is I needed my paa and I
noticed the skybridge so I thought I
might be of some help but I'll just go
back and stand next to a piece of police
tape and do nothing
wait stop how'd you like to stick around
and assist on the case are you sure Jake
I mean there's only room for one
Manhunter oh Bo right I don't want to
overstep you're not oversteep I mean he
interrupted the song but whatever great
I'll just leave my pie uh on theg ground
save it for later we all know that's not
your lunch on my count 1 2 three I got
it from
here get up get up turn
around you have the right to remain
silent anything you say can it will be
used against you in a court of law
thanks guys I got it from
here skim white chocolate macchiato for
Charles I got it from here I used a gift
card for that okay this is the boiled
decision-making manual one of these
sections will help you with choosing
your partner here we go what do you
prefer eyes or butt brains or body
brains uh sorry nope that's for deciding
lunch horrifying up I found the romance
section now first I will need the names
of the two people you're choosing
between I will not be telling you any
information about them no problem we can
work with that I will just call them by
their initials nope I will call them
couscous and Quin Wan whatever okay now
for this to work right you need to
answer these questions without thinking
who makes you laugh more quwan who has
softer lips cous the new C solay is in
town you have the two best seats in the
House who you bring in is this a reward
or a punishment you decide Kingo great
next question you die and become a ghost
the rules of the afterlife are that of
the movie Casper whose house would you
rather haunt how many more of these
questions are there 309 hello everyone
my name is Roger strike well and I will
be your guest Auctioneer this evening so
many faces to look at I want a radio
Conta test and I'm so excited to be here
tonight to sell you all of these cool
old Greek things our first item up for
bid is Lot number
344 it is this old vase vow if you're
nasty it was made in the
year five and depicts the classic Greek
Fable Boy Meets Girl boy has goat legs
and on the back just a whole bunch of
wheat so let's start the bidding at $10
yes okay started way too
low well I love that you're trying to
step up your sex game but strength is
not your issue stop humming and it does
not turn me on when you bend over and
back up into me gp40 diesel locomotive
with sprung Drive Wheels rule 17
lighting and full underbody detailing
you're going to be the bell of the ball
Terry is is your god oh hail Lord Terry
Giver of Life oh hail Lord
Terry check out Jeff's Junction it's got
an ice cream shop a 50s diner and a
Mexican restaurant with a sombrero on it
what happens to the somero when it rains
I see no drains does it just fill up
with water until the building collapses
killing everyone inside fun fact it
never rains at Jeffers Junction so you
achieve this level of lushness through
irrigation alone I don't know I'm just
trying to build a fun world that's what
model trains are all about imagination
no they're about accuracy people want to
see the world around them exactly as it
is but smaller okay well we can have
part of the model be very accurate and
part of it will be creative I'm okay
with that yes yes as am I uh would you
fetch me the 8 mm level for my office oh
[Music]
sure oops okay Marie cond came up with a
system to unclutter your life you look
at an object and if it doesn't bring you
Joy you throw it away try it sge hello
backup pair of suspenders do you bring
me joy yes because you have tab endings
and a sweet leather yolk I'm so glad
you're in my life I guess I'm keeping
them ooh let me try hello bag of old
dried mushrooms do you bring me joy yes
you provide Rich earthy flavor to both
soups and tease I guess I'm giving mine
too this is fun guys you can't keep
everything that defeats the purpose I
got the same hello unsolved case do you
bring me joy no because you're boring
and you're too hard see you personal
items only Scully get that case out of
the trash Oh for peace sake how many
kbps are you looking
for many yeah that's not an answer I
need an exact
number 100 too few too many four okay
bro I'll give you four kilobytes of
Internet you're making a fool
yourself no you're the
fool hey little man why you so teeny I'm
not teeny I'm average size What a Sad
brag I don't even know who you are but I
know who you are Devin you tell everyone
you got a degree from Stamford but you
really went to Stam forb an online
college based in Arkansas it's a good
school you live with your aunt that's
sad and you spend a third of your salary
on tropical fish and Aquaria you know I
found all this off of 20 minutes of idol
snooping around imagine what I could do
with a dedicated couple of hours what do
you want I want you to give the internet
back to my friends okay we're I'll keep
digging and digging and digging and
digging fine fine I'll give you back
your internet okay just we're through oh
and maybe your co-workers would like to
know what happened on your seventh grade
field trip to DC you monster he pooped
in the reflecting
pools he's done cuff him yes sir
that was the single coolest thing that
has ever happened relax barala that
wasn't even the coolest thing I've ever
done what have you done that's cooler it
was the 8S it was nothing I mean I made
a movie out of it but whatever what what
movie I don't remember the title uh
there was a crime on a plane I was a
passenger was that passenger 57 I
honestly don't know it had to have been
just say it was that you know Peralta
sometimes I don't understand the words
coming out of your mouth oh my God was
it Rush Hour what no you know what I'm
too old for this crap
it was Lethal Weapon sir are you
MTO does that make me
rigs I'm rigs allow me to introduce
Stevie chilling shillin he was my very
first partner and one of the alltime
great takes one to no one man come on
I'm Charles woh hey what's up man I'm
Stevie we heard Stevie and I were beat
cops together we called ourselves the
beatsy boys and yeah it was as cool as
it sounds what what you
want with the
Mone so y would just stand around like
that all the time totally get it my
first partner was also pretty cool
everyone called us Chucky and the
coot
you with the money that you so I guess
we all had great partners that we've
completely moved on from because your's
dad of old age he did anyway we should
motor Jake and I are sticking out a bar
called The Thirsty Ox a lot of crime lot
of danger lot of downtime for inside
jokes would you like some
milk would you like some milk the kind
cuz you look like would you like to milk
please what's it from it's fun he rememb
I know your shift is over and you've had
a challenging night but I think I found
a new way to raise morale follow me to
the briefing
room what's all this it's an afterwork
hang just trying to turn up as it were
we got uh snacks games decorations
chairs yes chairs cool maybe we can Mill
around in small talk about how some of
us are big lying Liars who lie all the
time like a bunch of liars Rosa I don't
think that's good party combo uh maybe
we should just name our favorite sailing
knot I'll
start the bow
line how about some
tunes cool
merry go around music yeah John Philip
Susa the skrillix of his day come on
people hit the Dance Floor have a good
time why is no one having a good time I
specifically requested it Gina why
aren't you dancing I can't I'm in the
middle of a feud with that that's not a
knife guy from crocodile
dunde he's being a real fine I
guess I'll just stop the party I didn't
realize it ever started enough I tried
to make this fun I even learned what
Skrillex was
[Music]
come on man use your muscles use my
muscles oh great why didn't I think of
that great advice Terry you know what
it's a pullup there's not much to coach
here so there's Carrie Miranda Charlotte
and Samantha but New York City is really
the fifth character
H what about Steve he seems nice oh
Steve is nothing no one likes
Steve Steve is nothing
[Music]
okay I don't get it Miranda could have
had Blair Underwood but she settles for
Steve oh but you do get it sir see now
you do how is you doing that helping
me Skully what was
up good job can you do it without
screaming
probably then we're ready you know many
people think that scrambled eggs are the
easiest food to make but that is
incredibly foolish they are a highly
nuanced and complicated dish okay now go
ahead and pour your eggs right into the
pan nice and
slow oh okay now what do I do oh boy
okay well you hear that Sizzle that
means the heat is a little too high on
those eggs well the the higher the heat
the faster the eggs cook the sooner
Kevin eats am I incorrect no you make an
excellent point but we don't want to
feed Kevin burned garbage cooking is
about patience are you completely insane
you never salt Cann a pan the hand the
hand is the middleman okay what you did
is the culinary equivalent of
unprotected sex
you know what you sir are not ready to
scramble
eggs hand over your
spatula
fine I only wish in return I could get
back all the time I just wasted on this
futile
project I'm just going to make Kevin
plain toast for breakfast oh that is
low attention Squad pretty dainty way to
make an announce
to workplace I want to be respectful
well as someone at a high risk for a
spook related death thank you as I was
saying it's time for round four of the
Halloween
[Music]
High if I don't make it till g i l
what's up N9 Jake baral here to tell you
that tonight is the night for the
Halloween Heist Amy already went over
this what Jes what are you doing I
always announce the heist yeah Amy what
the hell are you doing exercising my
right to announce the heist as the
defendant Champion defending Champion
the only reason you won is cuz no one
knew you were even playing it was a
pathetic Act of pure cowardice oh she's
your girlfriend peral not tonight she
isn't although don't kiss anyone else I
love you so much now then this one's for
all such a dork attention squad tonight
dope y'all three really should have
coordinated what I really should be the
one to introduce the heist as the last
legitimate Champion Peralta has in W
since the first year he's a has been
yeah well this has been has been with
your mama all week sorry I feel like I
crossed a line I
apologize attention everyone enough we
know the heist is happening no my
ex-wife just died no more alimony baby
you're so lame you know that Travis wait
a second is this just because I did
Molly with your daughter you did don't
think he knew about that just don't ever
come back here again if you do I'll have
you arrested how dare you I gave you the
best two weeks of my life oh guys I'm so
screwed we got no leads I'm not going to
get any of the money back what do we do
we go directly to Travis's house right
now pee on everything he owns and then
burn that place to the ground Adrian
that's it it is yes I knew wait no no
not anything about anything you said but
Charles didn't you just tell me you
fired someone yeah t I took him out to
dinner he thought I was getting a
promotion it was a whole thing he wept a
lot not as much as me yeah but the point
is he was upset right and he knew where
you like to park the truck uh-huh and
and he never gave me my key back he said
he lost it you really think it's him I
mean it's just a hunch but we should go
to his house and burn it down I was
going to say we could go investigate
sure sure sure and then Burn It To The
Ground no no burning of anything well I
already got the match lit how let's
hurry up and get there this is great
there's nobody here everyone cleared out
as soon as we got here even that actual
pervert was creeped out by
us I can feel your
heat no offense but it feels so good to
breathe air that didn't come out of your
mouth n taken o I know you're working
but you should probably put something on
your screen perverted in case someone
comes in like a lady in high heels
stepping on a businessman sorry yes I
meant to do that I've just gotten so
wrapped up in my research I've been
reading the most thrilling
footnote what was that I don't know
don't worry I'll creep them right the
hell out of
here
hello who's sneaking around back here
Bang You're Dead and so is Kevin oh
thank God it's just you wait no this is
bad in a different way what are you
doing you brought my husband to a public
place he's undercover we're perverts see
you're not fooling anyone Kevin zipper
is up for God's sake wait I'm confused
how did you even know we were here oh my
God you s a Tracker into my neck didn't
you don't be stupid The Trackers are in
your shoes underwear and wallet I also
braided one into your hair in my tangle
you put my husband at risk and for what
because you felt a little cooped up
that's not it you could have cost him
his life what life Raymond I spend every
day lying on the floor of that house
talking with Jake about popular culture
do you know what it means to clap back
Raymond because I do enough we have to
get back to the safe house immediately
let's go and if you're going to be a
pervert Kevin adjust yourself as you
walk move some quarters around in your
pocket you still want to pretend you had
nothing to do with this I didn't and she
didn't either chudy Judy is not a car
thief chudy Judy's an angel she's
putting herself through nursing school
and nurses are the best of our society
name one bad nurse nurse ratchet Kathy
Bates and misery Jackie had a pill
problem okay damn got a lot of real good
examples off the top of your head you
believe me right Jake I mean the fact
pattern's not great but Trudy did seem
very nice when I met her you trying to
get your freak on with my sister what no
I see you looking at Trudy Judy's booty
I am not looking at Trudy Judy's booty
oh you don't think she's a cutie don't
be snoody She's a Beauty but I'm on duty
and you're married well yeah but that
doesn't rhyme I'm sorry I just get so
overprotected she's such a good kid I
guarantee you she didn't steal those
cars WEAU her sitting in a Bentley with
a power amplifier and a homemade
override plugged into the can bus yeah
she guilty since you're leaving I'd like
to make a
toast bye oh my God that was perfect so
nice Gina I got a little going away
present for you don't worry it's nothing
big oh my goodness wow you once said if
you ever die you wanted someone to turn
your tweets into a book so that's what I
did oh my God I said so many witty
things so fast yeah I me I don't know
what to say this is horrifying what this
is way worse than crying I mean you put
so much work into this I'm completely
uncomfortable it makes me kind of makes
me sick Amy there's something I want you
to do right now burn the book I made you
yes it's the only way to cleanse your
childish sentimentality and become the
true you the one that's really
Rosa okay sure I mean it does include a
very personal forward I wrote and $75 of
my best archival glue but yeah this
feels good hey never seen you burning
stuff with a bum Barrel before right on
what was in there Hitchcock first rule
of the bum Barrel never ask somebody
what they're burning well okay then all
right Amy it's time put the book in the
barrel let's
go no I can't do it what I thought you
wanted us to change you I thought I did
too but I don't I like having emotions
okay this is who I am you're leaving and
that's a really big change and I'm going
to cry about it a lot okay and there it
is another flawless Gina moment what
what's going on Amy the lesson I wanted
to leave you with is to just be yourself
if you want to cry like an idiot for
hours on end just do it you want to make
a big old ugly book full of all my
brilliant thoughts do it do
you
Gina oh
wow that was really really sweet oh dip
I got Rosa to feel her feelings too
inadvertent genome moment two for one
come in my babies come in sorry to
interrupt ladies but you might want to
take a couple of steps back this is not
going to smell good UNH unh
[Music]