[Applause]
Barack Obama is the nickel back of
presidents Obama couldn't negotiate
getting a Whopper without pickles at
Woodstock Dave thanks
Dave I bet Obama likes mustard on his
hot dogs because he's gross at Duck
punks just found out my daughter shares
a birthday with Obama
puke in caps at mom of four
munchkins Barack Obama dances like how
his jeans
look you know this jeans thing this is
so old this was years ago come
on my mom bought new conditioner and it
sucks it isn't even conditioning my hair
I blame
Obama Barack Obama
bro do you even
lift well I lifted the ban on Cuban
cigars that's worth
something Barack Obama is
the Barack Obama is the shark NATO of
presidents loud stupid and overhyped #
shark
[Applause]
nat4 President Obama will go down as
perhaps the worst president in the
history of the United States exclamation
point at real Donald
Trump well at real Donald Trump at least
I will go down as a
president a 30 rack of Kors light is $23
now at
sunstop thanks Obama
[Applause]