you lose everything and everything falls
apart and eventually you die and no one
remembers you that is a very good point
make a right turn wait wait wait wait
wait no no no no it means Bear
right up there it said right it said
take a right no no no no no look it it
means go up to the right Bear right over
the bridge and hook up with 307 make a
right maybe it's a shortcut Dwight it
said go to the right it can't mean that
there's a lake there think it knows
where it is going the machine no stop
yelling at me it's there's no Ro
here remain calm I have trained for this
okay exit the window here we go make a
uturn if possible look up for
Le Michel are you okay swim for
it I got you
let go let go
on I got you I got
you come on come
on come
on what
oh
nothing Pam's on vacation and she gets
back tomorrow so it'll be nice to see
her it'll be nice and uh she set a date
for the wedding with Roy uh June summer
so that'll be
nice and that's
that
what oh
nothing Jim's been looking at me kind of
a lot all
week I would be creeped out by it but
it's nothing compared to the way Michael
looks at
me it's going to be okay okay you know
what everybody let's just get over the
whole Merida thing she cracked her
pelvis a tiny little crack and she's
going to be fine so let's just Michael
Angela's cat
died
sprinkles I'm sorry Angela man what a
day
huh how could it get any worse the
computer crashes with the porn and then
Meredith with the accident and then
Pringles
God that's three things I'll tell you
what's going on this office is
cursed and we need to do something about
it well I am taking responsibility and
it is up to me to get rid of the curse
that hit Meredith with my
car I'm not superstitious but I'm I am a
little
stitious I finally broke down and bought
myself
a plasma
TV check it out I actually hung this on
the wall myself it's good I want to show
you something a lot of people in the
room you need more space voila right
into the wall wow sometimes I will just
stand here and watch television for
hours I love it I love this TV hi guys
uh does everyone know my boyfriend Bob
Vance Kevin Malone Bob Vance Vance
Refrigeration Stanley Hudson Bob Vance
Vance Refrigeration Ryan Howard Bob
Vance Vance
Refrigeration what line and work you in
Bob lazy
Scranton sitting in my office with a
plate of grilled fot call a man F just
to see what we're shaking no mic our
town is dope and pretty so check out how
we live in the electric city they call
it scrip what the electric city scrip
what the electric city called p control
if you're bit by a spider but check that
it's covered by your healthare provider
it reminds me of the orientation video
Michael showed on my first day the
Scranton Witch Project I am so scared
when people don't label their personal
food you like cold mines and you want to
see them we check it out yo the an
Museum plenty of space in the parcking
lot the little cars go in the compact
spot spot spot spot spot well so far I
think it is killing I thought it would
either be an A or an A+ but I completely
forgot that there is an A+
plus honestly Michael it's for you to
know it so that you can communicate it
to the people here to your clients to
whomever okay what it's whoever not
whomever it's whomever no whomever is
never actually right well sometimes it's
right Michael is right it's a madeup
word used to trick students no actually
whomever is the formal version of the
word obviously it's a real word but I
don't know when to use it correctly not
a native speaker I know what's right but
I'm not going to say because you're all
jerks who didn't come see my band last
night do you really know which one is
correct I don't know it's whom when it's
the object of the sentence and who when
is the subject that sounds right well it
sounds right but is it how did Ryan use
it as an object as an object Ryan used
me as an object is he right about that
how did he use it again it was Ryan
wanted Michael the subject to uh explain
the computer system the object thank you
to whomever meaning us the indirect
object which is the the correct usage of
the word no one uh asked you anything
ever so whomever's name is Toby why
don't you take a letter opener and stick
it into your skull hey this doesn't
matter hey Dwight hey you want an Eminem
no thanks I'm stuffed no seriously
should have an Eminem they're really
good okay
good
huh so
good hey I thought you weren't supposed
to eat anything for a couple of hours
after you've had a crown put
in they're having this new kind of quick
drying
bonding so sounds like a good dentist oh
yeah
what's his
name
krst your dentist name is
crentist
huh sounds a lot like
dentist maybe that's why he became a
dentist let me see your
teeth let me see him let me see
him me should
flaws I
know fine whatever you want just like
always whatever you want whatever I want
it's never whatever I want it's fine
when I wanted to see Stomp and you
wanted to see Wicked what did we see we
saw when I said that I wanted to have
kids and you said that you wanted me to
have a vasectomy what did I do and then
oh when you said that you might want to
have kids and I wasn't so sure who had
this VCT reversed and then when you said
you definitely didn't want to have kids
who had to reverse back STI stap STI
stap STI stap I did okay you have no
idea the physical toll the three
vasectomies have on
person hello hello this is Dwight shuit
from the dunder mlin Paper Company wow
that's great cuz I need paper excellent
then you are in luck because we are
having a limited time offer only on
everything wow this is my lucky day ask
him his name what is your name sir I am
Bill
butlicker really that's your real name
how dare you my family built this
country by the way be respectful Dwight
please oh yes Michael could you hold on
one second that's my other line what no
but I hello yeah no I'm just on the
phone with this stupid salesman he's so
dumb probably just going to keep him on
the line forever not buy
anything okay it's up to you to change
his mind sorry that was a family
emergency oh no what's wrong you know
what that's private boundaries twight
come on I'm sorry Mr buter as I was
saying we're having a limit a little bit
louder I'm hard of hearing he's hard if
he's an old man okay as I was saying
right now we are having talk louder okay
our prices have never been lower you
have to talk louder never been lower
louder son buter our prices have never
been lower stop it stop
he that is totally inappropriate you
never yell at the client you never you
listen to me sir here we go the three
words I would describe you as is
aggressive hostile and definitely
difficult Mr am I rate right now please
give me another chance me the Mr but
licker give me the phone I have to put
you on with my boss well I should hope
so who is this hello this is Michael
Scott regional manager well this is
Willam M butt licker hello Mr butt
licker how may we help you Michael I
like the sound of your voice you know
what I'm going to do I'm going to buy $1
million over the paper products
today see done thank you very much sir I
don't think you'll regret it you know
what I did you are the master there is
one condition Michael yes you have to
fire the salesman that treated me so
terribly don't do it
Michael it's a million do
sale are you swallowing them whole
you're eating them so fast are they even
tell touching your tongue yeah brownies
is it h pastry cubes made of sugar and
fat no thank you I'll stick with my
jerky so why' you come in here to
socialize and inform ooh
brownies I'm taking two so I can parcel
them up and eat them at my leisure later
on much healthier you're taking two yeah
um but one of them is tiby yeah why
don't you send that to him in Costa
ricao um I'm just going to hand it to
him right now okay Weir know why is that
why is that weird she said she's going
to give it to him right now she's
probably going to because they sit next
to each other yeah they used
to Toby works here again oh can you
imagine oh no you don't know I don't
know what you should probably just
Meander back there take a look see if
he's see if he's back dare
I you know what I'm going to for Old
Time sake
great practical joke Jim got we go to
the
annx I'm no
God no God please no no
no
no Hey
cuz heard you're having money problems
no you didn't listen I got the answer
you declare bankruptcy all your problems
go
away I
declare
bankruptcy I have it song attention
everyone that I want to sing that I
wrote especially for this occasion when
I was up there among the
Flames ready Ryan started the fire it
was always burning it's the world
returning ran started the fire it was
always
everybody I can't believe I started the
fire but I just thought you should
know I think something a little fishy is
going on little fishy yeah I mean I've
been noticing them all day I was
thinking that little girl is a child I
want to see you sniffing around her
anymore this afternoon do you understand
boy have you lost your mind cuz I'll
help you find it what you looking for
ain't nobody going to help you out there
Jesus can come through that door and
he's not going to help you if you don't
stop sniffing after my child okay
Stanley yelled at me
today that was one of the most
frightening experiences of my life
it's kind of
blurry that's
better question what kind of bear is
best that's a ridiculous question false
black bear well that's debatable there
are basically two schools of thought
fact bears eat beets oh bears
beats Battlestar Galactica bears do not
what is going on what are you doing last
week I was in a drugstore and I saw
these glasses uh
$4 and it only cost me $7 to recreate
the rest of the Ensemble and that's a
grand total
of
$11 you know what imitation is the most
sincere form of flattery so I thank
you identity theft is not a joke Jim
millions of suffer every
year Michael oh that's funny Michael
first I was afraid I was petrified no
it's ah uh uh uh Staying Alive stay
alive you were in the parking lot
earlier that's how I know
you ah ah ah ah staying alive staying
alive stay alive stay alive you can't by
the way I use my walk I'm a woman's man
no time to talk it loud women been
kicked around since I was born it's all
right it's okay you can't look the other
[Music]
way alive staying alive yeah okay you
didn't maintain 100 beats per minutes
and the ambulance didn't arrive because
nobody called 911 so you lost him okay
he's dead anyone know what we do next
anybody Rose I have no idea anyone else
we bury him wrong check for an organ
donor card if he has one we only have
minutes to harvest he has no wallet I
check he is an organ donor he is give me
some ice in a styrofoam bucket here we
go
God we search for the organs where's the
heart the precious heart I'm not feeling
well I need to sit
down are you
okay oh my
God oh my God actually it's kind of too
bad we're not coming into work tomorrow
why I bet Michael had some elaborate
theme party planned like scrambled eggs
Saturday like hey everyone let's get
your boss laid Saturday
I have an announcement uh to make I am
moving to Costa Rica thought about it
for a long time now and I'm finally
going to do
it
so I'm just going to hop the fence and
Jog home now
hello hi Michael's Gott paper company to
see Mr David Wallace I believe we're
expected well well
well how the
turntables you ready hm you kidding I
was born
ready
um I don't know how to tell you this but
we have a little bit of a problem know
what the minister just told me that it's
tradition for the bestiest mench to be
older than the groom oh come on I've
never heard of such a I haven't heard of
it obviously but I'm out because I'm
significantly younger than you not
significant as a big I well okay either
way either way
Dwight I can't be there for
you I'm
sorry Jim I just really wish there was
something I could
do
Michael I can't believe you came
that's what she
[Laughter]
said best prank
ever last week I gave a fire safety
talk and nobody paid any attention
ion it's my own fault for using
PowerPoint PowerPoint is boring people
learn in lots of different ways but
experience is the best
teacher today smoking is going to save
lives
does anyone smell anything smokey did
you bring your jerky in
again oh my God uh oh my
God fire oh fire oh my goodness what's
the procedure what do we do people are
dead how did that happen out in the hall
we don't know that the smoke could be
coming through an air dock oh my God
okay it's happening everybody stay calm
what's the procedure everyone what's the
procedure stay
Cal calm down no no Michael no touch the
handle if it's hot there could be a fire
in the
hallway what does warm mean oh my gosh
not a viable option what next the other
door oh here's a door check that one out
how's the handle it's warm okay go to
the back well another option another
option jeez okay come on down everyone I
forget my leave it woman get out of the
way go go go things can be replaced
Phyllis people human lives however
can ah my hand that's hot this one's hot
too okay we're trapped everyone for
himself go get out of way okay okay C
pleas out have you ever seen a burn
victim Mo okay procedure procedure exit
option where do we go folks use a r to
cover the mouth a what a rag a damp rag
perhaps let's remember those procedures
what are the options okay that's the
wrong way we've already tried that
remember your exit points exit points
people what's next stay alive I'm
getting help pull me up you're too heavy
I only weigh 82 lb sa
Bandit how about 911 anyone 911
what do we do use the surge of fear and
adrenaline to sharpen your decision
making okay I am not dying here come
on what is that the fire shooting us
what in the name of God is going on
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
attention employees of Dunder Mifflin
this has been a test of our emergency
preparedness there is no fire it was
only a simulation what fire not real
this was merely a training
exercise so what have we
learned oh come on it's not real Stanley
don't have a heart no no no no no you
will not die Stanley Stanley you will
not die Stanley Stanley Barack is
President you are black Stanley I'm
going to give him mou to mouth no no no
don't give him mouth to mouth for this
you going to swallow his Tong open your
mouth swall don't swallow it
fine leave me
Al SA
[Music]