For the record, I don't squash all of Phil's dreams.
Just the ones that are, you know, potentially fatal.
I'm just trying to get the kid ready for life.
Yes, if we didn't do this to them,
the world would.
Okay, everybody, final launching positions.
Get ready to eat some crow.
It is not as delicious as it sounds.
Okay. Uno. Dos. Tres. Three!
What happened, Cam?
I-I don't know. I-I don't know.
Can we do it again?
No. We only have one pumpkin,
and we just chunk it.
Oh.
Well, we were right.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, guys.
This usually feels a little better, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
All right. I hate to admit it,
but when they put the pumpkin in,
I was kind of hoping it would work.
Yeah.
Me too.
All right, let the gloating begin.
You know, it was a pretty good try.
We don't need your pity.
Let's just get this stuff cleaned up.
Yeah.
Oh- Well,
or if maybe we, um-
We launch it from a steeper angle?
Maybe if you had somebody else,
you know, helping you pull the thing.
But we don't have any more pumpkins.
That's the easy part.
They're on every porch
up and down the block.
Well, we can handle that. Come on, kid!
Come on, let's try one.
Alright, let's do it.
- Alright.
I say pumpkin, they say chunkin.
There are dreamers,
and there are realists in this world.
You'd think the dreamers
would find the dreamers,
and the realists would find the realists.
But, more often than not, the opposite is true.
Maybe if this works,
we should launch my centerpiece next?
It wasn't that bad.
Your rice pilaf was.
Ready.
Here we go.
Okay. Okay.
Keep going.
You see, the dreamers need the realists to keep them
from soaring too close to the sun.
And the realists?
Well, without the dreamers,
they might not ever get off the ground.
Ah. Okay, next one's going
through the, the, the goal thingy.
I can feel it.
Lily, you are not in charge of what you wear.
Of breakfast or anything.
Now put that backpack on
and march it out to the car.
It's too heavy.
Well, that's tough because I'm not
carrying it for you anymore.
I like this new guy. Huh? Oh!
See? I told you it was too heavy.
Oh my gosh! What in the world is in this?
Oh!
Claire, why is there a fully cooked turkey
in the backpack we left at your house?
Yes, Claire. Why is there?
Could it be you made a backup because you never trusted me with the dinner at all?
Well, I thought there was a chance.
What? That I'd screw everything up?
You know what? I have half a mind to
pack up the beautiful meal I made.
Dinner is served.
I don't understand, does everybody get one?
I was just going to sub in my turkey
if you got in trouble, which I mean,
Well, now you touched it.
So you, Alex and Haley will share that one.
Dark meat for your dark, untrusting soul.
Phil!
You know, this was a brand new backpack, and now it's got turkey juice all up in it.
Okay, back it up, Old Yeller.
Okay, could we just stop?
This is Thanksgiving, for God's sake.
And not to mention that
tomorrow is Luke's birthday.
Hey. This is the suitcase
with my present, right?
You had it in the video.
No!
What the hell?
Congratulations, Luke!
You're finally a man. In my country,
when you turn 16, you get your turkey.
Wait, you made the video before
you decided to come back early?
Were you gonna keep the turkey
in there for four days?
It's a tradition.
How did you get that thing through Customs?
It is called Customs.
They respect customs.
Wait a minute. I know this bird.
I've been oiling these breasts all day.
This is my turkey. Done to perfection.
Eat it, Claire!
Wait. So how did dad's turkey
get in their suitcase?
And where did that small turkey come from?
And how did you know to come here?
Dinner was supposed to be at Claire's.
All right! All right!
It's like the Caine Mutiny in here.
Our vacation got canceled at the last minute.
We decided not to say anything
because we wanted a break.
A break from what?
From Thanksgiving craziness.
From. From stress. From yelling.
From these two parading around in dresses.
Oh, that was a one time thing
- Okay. We don't wear dresses at home.
Now, look, I get that Thanksgiving is a big day for families who never see each other.
But this group is together nonstop.
Look, why don't you take the
suitcase turkey home with you?
You take the backpack turkey.
We'll order a pizza, and we'll all call it a night.
Fine. That sounds great. Fine.
- Alright. Okay.
No! No no no no no no no no.
I know I seem like the last person to say this,
but we can't just skip Thanksgiving.
Time is going by so fast. It seemed like only yesterday that Manny was hot for me,
and he's not anymore.
And someday, Alex may have a boyfriend who wants her to spend it with his family.
Okay, we probably got a little window there, but my point is that I love my crazy family,
and I want to spend this holiday with them.
Ay.
- Aw.
If you want a break, we can skip Christmas. Yeah?
Fine
- Okay.
It's settled.
Si.
Skip Christmas.
Okay, cool.
I already had plans to spend
Christmas in Cabo with my friends.
I've gotta get out of here.
Well, we only have one six pack, so in a way, it's good all the girls said no.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Um, my SAT prep group
needed a quiet place to study.
You ain't studying acting.
Okay, we don't have time for this.
You're fa-
Everybody freeze!
Taekwondo!
Eyes on those bloodbats!
Let's burn em down fast!
Come on, Madskillz87!
You're supposed to be on spell interrupt.
Do not let those casters
get off any more frost traps.
Lisa, looks like it's you
and me on the lava demon.
Hang tight!
Powder!
Let's send him back to hell in time
for Madskillz to make it to his oboe lesson.
I thought my dad was embarrassing.
Shut up!
Okay. Let's go! Let's go!
Hello?
Is anybody here?
- Drop it!
Ow! Ow! Getting right to it, I like it.
Please, sir. Have pity. Tis true.
I'm just a common thief. But if you have mercy,
I'll make it worth your while.
Oh, what medieval creature is this?
Half man, half robot, Walter?
If you come out now, you simpering coward,
maybe I'll show you a little mercy.
Please don't hurt me.
It was her idea. I'm the one who wanted to go slow.
Ruben.
Oh, Alex.
Claire.
Ruben again? He wore a Batman cape to the first day of high school.
You're really judging me right now when you look like a
hooker at Comic-Con.
Yes. This was a miscalculation on my part,
and I will be getting my coat.
Claire, what is going on?
I am getting out of here as soon as I-
Luke.
Is that beer behind your back?
Get out here. You are so grounded.
Miss Dunphy, do you ever tutor?
Dude!
Oh, I'm just gonna grab my razor
scooter and bounce.
Happy Bir-
No! You know, it's no one's birthday.
You're probably here for the same reason as those two.
Well, technically, this is your fault,
because we were afraid our marriage was getting as boring as
yours.
But based on your outfit, we need to work a little harder.
You should all be ashamed of yourselves.
I'm the only one authorized to be here by sneaking in.
You've disrespected me and violated the trust between me, my clients,
and this sexy, sexy house. No, no.
Great. Now Lisa's dead.
I want everybody out of here right now.
Well, at least we have our house to ourselves still, does
Magic Mitch have another set in him?
Yeah, his grandma's built up shoe isn't gonna pay for itself.
Okay, we need to work on your sexy patter.
Off the lamp. Off the lamp.
I love you, Mr. Goat.
Aw. You see, Joe, you listen to mommy,
and now you have a new best friend.
What?
You're cold? I'll go get you a blanket.
Well, if he was going to get the pig a blanket,
you know what that would be called?
Pig in a blanket.
Okay, I teed that one up for you. All right,
it's time to fry this turkey. Somebody please lower my
splatter goggles, boys.
You heard him.
You do it. You're not the president of goggle lowering.
I would be if they took a vote.
What could Cam have done?
Maybe he's the one who's having an affair.
I saw a list of clues in a magazine.
Has he joined a gym or bought sexy new underwear recently?
I think it's sweet that you think we're capable of having an affair.
But we're just. We're so tired.
All right now, boys. The key is you drop it nice and gentle like.
Milo!
Run away! Goat!
Oh! Oh. I think she wanted to run to the barn.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Let me put a positive spin on this.
Who here likes goat?
Luke?
And there you go. That is me clearly running in front of Pritchett's Closets.
Oh, yeah? Yeah, with the Reagan Bush poster in the window.
Huh? The photo is a fake.
It's not my fault, Manny made it.
Manny was photoshopping everything,
so Joe was in real danger?
I did not realize how easy it would be
for you to connect those dots.
Pretty disappointed in you, Luke.
Well, you know, it's easy to see where he learned it from.
His mother's a cheater.
What? Oh, don't get so hot and bothered.
Your makeup's already running. And what do you mean?
Chinese character on your bruise?
Yeah, it's probably an imprint from the intruders ring. And
I'm sure he was in a gang of some sort.
Just give it up, Mitchell. He knocked himself out with some
nunchucks that I confiscated as acting vice principal.
Oh my God, Kung Soo is back. Daddy!
Did you hear that?
Cam! Cam didn't really win the football game.
He stole the last play from the lady coach.
Accidentally, I overheard it on a walkie talkie that I
require as an acting vice principal,
which is a position I'm pretty proud of
because I'm basically a sheriff.
You're not.
Yes. I am basically a sheriff.
I wear a hat. I have a badge.
Hey, hey, hey.
Dad is doing his trick, and he's never done it before. He could die.
What trick?
Oh, Phil, honey, wait. You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I'm the only loser in a remarkable family of winners.
No, no, no, we are not all winners.
It turned out we all stink.
It doesn't matter. I don't want to live a life ruled by fear.
I have to do this trick today.
Although it is getting hard to breathe.
Don't stop. Dad, you can do this.
I believe in you.
It's not.
Very interesting helping honey!
Okay, I'm just gonna try to barrel through this. It's
Normandy. I'm an American G.I. named Tony Rosetti.
I'm from Brooklyn, and I love my mama's home cooking.
But I don't think I'm gonna be able to get out.
Is he talking as Tony Rosetti or as Phil?
What is wrong with you, cowards?
Phil needs
help.
Oh! Oh.
It's too late to get out. No,
this was a mistake.
Something's wrong. Dad!
Oh, God. Phil! Phil! Ah! Oh my God!
Holy crap! Where'd he go?
Private Renzetti reporting Operation Overlord is a success.
Oh!
Cocktails are on me.
That was amazing.
Got to hand it to you, Phil, you get the big turkey leg.
Let's take this party to the table.
Come on, hippies.
Hello, you two.
Hi.
How about a little quiche?
Oh. How European? Mhm.
Oh, Renaldo.
What's your secret?
Cam got offered that coaching job in Missouri,
and Pepper got his eighth facelift.
What? I know we don't buy soup anymore
because he can't close his mouth all the way.
Cam, you got the job.
And you're moving.
Damn it, Renaldo. Apparently, Pepper's not the only one
who can't keep his mouth closed. Go serve your little apps.
I can't believe this.
Don't panic. I'm. I'm gonna turn it down.
Really? But it's what you've always wanted.
I know, but Mitchell, he's. I've never seen him so happy.
I can't ruin that. I'm. I'm not even gonna tell him I got the offer.
Look, I am not a fan of the idea of you guys leaving,
but if you don't tell Mitchell,
you're gonna end up resenting him.
No, that's. That's not how I'm built.
I make decisions, move forward, don't look back.
No regrets.
Hey, everyone. I just want to thank you all for coming to
see our new home and meet our precious new roommate,
Rexford. And I also want to thank my wonderful husband, Cam,
who really led the charge and made all of this possible. I.
I couldn't be happier right now,
and it's all because of him.
Now, if I could just get him to give up hogging the covers, huh?
Cause I haven't given up enough for you.
This is so embarrassing. I just realized Renaldo was
offering me quiche.
So you were never gonna tell me you got offered the job?
It's just that you seemed so happy,
and I couldn't ask you to give that up.
Cam, you've been wanting to move closer to your family for years,
and this is your dream job. No,
no, this is my chance to be there for you.
Are you sure?
I don't care where we live as long as you're there by my side.
Always.
Oh.
All right, now let's celebrate with some champagne.
Yeah.
Mitchell. That was beautiful.
Well, everyone was looking at me.
What the [bleeped] was I supposed to say?