[Music]
if I see her what do I say that I'm
doing here in the building you came to
see me I work in the building what do
you
do I'm an architect oh I'm an
architect have you designed any
buildings in New York have you seen the
new addition to the
Guggenheim you did that yep y it it
didn't take very long either what about
architect stepen he's into architecture
hey just like you pretend to be
let me be the architect I can do it I
can look why couldn't you make me an
architect you know I always wanted to
pretend that I Was An Architect I'm uh
I'm an
architect really what do you
[Music]
design uh
railroads I thought Engineers do that
they can you very knowledgeable
I'm uh I'm also an
architect you're an
architect I'm
not I can discuss other things you know
architecture nothing is higher than
architect I suppose you could be an
architect well isn't an architect just
an art school dropout with a tilty desk
and a big ruler it's called a t Square