that is nearly it but before we go we do
have time for a quick visit to the big
red chair who's up first hello hello hi
hi hopes for you what's your name Jenny
Jenny lovely and what do you do Jenny
I'm a disability support worker okay and
where do you do that H well I do it in
Ireland at the moment but also in
Australia because I kind of live there
as well oh okay okay very good and
whereabouts in Ireland Wicklow so not
really near cork no but wicko is lovely
very nice okay off you go with story H
so I have two belly buttons and I use
them to get free
drinks now we're
talking yes bring it home irel bring it
home oh
yeah I want to see it that's not the
whole story okay okay you got two belly
buttons yeah so I used them to get free
drinks a lot and there's a lot of
stories but one of them um I go on a
birthday Adventure every year so I went
just and we need to backtrack slightly
is one just something that looks like a
belly button or do you have two belly
buttons they're legit so what your two
in bical cords well the doctor thinks I
could have absorbed my twin in the womb
oh we don't
know she she has her own twin in the
w a story you got a story yeah wow
that's not even her
story that's just a buy the bue so
you've eaten your twin you've got the
you've got the two got the two belly
butt you're now out in a birthday
Adventure okay go so in Queen town in
New Zealand and uh there was an Irish
bartender in one of the bars so I'd
shown him the buttons the night before
and I got some free drinks in so I was
like right this is the place to go for
my birthday going to get some free
drinks and they had cocktails and
teapots there so I went up to it I was
like right any chance of some free
teapots now I know I've shown you the
buttons but come on it's my birthday and
he was like actually wait there we've
got a call who's terrified of belly
buttons and if we get you to show you
them we like we will give you free
teapots for the rest of the night if you
show your belly buttons to our colleague
I was like yeah let's do it so they
brought me over to the bar where it goes
up like this and they grabbed her by the
shoulder so she couldn't move and they
were like go go go so down went the
waistband and out came the buttons and
uh I showed them to her and she was like
and she completely freaked out and
started crying and left and uh they
high-fived me and they gave me free
gbots for the rest of the
night free you're free to walk but can
we can we see okay I have to un oh okay
okay look away look away everyone look
I'll just s like this for a wait wait oh
there they
are an upstairs and downstairs you can
walk you can walk who are you Simon this
is Simon come on do it again
would be Trill to see you so where are
you from s uh from East Putney East
Putney East py
massive okay assignment yes off you go
okay when I was 10 my parents took me to
a small
farm don't I say anyway we're going to a
small farmer we took the youth there and
so can't understand a word you are
saying okay dad was looking for some
animals and things to take home to our
farm and so anyway him and Mom spotted
this new dining room table and I was
just wandering around in my in my jandal
and you know just checking out the stuff
Mom and Dad spotted this table and
chairs that they thought that's going to
be perfect in the dining room we put it
on the back of the Ute and we're going
home and us boys is setting up me and my
two brothers sitting up on the back of
the Ute in the chairs and a dining room
table chairs dad thinks it to be a good
idea oh I know what we'll do you boys
want ice cream out the back you know
like yeah absolutely whatever ice cream
next thing you know we're all sitting
there looking our ice creams sitting on
the back dad decides seen a bit of
Formula One he'd like to take Corner
probably a bit quicker than he should
have me on my
chair bang fall down on the road like
that hi hi what's your name Ellis Ellis
Alice sorry Alice sorry Alice where you
from Alice New Zealand oh my
good yeah do you know Rose mfil no I
don't what
how you don't know who I
am I find that hard to believe where are
you from in New Zealand Oakland I'm from
Oakland what school did you go to a
small school called St Dominics College
I know St Dom's uh yeah did you go to I
went to Oran Girls Grammar oh everyone
knows or girls everyone knows yeah yeah
yeah we've got a reputation uh wait so
how old are you I'm sorry sorry I'm I'm
just interviewing her now because I I
swear to God I know you I think we do
have friends of
friends oh oh she's admitting it now I
also my favorite thing about you Alice
is that you're wearing your
coat like you're just going to be
flipped and
leave yeah list let's hear her story
let's hear your story off you go Alice
okay um so a few years ago my boyfriend
and I went on a holiday to Vietnam m
yeah and I quickly learned when I
arrived in Vietnam that I don't do very
well in heat and humidity um so we went
on a um day trip down to the meong Delta
which is about 4 hours outside of hoochi
Min City um I was melting melting the
entire day um and then on the way back
um the um airon and the bus just
completely broke I then proceeded to
have uh a big meltdown okay Alice
remember you're representing our country
here okay sorry Snappy um so bus pulls
over I refuse to get on a may or may not
have said you don't understand I'll die
if I get back on that bus um arrive back
and hoim wake up realize I have um left
my phone somewhere at the
temp I mean I was as nice as I was that
story it was like it was happening in
real time
you're going to get that with the St
Dom's girl okay all right only four
hours from oim in City it felt like five
hey I wasn't in the mood for that no I
wasn't in the mood for
it I find this so difficult ruthless
tonight let's find out who's up next
hello hi hi what's your name I'm Alison
lovely where are you from uh
Northumberland Northumberland and do you
live down here now or you just on a day
trip no I've just come down specially
for the show oh how exciting and what do
you do in northand I retired in August
after 37 years in the NHS well
[Applause]
done they don't need people anymore
retire yeah take it easy don't go into
that
LE I know I can you won't be flipped
oh retired from the
NHS all
right had a really horrific story
now off you go with your story okay so
I'm away for the night with my boyfriend
at the time we've been out drinking we
go back the hotel and we've had lots to
drink I wake up in the early hours and I
really need the L and instead of going
into the bathroom I'm disorientated and
go out the hallway the door shuts behind
me I'm knocking I'm banging and he's in
an alcoholic coma and won't wake up and
I think oh my God I am going to wet
myself what do I do so with my best
pelvic floor I waddle along to the
corridor and there's stairs that are
carpeted thank goodness and I slightly
deposit a bit of pee on each step three
flights of
stairs and this man appears and he says
can I help you and I went oh I'm locked
out my room and you want I know I'm the
night Porter and I've been watching you
on the CC
TV good story you can
walk oh excellent It's the lady in the
strawberry cardigan hello what's your
name beex and where are you from beex
New Zealand New Zealand lovely and but
you're living here now or yeah yeah not
in a holiday that's for
sure all right Vex off you go with your
story okay so um I just lounging on the
sofa watching telly I had my little dog
sleeping next to me he was lying on his
back and um he starts kind of like
twitching and wiggling and as sleeps
fine he's having a Little Dream but
suddenly out of nowhere some
liquid I can't apologize enough I don't
think we've ever had dogs spunk in a
story before but that's wait what a dogy
wet dream what was
that yeah a dog in a wet dream got
little imaginations
could have been P it could have been it
could have been P could it could have
been p i mean that's probably more
embarrassing for the poor dog wet itself
uh anyway sorry oh hello hi hi what's
your name Alex Alex lovely and where you
from Alex New Zealand New Zealand do you
know beex no I made her tonight though
oh friend for
life I saw that look
and what do you do here Alex uh I work
for an advertising agency okay what sort
of clients like sexy clients or doll
Pharmaceuticals doll okay off you go
with the story uh so uh as you know I'm
from New Zealand uh however my grandma
she was born and raised here in London
so we decided the family um when she
passed away that it'll be quite poetic
that her kind of final send off would be
um in a double dick of bus so the day
came to take her to the cremator
and then um but no one kind of thought
to measure the coffin versus the door
um and it was it was old bus so it had a
pole in the middle so we couldn't get
her get her in there but we didn't have
any other option and it was kind of
either put her in the boot of the car or
kind of trying to figure out the bus so
we ended up strapping around with some
bungee
cords it doesn't doesn't end there sadly
um it with the whole point of the of the
bus was that so the whole family there's
like you know 16 17 of us would all kind
of be able to be with her on the
40-minute drive of course um so we then
me my cousins and aunties and stuff all
proceeded to jump over my grandmother's
coffin to get into the bus um and then
jump back off again uh when it came to
arriving at the
crematorium so yeah I'm going to let her
let her walk yeah yeah you're walking
you're walking Alex well
done hello nice lady hi hi what's your
name Lauren Lauren yeah so I'll f with
your story all right so I'm sorry but
this story is going to put someone on
the spot on that stage um I'm one of
three girls about 10 years ago I was on
holiday in Dublin checking in Dublin
International Airport and my 11-year-old
sister starts watching someone check in
and she runs up to this person and says
oh my God are you Anne
halfway and then turns around whips off
her sunglasses and says hi you can call
me Annie and then you know proceeds to
interact and talked to all of us asking
how our holiday is posing pictures with
us it was so nice and was so lovely and
that would have been a really great
story had it ended there however after
an left my mother then just started
crying hysterically about how nice an
hathway was all through checkin all
through
security who naturally none of these
people had any context and naturally
thought she was bat [ __ ]
crazy thank you an for being so lovely
and nice and for making my mom that's
like
story
nice Benedict Cumberbatch and I were
actually at the same boarding school uh
we both went to Harrow and there are
lots of rumors circulating about what he
got up to there so I thought I'd use
this do it
now I've got your
back I've got your back you didn't I had
it
just sat at it
now okay so about 3 years ago I went to
London to go to the premiere of The Iron
Lady to try and meet Merl oh my God so I
took my mom and my best friend we kept
missing her as she was like making her
way through the crowds and my mom got
fed up of the cold and went into the
National Theater by the time we found
her she was drunk and when I say drunk I
mean steaming your mother or me yeah my
[Applause]
mother so we went to like take my mom
back to the hotel but we went past the
premier again and she was talking to the
security guards and she told them that
she was their Undercover Boss and secret
millionaire but they belied
to we met Merl came out to the after
paath and was like she got into her car
and we were like oh it's fine we've seen
her I'm so happy and the window was down
a bit in the front of the car and we
were all like oh I'm so cold I'm so cold
and Merl got out of the car and came and
meet me and my friends and my mom was
like oh thanks marold
babes I was like Mom just we're taking
you home
now you could walk you could walk well
done nearly it we go just time for a
quick visit to the big red chair now
Alan is all set there he is he's ready
he's ready okay let's find out uh who's
going to be trying to keep you in that
chair who's up first
hello hi what's your name Franchesca
Franchesca and where are you
Franchesca I'm in North Finchley in
London lovely I don't like the color of
your
curtains they're not mine I'm in a house
shair don't BL me right back at you
they're not my choice what do you do in
North
VY uh I'm an actor and I also work in a
local puup okay so nothing
um
unemployed I've been there it gets
better thank you please put me on
Bridget and I'd love to be on it yeah
yeah yeah all right off you go with your
story and remember you're trying to keep
Alan in that chair okay good luck
everyone off you go okay so a few years
ago I was working in Sheffield in a
theater and we have this Barn restaurant
where the audience and cast would come
before and after a show and one night
this famous person had been to see the
show and came into the bar afterwards
where I served them um and I was making
their drinks I think it was like two gen
and tonics and as I was making their
drinks these two cast members came over
and started asking for their photos and
that kind of thing so I put the drinks
on the bar they turn around pick up
their drinks and then walk over to their
table without paying now you're probably
wondering who this famous person is it
was grae
Norton I knew it was going to be
me I never pay for
drinks before we go just time for visit
to the big red chair who do we find in
it tonight hello hello hi what's your
name Sarah Sarah hello Sarah and where
about you from Sarah um near Market
Harbor lerare oh you know Market Harbor
near Market Harbor Mark Harbor
adjacent uh are you just out in the
country are you in a little village or
something yeah in a little village in a
little village it will remain nameless
okay I tried you did did you work for
MI6 all right Sarah off you go with your
story I used to work for the foreign
[Applause]
office what
what so on anyway so I was at the
British Embassy in Monte Vio Uruguay and
one of my jobs I had to cover for the
accountant one time and I had to go to
the bank and cash some checks and get
some money and while I was in there two
armed robbers came in and um bundled us
all into the corner there was a lot of
crying not me um but a lot of people
were crying and upset and I was trying
to sort of help people around and you
know do my do my Consul thing and um
eventually the robbers found what they
needed and ran off the police came and
it took forever and ever to answer all
their questions um meanwhile eventually
I I got out and I was like oh and I was
a little bit nervous and a bit sort of
shaken myself and I thought well do you
know I've done my bit the Ambassador
will be so proud of me you know I've uh
helped all these people there'll be a
coup of tea maybe there might even be a
gong or you know an MBE who knows you
know anyway I got back to the Embassy
shut everybody gone home I found out the
next day our driver had messaged and
said she's held up at the bank she won't
be back early so you might as well all
go home so and I was like like I was
held up at the bank you know H up the no
tea no nothing you deserve to walk you
deserve to walk sir well
done a bank
robbery I mean that is a better class of
story than we're used to I mean normally
there's some dog poo involved or
something but no hello hello hi what's
your name my name is Podrick Podrick I
think I know where you're from I'm from
Ireland and what part of Ireland you
from I'm from keni Kenny I used to live
in Kenny oh nice one not really
uh cut that out I'm going to Ireland
tomorrow
uh how long have you been here Podrick
oh I'm here like 12 hours oh I see
okay fresh off the plane or the boat
have you moved here 12 hours ago no no I
just came for the show oh okay you're
just here for the are you here for the
weekend no no come back
tomorrow you know what on telly I
all right off you go with your story
okay so about four years ago we went on
a hiking trip in school I was about 16
at the time and then we had to hike
about 25k and we were all sharing rooms
anyway and we went back to the hospital
after hiking about 15 just up for a
minute work Jam Le Curtis is looking at
you like like you're ringing a
bell I heard it's all good it's all good
keep going okay so uh So you you're on
your 25k hike yeah and we were told at
600 p.m. after dinner that we to meet us
at reception and the teachers and
everyone would go on the hike and anyway
I was share in the room with Kevin and
Kevin was having these pains in his
chests and he kept like holding his
chest and breathing in and out really
heavily and we all thought Kevin was
faking it to get out of the hike and
like I was kind of like yeah it's a good
point I play that card but whatever and
anyway we just left Kevin and went down
to reception and about 50 minutes later
an ambulance pulls up outside and a
paramedic comes in and gets Kevin and
loads him into the back of the ambulance
turns out Kevin was having a minor heart
attack and the eight of us in the room
did not give a [ __ ] about
you very quickly before I flip you uh uh
uh is he okay yeah he's fine just oh
good good that's
yeah Fiona oh I like that that was
seamless that
Fiona it's like your Siri or something
Alexa Theona play BBC Radio
too okay Fiona where are you from I'm
from Cornwall originally but I live in
Su in Su okay and what are you doing
Siri I am a wine Ambassador for a New
Zealand Winery okay good job uh okay off
you go with the story okay so I was on
FaceTime with my mom and I was chatting
and then all of a sudden my husband
comes out the shower naked
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what happened and then what
happened something horrible something
horrible
happened the mother got turned on or
something who's up next oh hello oh
hello hi what's your name misty misty
lovely where are you from M I live in
East London East London is that where
you're from though I no I'm originally
from America oh which bit
grew up in Nebraska and then uh lived in
Seattle for the last 20 years wow so you
just visiting here no you live here no
we live here now okay and what do you do
I uh teach ukulele in primary schools oh
oh I wondered who did
that
con you were doing a great job thank
you parents all over his lond going is H
her that's the
reason all you know with your story uh
so when I lived in uh Seattle area I
worked for a large software corporation
and um my team was about 350 to 400
people and we had a big event that was
going on and uh we were giving out
t-shirts at the event and they love
nothing more than t-shirts um and so we
had somebody come into my office early
and say hey I'm not going to be there
but could you save me a small T-shirt
because most of them are extra large um
so after the big meeting went off I
fired off an email to this whole team of
350 people and said um um you know great
meeting uh and John I left an extra
large shirt on your chair I'm sorry it's
all I had and then I closed my laptop
and went home and on the drive home I
could hear my phone blowing up next to
me and like ding ding Ting going off
forever and I thought I've got to pull
over somebody's diet or something and so
I pulled over and it was then that I
realized that I left the r and off of my
mail and so I said John I've left an
extra large [ __ ] on your chair I'm sorry
it's all I
he here she
goes hello hello gr hello what's your
name Roger Roger all right Roger and
what do you do Roger I'm a doctor he's a
doctor like an actual doctor yeah
yeah no there's a lot of you
know like a general practice or do you
have a specialty I work in a hospital
okay like a doctor
yeah he knows what he's doing yeah the
hospital I work here H and where do you
do it in London in London keep it nice
and vague uh but on Monday someone will
see this face and go oh for [ __ ] sake
that's my
doctor I'm relying on him off you go
with his story so I uh took a 24-hour
round trip to uh New York because I
wanted to see Springsteen on Broadway
knew you'd be one of these stories yes
and uh everything was going fine I got
to the theater Door and I checked my
ticket in and the ticket didn't work uh
what happened uh there was a mixup and
uh the friend who I'd got the ticket
from was back in London at home asleep
with his phone switched off so quite a
challenging situation to be in as you
can imagine
yes very very luckily a good friend Lori
um from New Jersey was there with me and
she swapped her ticket with me so I got
in to see the show and she had to
Wrangle with the box office eventually
they let her in 30 seconds before the
show started
oh that was
brutal I mean interesting for
him that was just a Trip Advisor review
that's I was so invested
I he got in he got in no I was worried
that he FL all the way and he hadn't got
he got in he's a doctor he can heal
himself hi there hi what's your name
Ryan Ryan and where you from Ryan I'm
from New Zealand lovely home of the
story New Zealand and are you traveling
have you sett living here for two years
for two just just two years
yeah
yeah what are you do what are you doing
for two years uh I'm an electrician an
electrician yeah handy okay uh his card
get his
card I'll me go with your story ran uh
so I was at a new year Festival um I'd
had a bit too much to drink during the
day in the camp ground uh I was walking
along to the festival and I needed to
get rid of a bit of what i' drunk um so
I saw a whole lot of portal I ran up to
them ripped the door open uh projectiles
be everywhere uh then I looked down and
I just spewed all over a guy who was
sort of relieving himself on the L
um I was a bit freaked out first thing
that came to mind he looked angry he was
going to whack me I gave him a bit of a
whack myself slammed the door and ran
away
I qu no no no I that's awful no I quite
like that he vomited on someone and then
hit
them that's awful no do you I I I would
let you walk by couch
walk walk that's do
you oh he's gone he's gone too late that
is nearly it before we go just time for
a quick visit of the big red chair who's
there hello hello hi how tall are you
very yeah you must are you 7 feet tall
something like that yeah yeah what's
your name my name's Luke Luke okay Luke
and where you from I'm from New Zealand
hey it's been a while it's been a while
since we had a New Zealander do you live
there or here I live here okay what do
you do here Luke um I'm a committee
coordinator in central London a
committee coordinator yeah very vague
and mysterious and dull really
boring very boring yeah you you should
release a
song well apparently it's really easy
uh just do bit of M golf you're there
all right Luke off you go with your
story lovely so a few weeks ago I was in
VI I'm on a little solo trip on my own
and I met up with this guy on a date who
I'd met a few weeks ago and um we went
to the Christmas markets and very
romantic very cute wholesome Vibes so
walking around with mold wine it was the
first snowfall of the Season it was very
lovely and wholesome yeah and um he
suggested we go to one of the s and I
was like oh lovely like never been to
European saers before but heard
that how old is
he should we go to a SAA oh
lovely is he
okay he's okay he's
okay he's dead now is there a foam pit
back there what happened no it's quite
safe it's quite safe yeah it looks it
looks more dramatic than it is I've done
it it's fine get in there I've done it
I've done it let's do it now no no
Dakota
no who's up next hello hi hi what's your
name Tracy Tracy lovely and what do you
do Tracy um I have a business selling
eoin gifts for children eoin for H pony
m GS love presents oh you you sell
things to Pony mad children that's right
oh so basically [ __ ] with ponies on it
yes exctly mean quality [ __ ] with Pon on
yeah yeah nice and where are you from
London London okay you know home of the
pony man
children offie go with your story so
when I'm married I was really lucky to
become a part of very big Irish family
so that means lots of weddings
christenings funerals and on this
occasion it was a funeral so off we went
and obviously with Irish funerals
there's always a mass first so as we're
going into church my husband says you
have turned your phone off haven't you
and I was a bit offended and I showed
him my had so that was that between the
funeral and the cemetery we had to drive
there so I thought well I'll quickly
check my phone emails messages Etc
anyway we get to the funeral and we're R
the gravide and the coffin is being
lowered in literally as my phone rings
but what made it 10 times worse is my
phone ringtone is I've got one less
problem without
you you can walk you can walk yeah
that's a good very good
good hello hi what's your name Ellen
Ellen lovely and where you from Ellen
Sydney Sydney in Australia and do you
live there or here no live here now okay
what do you do here I'm a nurse and a
paramedic wow okay thank you now when
people have nice jobs you feel a bit bad
off you go Ellen with your story so one
night in A&E a gent comes in quite
hunched over looking really really
uncomfortable and I go hey mate what's
brought you into A&E tonight and he goes
so I was gardening naked I've fallen
over
oh what do you think it was a
wheelbarrow I mean you know a lawn mower
who
knows you heard those stories before
haven't you what did you just do to
her she's a nurse she can heal herself
what
happens she's gone she's gone now so
what do that mean you're like you're
over it you're not into it it's a bad
story well it's just I feel I've heard
the you know I was putting in a light
bulb and then I sat on it that kind of
thing really we've all heard those
stories haven't
we last dinner party what what what than
doesn't know what the red chair is I
have no idea and that lady just fell
back yeah no she did she's okay she's
okay I say I hope she's okay let's try
another one okay okay hello hello hi
sorry to keep you waiting what's your
name Jenny Jenny lovely and what do you
do Jenny I'm a photographer oh yes and
what do you take photographs of
portraits all people all people like
show busy things or a little bit
sometimes yeah okay is your story
involving anyone on our couch no okay we
can all relax
everyone all right jny off you go with
your story um so my husband and I had
been invited to a really Posh wedding
and so we'd been on the champag since
about midday so by the time the dance
flooor opened we were three sheets to
the Wi wind good on you yeah and um
anyway on the dance floor um I've got
had the time of my life from Dirty
Dancing came on yeah and I motioned to
my husband who was the opposite side of
the Dance Floor that we should do the
lift and he was like yeah okay so I
kicked off my shoes I tucked my dress
into my knickers and I ran full Pelt at
my
husband we crashed into each other and
we went down like a ton of bricks and I
then find myself straddling my husband
with bruis kn knes and my dress right up
around my waist and I look at him and
I'm and I say what was that and he
looked at me and went sorry I've never
seen Dirty
Dancing walk yeah you walk you more
on okay so you see if you get to the end
of your story you're good that's that's
the and she comes and joins us no oh you
still never see her
again in a way the end of the story is
kind of the same
read one more go on yes yeah let's have
another one yeah yeah hello hi there hi
who are you I'm Linda Linda Lovely and
where you from Linda I'm from
northamptonshire northamptonshire dine
northamptonshire and uh what do you do
or in northamp I'm retired but I used to
be a district nurse so you'll probably
tip me in a minute
no I don't tip every
nurse I have high hopes for you Linda
off you
fingers crossed uh what's your story off
you go well I I many 20 years ago it
probably was I was asked to go and see
this man cuz he'd been constipated for
three days and nothing have worked Chapo
gold
so so anyway in those days we used to do
what's called a manual removal I mean
draw your own conclusions anyway we got
there and the man assumed the position
and did I've got a what did they do now
I no idea I've been retired is there a
hoer or something I so Manuel he assumes
the position we're there yes so I'm
feeling around and I can feel something
really hard and I'm thinking I thought
it was a stone actually anyway I got it
out and I went and ran it under the tap
and it happened to be his wedding ring
anyway I the his wife was standing there
and she said do you know I've been
looking for that for two
days he'd obviously swallowed it
accidentally somehow I don't know but it
was really funny because we used to call
it digging for gold and that day I
actually got
gold you can walk you can
walk I didn't think oh don't be
nervous oh you're fine you're fine
what's your name Zoe Zoe and where you
from Zoe I'm from um Scotland on FR
Galloway but I lived in Ireland for
about 20 years it's a lovely accent very
nice where abouts in Ireland did you
live uh for Moy County Cork for Mo home
of the pencil horrible
[Laughter]
town no it's got a giant pencil in it
has it's got a bridge if people want to
jump off
it I hated
the we're looking forward to this
story I think the cannon is
loose off you go um I'd moved to Ireland
and started a new job on a big stud farm
and I'd also started a relationship with
my boss
and it was she I've got to St you for a
second did you say slug Farm or stud
Farm stud Farm stud stud stud Farm hes
okay we got it got it okay so um I was
at the stage in the relationship where
you don't show your true colors where
you you kind of want to look like you're
nice and kind and do the small things
and there was this one morning I had to
get up early to go and work in the north
and I thought it's not nice when the big
light goes on so be kind and I'll cover
his face but he woke up when I was
putting the pillow over his
face and he abolutely M you w you
w hello the hopes of a Nation are riding
on you sir uh what's your name hi I'm
Reuben and uh where do you live Reuben
um I live in Oxford okay the hopes are
fading
but but off you go Ruben
okay so I'm a student and I've been like
job hopping and I was at a job as a
baker in a supermarket yes and while I
was while I was baking I had to keep
going into the freezer and back and
while I was in the freezer I kept
getting this idea which was to to see if
my tongue would stick if I licked the
wall now it was a really really busy day
and I I I went into the freezer and I
just I thought about it and I did it and
as soon as I did it my my tongue's stuck
and I was there completely stuck for
about 30 minutes and then I started
getting this stressful feeling that I
realized I put I had bread in the oven
and so I could hear beeps and things and
I was thinking there's only one way I'm
going to have to pull my tongue
off and grae when I tell you there's
still a bit of my
tongue that was a it was a good story it
was a good story he didn't it didn't he
didn't go back and scrape off he didn't
go back and scrape off he just let let
me the free health and safety yeah hi
good evening hi good evening to you H
what's your name critty Kitty yes lovely
and where you from Kitty thank you I'm
from North London okay and what do you
do kitty I'm a business manager in
higher education okay nice yes oh we're
applauding that we're applauding that
well Kate Blan was no no one else was
interested off you go with the story KY
okay to caveat this was years ago in
case any colleagues are trying to work
out who who this was and who who this
happened to but uh festive season going
for drinks with work colleagues uh we go
to a nearby bar you know going to be a
good time everybody's in good spirits
finish work etc um a little bit of drama
at the beginning of the evening somebody
thought their bag was stolen but it was
misplaced uh somebody else thought that
their drink had been drunk but we just
figured that they had you know drunk it
themselves um fast forward during the
evening one of my friends uh is
signaling to me that she's feeling
really really sick she's going to be
sick not sure how soon it's going to
happen so I grabb the closest thing and
and as fast as I can uh near to me which
is a glass so she's sick in the glass
not too messy it was just liquid few a
little bit of froth so you know no sweet
corn no carrots we're we're good I'm
Fanning her I'm feeding her water
helping her to calm down it's not
working we need to go outside I grab our
bags I grab our coats uh and I grab the
glass cuz I want to go and hand it in at
the bar but it's not
there I turn around and the content no
sorry the contents are being drunk by
the person that we realize was going
around drinking everybody's
drinks that's a good story you can
walk oh there was karma in it everything
Karma we love karma in a story hello hi
hi you're
on what's your name sir Jim Jim lovely
and what do you do Jim I'm retired now
what did you do um I was hdv driver for
local Council okay Grand and where did
you do that down in Devon all right oh
does this story involve Josh wian no oh
okay sorry there's more than one person
in Devon gr not on the
couch okay off you go with your story hi
well I got some nice neighbors next door
to me Luke and Laura oh yes and um
theyve got a three-year-old son and um
he's fascinated can I just stop people
is he very quiet very quiet he's very
quiet he's a lovely little lad you
[Applause]
very
quiet he quiet
very he's a lovely yeah
okay all right keep keep going story
keep going well I've got a large CUO
clock in the kitchen and he absolutely
loves it and he got want to come around
and have a look at see it working and I
can't happen to turn the hand around so
it cooko and stuff anyway Laura and Luke
went away at Christmas and they went to
the inlaws and they're all sat around
the dinner table and chatting when Harry
suddenly piped up and said gym next door
has got a large [ __ ] that a bird keeps
popping out
of no idea what was going on in that
story
n for the last 30 seconds in my ear I've
just had Gabrielle going do it do
it do it you you knew the word [ __ ] was
going to come up and who are you my name
is Britney Britney and uh where are you
from Britney I'm from New Zealand New
Zealand we love a New Zealand we love a
new long story short we love a new
Zeal and do you live here now Britney
yes I'm living in London working oh
great what are you doing Britney I'm
working as a nenny lovely not playing
any CHS um
using our services walking on our
streets but uh enjoying our street light
but
[Applause]
no I'll have you go with the story
Britney well I was out one night for a
friend's birthday um we're having a few
drinks where we ran into a couple of
very cute Irish Brothers oh yes um so a
few drinks later one thing lead to
another and I actually went home with
one of the brothers the younger
brother um but I was rudely awoken in
the middle of the night and he was
standing in the corner peeing so I sort
of woke up like what are you doing what
are you doing he got a fright and sort
of think he was half asleep went to the
toilet all was well woke up in the
morning and went okay this is where it
gets awkward do I tell him what do I do
um thought I'm never going to see this
guy again so I went um do you remember
peeing in the corner last night and he
went no no no I didn't it was all
embarrassed so we went over and checked
the corner and there was nothing there
it was dry went oh I've dreamed at what
you know what actually happened so
anyway he was dropping me off home
thought i' get dressed um went to put on
my shoes and realized he' peed in my
shoes oh but I didn't actually tell them
I just car carried on home and threw the
shoes out when I got
home okay I'm saying I think you should
walk that's quite a good one what what's
couch saying I like that story she
should walk but In Her
Shoes H Britney you can walk on you go
well hello hi what's your name I'm Andy
Andy and are you from New Zealand yes we
love it we love New Zealand Embassy New
you must have toured New Zealand I've
never toured New Zealand though are you
kidding you're kidding I I would love to
I never went You've Been Everywhere I
know everywhere about New Zealand let's
hear a
story let's hear a
story I'll think over the story okay so
I was uh out for a run with my friend
dunk and uh we were running past the
running past the park and dunk really
needed to go for a poo so we saw a a
woman can I just stop you that's why
you've never been to New
Zealand so we we saw a toilet block and
there was a men's and a woman's and uh
we ran over to the men's and he was
busting he really needed to get this
thing out of him and the men was closed
so at this stage he didn't even care so
he went over to the woman's toilet and
that was closed as well so he's
frantically looking around where can I
go where can I go so he ran over to this
this book Bush and crouched down behind
this bush and he went and about 30
seconds later I saw this a big German
Shepherd came bounding over and dunk
pulled his pants up jogged off and then
this uh and then about 20 seconds later
the owner of the German Shepherd came
over and she was like oh Roy you naughty
boy get a bag a bag around up the PO
ties it to the Bel and then just wanders
off with the PO dling from the Bel you
can walk well done very good story very
good story hello hello hello hello okay
now now Focus everyone
Focus okay sorry I'm trying to focus the
couch H what's your name sir uh I'm Sam
from New Zealand oh New Zealand we like
New Zealand we like newal he just capped
himself love well you know he's from New
Zealand he's excited sorry what' you get
flipped for yeah whatever yeah okay wait
wait wait Sam I'm so sorry
okay focus everyone focus focus okay Sam
I know really I would really gather
yourself okay just go with your story go
with your story okay um so my story
actually involves one of your guests gr
um Helena
Hela so yeah my mom's a nurse and um she
used to live in London she told me not
to tell the story and she's probably
going to kill me
now you wanted that she told stor Helena
you decide can we bring back I to bring
him back he want yes we want to hear
okay
okay okay you're good Sam you're golden
you're
golden okay here you go here you go Sam
so your mother told you not to tell the
story long story short Helen is in it go
okay she's in it um mama was a nurse and
she actually used to look after her
father for a while when they lived above
the flat and anyway um Mom would have a
key and she' go up every now and again I
think one time she was actually in the
bathroom
and she heard someone singing around
singing around and so she opened the
door and um Helena's dancing around
naked dancing with some sort of song and
yeah that's where my mom first kind of
they kind of met and you know that's
it hi what's your name my name is Kelly
Kelly lovely and where you from Kelly
I'm from Colchester Colchester oh lovely
and H what do you do in Colchester uh
I've just retired after 33 years at the
bank okay lovely what were you doing at
the bank was in uh reward I was the head
of reward head of reward yeah pay bonus
shares pensions all the things that uh
people earn okay no wiser off you go
you're retired now you don't need to
know H off you go with your story uh
husband and I go to a big big concert at
Wembley uh it's our anniversary so uh i'
had arranged uh child care and he had
arranged for us to have a hotel for the
night in London very excited being
grown-ups had a good few drinks at the
concert afterwards ran to the tube last
two to jump on before the doors closed
and there we were wedged up against the
doors and as it jolts away from the
station he wrapped his arm around to
hold on to the handrail and uh you know
I'd had a few drinks I knew we had an
adult night ahead so I turned and I
started with his little finger and I
kissed along each of the fingertips a
bit at a time until I got to his Thum
where I gave it a let's say a cheeky
nibble so pleased with myself I turned
around to smile at him and he
went but it wasn't going to be him was
it no of course it wasn't him we can see
that going a mile
away it's never him that is nearly it
before we go we do have time for a quick
visit to the big red chair who's there
hello hello hi where are you from sir
I'm from New Zealand a home of the story
and what what's your name sir I'm Henry
but you can call me fingers
okay it's it's he got nine fingers so
Henry does your story involve your
fingers possibly yeah okay okay great
here we go off you go with your story
all right so it was my 10th birthday
party
and very very
good so my parents had just brought out
the cake I blown out the candles and
made a wish and then they let me cut
them a slice each and they hit it off so
they made one fatal error and they LIF
the knife there and then so me with my
friends around 10 years old naturally I
start trying to impress them so I start
playing the knife game oh no I've done
this a thousand times no wishes but then
I'm so confident and so eager to impress
my mates that I let my friend who's
sitting opposite me have a go on my left
hand oh my God he doesn't have the same
luck I do he gets four fifths of the way
through me below the knuckle on my ring
finger and I'm lift there sitting there
with a knife through my finger in the
table and so yeah now I can't get
married you can
walk oh my
God I mean that was like that was like a
documentary friend wasn't as lucky as I
am I you're not lucky at
all my God can we able to do another one
I love it when they F when they go home
oh
okay here we go here we go hello hello
hi what's your name Tom Tom lovely and
where are you from uh chisik in West
London chis West West London nice and
what do you do we not in chisik a little
bit we're in she's Bush we're CH we're
near you too far at all yeah me and
you what do you do Tom so I work at he
airport I um yeah working with the FL I
don't fly them but um I clean them and
put the fuel in them make them all good
for
you okay off you go with your story Tom
okay so growing up I used to go and
visit my dad in a beautiful part of East
London right on the river um and it was
was a summer Saturday and we'd spent the
entire day sort of lovingly uh restoring
and repainting the garden um fence
outside the front of the property and
coming down the street is a man and his
dog uh and and uh the the dog gets to
the front of the gate does that thing
they do call a nature starts twiddling
around um and what can only be described
as the most explosive diarrhea goes all
over the gate I was in fits of laughter
as you can imagine being an 8-year-old I
turned to Dad he had a face like thunder
and I said daddyy why why you so set
this man he's just let your dog peill
all over your garden fence he says
Thomas that's gray and bloody Norton
no did not
happen B can happen hello hello tat City
I know those are those are those real
tatter or sleeves uh they're pretend
yeah I've just got a top on it no
they have you got anything on your tummy
uh not my tummy I do have my chest and
my ribs and I'm not going to get those
out on National telis that be you're
just got to get flipped uh okay what's
your name Ian Ian and what do you do Ian
I work in uh Community safeguarding oh
okay safeguarding and uh where do you do
that I do that in buckinghamshire in
buckinghamshire all right Ian off you go
with your story okay so when I was 19 I
was in a rock band and uh we were
playing a big gig in London well 12
people um Jody was there but she thought
it was a call playay gig
so um so it's going really well and I
thought I'm going to show off to the 12
people In This Crowd by jumping off this
stage so I run off take a leap
completely mess up the landing and break
my leg in four places oh so um so it's
uh yeah awful and um so I get home and
I'm finally recovering from it and then
I have this awkward realization that my
mom is going to have to help me get
dressed cuz I can't get anything over
the cast and uh put it off and put it
off but that moment comes where she's
having to help me put on my pants and uh
gets to the top of the legs and I'm
sitting there thinking just stay silent
it's okay we're just going to ignore
that it's happening but she stops turns
her head slightly to the side and goes
well we take half to your father
oh every shade of raw hello hello hi
what's your name Carol Carol lovely
where you from Carol rice lip rice lip
rice
lip rice lip what do you do in rice lip
Carol I live in myice lip
okay
sure what are you doing on planet Earth
Carol if anyone knows the answer let me
know all right Carol you're going to
Delight us with your best story off you
go okay so some years ago um I had a
couple of dogs one of them Stephie um
suffered a bout of incontinence so the
vet fixed it with some teeny weeny
tablets that um I had to give her in the
morning so I know a few days in I'm
rushing around trying to get ready for
work sort the dogs out so anyway I go to
the kitchen to give her her tablet only
to find it's not her tablet on the
counter but my contraceptive pill which
means I took the dog's anti-incontinence
T so I'm standing there thinking do I
phone the vet or do I phone the
doctor anyway turns out I was okay in
the end it's just that every now and
again I just go up to a stranger and
sniff their backside oh boo boo lost the
hi I'm Andrew all right what do you do
I'm a head hunter a head hunter it
sounds exciting when people say it and
then you remember how boring it
is off you go with your story okay so my
fiance is from the Czech Republic and um
a big big tradition there on Easter
Monday and this is fact is the the girls
beg to get
whipped so what bit of a wh this is no
we're not no
okay I don't know where we got these
people
from I don't know were
they I love s Duty were they
vetted hello who's there hi Hi how are
things oh very good thanks now oh now
are you from the Sweden no I'm not I'm
from Northern Ireland oh
really I have a great
ear I have a very good ear I used I used
to live in Sweden what what I used to
live in in Sweden for 6 months see I got
it that's yeah you going to speak
Swedish me I don't know can you speak
Swedish I can say one one sentence is it
disgusting no okay go okay go for it
inan ream T oh what's that huh say
again in reum t it means no junk mail
please oh yeah sorry okay I how do you
actually say that in ream okay put it it
I think you P yes I think the say is
you're I can't say anything in
oh he's
G could have been a great story could
have been a great story we'll never know
we'll never know next one please hello
hello hi what's your name Petra Petra
and where are you from Petra I'm from
Czech
Republic happy
Easter just say Happy Easter
I'm surprised you can sit
down is that true is it true it's true
it's true it's true we begging to be
whipped on E Monday no Petra they can't
no you you don't beg to be whipped do
you
Petra I
do what's all that about on an Easter
Monday only on the Easter on Easter
Monday is a tradition that um if you get
whipped on Easter Monday you will remain
beautiful and healthy for the upcoming
year who came up with that one who yeah
really I think a man came up with really
I don't think any woman kind of went or
maybe she thought maybe she thought then
I'll get it out of the way in the one
day he won't be doing it again on Easter
Tuesday H do you have a story or you
just here to oh you do have a story off
you go off you go yeah so about 3 years
ago my fiance and I we went to Paris uh
for a romantic weekend and at the hotel
I realized I don't have a toothbrush so
I decided to pop into the pharmacy while
he was waiting outside so I W back out
and I said well you will be surprised
but French people actually are really
nice and polite and he said well how
come and I said well if you show a bit
of effort and speak a little bit of
French instead of English they really
appreciate it and he said so what did
you say and I said well I walk in I said
Miss
and and only I you walk give them we
like you what about Let's see we get a
story hello nice lady hello what's your
name Jessica Jessica can you can you
hear Jessica no I'm not talk oh she's so
sweet and she's French she's adorable I
don't think she's French she said didn't
she say like
pardon she said pardon she's POS
a chair a chair put me in do you want to
go do you want to go okay can you can
you ever go in the chair okay go you go
and do that again okay where's the chair
it's follow that man there follow follow
so a few years ago I was teaching in a
class and we had the Globes out and the
children were discovering all the new
countries they'd never seen before and a
little boy points to the country and
says what what country is this and I
said oh that's popping you gu does
anybody know why poing ug Guinea is
really famous nobody knew so I said well
there's still eight humans there it's
really strange right does anybody know
what that is when another human eats
another human and this little boy stuck
his hand up and said yeah I know
lesbians you lot are happy with
yourselves been looking forward to this
this is Thomas so which of you knows
Thomas you so what's your name um I'm
Jessica Jessica and while why is is
Thomas upset with us um Thomas is upset
because I've um postponed a date for the
second time so I could come and and be
here I'm getting a blame for everything
is is he is he your boyfriend no no I we
have not been on a date yet cuz I so you
put him up what what did you put him off
for the first time my sister and this
time Kylie okay you know that book Not
That Into
You but are you in are you into him
you don't know well clear clearly not
that into him she she's followed him off
twice can I suggest you take him out
tomorrow night when this is
on this is a story all about how my life
got flipped don't you
care go on baby hello who's there hello
sir hello what's your name Thomas okay
and where are you from I'm from Durham
Durham all right but you live here now
yes okay very good I'll you go with the
story uh so I asked a girl out a couple
of weeks ago and she said yes uh which
was great cuz she's quite hot and like I
really enjoy out but she Cel on me um
once and then we rescheduled for tonight
and uh she canel on me again so she
could come here and watch
K so I had no plans tonight I thought
I'd come down and see if she wanted to
rearrange for next week well can I just
say Thomas you're very keen cuz she's
given you no indication that she
is oh dear well I guess he didn't look
the good thing is he didn't make other
plans that's good yeah okay so so this
is your decision now this is you this is
you sending a message to him so Jessica
are we going to flip Thomas or are we
going to let Thomas walk this is oh
okay please get Kylie Kylie please will
you lever him off the red chair oh no
that's the worst ever oh just just end
just end oh
oh oh hi who are you I'm John John
lovely and where you from John uh I live
in London originally from norn IR oh
norn
irand where where abouts in norn irand
fer just outside Belfast in norn IR
Banger's lovely Banger it's a lovely
seaside resort lovely yes so but you
live here now I do and what do you do
here uh I try to make it easier for
people with disabilities to bank to to
what to
bank to
bank those are
helpful my career guidance
officer never suggested that to me
[Laughter]
I can't wait till we hear a story now
you go sir so uh I got up one morning as
usual uh getting myself ready to go to
work and from the from getting out of
bed and the 20 ft or so to get to the
bathroom I was EX in excruciating pain
uh around the the rectal
region uh what yeah it's I get
it I'm concerned I know I know it
is Dr Clarkson's very
concerned I think you should go to the
ER at that point well I I did go to the
doctors got seen straight away uh he
says right can you remove your treasures
and underwear and lay down and uh think
happy thoughts so he rummaged about and
uh he then he uh he asked me a question
um do you like
asparagus uh and pulled out asparagus
tip from my uh
enus bizarrely I had not eaten asparagus
for months so I have no
idea I'm slightly offended anwers
answers on a
postcard what the hell was that about
comes on national television and talks
about anuses later it would be harder to
yeah to get in and then get out cuz
they're sort of weird at the top on I I
don't know trying to also did someone
break into his house and insert some
asparagus in was it cuz if it was cooked
surely that wouldn't hurt you would it I
didn't understand okay so I'm here
tonight to surprise my beautiful wife
Alma Alma yeah see she actually in the
audience tonight oh where's
Elma are you sure she may have
left yes right she's
gone no your beautiful wife elma's still
here off you go Val is this a nice
surprise uh yes of course okay she's
pregnant of our first baby oh we don't
know yet the gender of the baby oh yes
because I really want wait until the
baby's born of course but she really
want know as soon as possible oh yes so
the doctor
wrote on this piece of paper oh legend
of the
baby and I say to her we will open in a
special occasion oh yes so because she
really loves you and your show I believe
that tonight is the best
occasion may I open yes dude you dare
pull
that we'll get it back get we'll get it
back we'll get it
back we'll get it back we'll get it back
we'll get it back okay get Valia back
get Valia back I'm sorry I'm sorry Valia
I'm sorry I'm sorry okay this is it wait
wait wait wait here we go so Elma Elma
are you ready it'll be a boy or a
girl a boy you're calling it
Wayne here we go here we go the babies
is a girl
over there you can walk you walk there
is hello sir hi okay the hopes of the
nation are on you what's your name my
name is Paul Paul yes and uh where are
you from uh I'm from uh cester in esic
cultur tics and what do you do there uh
well I don't work in cultur I work in
chompster but I work in Reta
fashion god is in the
detail I'll tell you where he is from is
the Bridge the Starship
Enterprise actually he does have have
the sort of William Shatner thing going
on you look lovely you look lovely I go
with this story I was working on what
was a fairly short construction uh job
at the local zoo and stop it Jean Luke
peard is talking
on a fairly hazy morning uh I was
holding up uh steel which uh I didn't
manage to keep hold of and it slipped
from my fingers and as it did it went
across the road that was uh into the
ringtailed Lemur enclosure uh but
actually snapped through the electric
fence and jam in the corner of the uh in
the corner of the the pit that I was
working in and actually the electric
fence was on quite high and where I'd
got jammed it actually come up between
my legs and I'd actually got electric
shock for a couple of minutes before I
could actually move whereby all the
ringtailed Lems that actually decided to
escape that's quite a good story off you
go quickly go
go off you go with your story so this
takes place in 1977 which was the year
of the queen Silver Jubilee Silver
Jubilee and we were having I must get a
pen
Tony 25 years ago yes and uh and we were
having a street party in uh in a little
close in West in West eing oh yes yes
and a few months before this Phil
Collins had moved into the clo very
exciting Phil Collins had moved in yes
and it was can I say this couldn't be
more in
1977 and um and it was at the time when
Genesis were at the height of their FA
we were all very excited and um my
mother was on the committee and she was
collecting money for the street party
she's great she's great yes so she was
going around knocking on door she got to
Phil Collins's door and knocked on the
door and he uh he uh answered and she
explained what she was doing and he gave
us some money and then he said to her um
what are you doing for music because if
you like I could bring the boys around
and she said uh no that's okay thanks
we've got a
disco hello hi yeah H what's your name
my name is aen aen yep and I'm guessing
you're from Ireland I am I'm from Derry
oh you're from Derry up for the north of
the country okay and do you live there
or here uh study here I live over there
oh right what are you what are you
studying uh costume design [ __ ]
interpretation okay there will be
subtitles on
Friday I right now only I can understand
it yeah but I know I can't no so far
you're not missing
anything I've never heard of costume
interpretation it's like costume design
isn't it except fancier fancier it's
fancier Frank oh yeah oh yeah yeah all
the
labor okay off you go right so lead up
to Christmas I was back home um and how
exact
place did you get any of it Christmas
something about Christmas Yeah Christmas
that's the only good detail so
far just pick out words you'll follow
the story say blah blah blah Christmas
blah blah blah home going into the shop
and I had to get milk and
bread so i l was really stressed so I
was like run in run out get the
groceries let's go told my boyfriend to
do a lap and just pick me up no need to
park the car so as planned I came out
you know perfectly timing uh silver
people carrier just casually drifts by
casual speed so without hesitation I
Sprint across with my with my
groceries jump in the back of the car
screaming and thump in the back of the
chair shouting go go go go go go but
taken in mind it was Christmas and I had
like a scarf up here and a
hat I thought which was my boyfriend
turned out to be this middle-aged like
six-year-old
Woman
Jesus and pushed her foot on the
accelerator and on the lamp
post Sor you walk you walk welome hi hi
what's your name my name is Sebastian
Sebastian and where are you from I'm
from Newcastle Newcastle okay do you
live there or here uh I live in
Newcastle yeah okay uh how you go with
the story Sebastian well many moons ago
um I actually went to school in
Newcastle um and there was a disco
coming up uh there was a really popular
girl at school um usual s of scenario
all all the you know all the guys after
her um I sort of waited till the last
moment last couple of days
um and asked a girl one of this popular
girl in question if she'd like to go
with me she said yes this was literally
I think the day before the Disco um lo
and behold the turns out that she was
actually going to go with somebody else
um and that other person was actually
Charlie Sebastian lipat that's the one
you dirty
bastard I didn't
know I was just thinking how could this
have happened to two
people Rachel
ghou they're very same yes you know who
it
is wow you know at the time you look
older than
time the same
age and did you end up marrying Rachel
gold uh no not yet no okay there still
time you know you don't happen to have a
sword with you do
you you you could you could add Revenge
if you want to do you want to there you
go all those years we've just got time
to go for the visit to the big red chair
uh hello hello hello hi what's your name
uh James James lovely James and what do
you do uh I'm a civil servant a civil
servant lovely in London here uh yes in
London and are you from the London area
uh no I live in London but I'm
originally from um suffk oh oh yeah M
it's a suff
massive is he mentioned in the song
probably yeah what school did you go to
um so I went to brandeston oh sweet yeah
I went to Prim Primary School yeah okay
so we put did we know each other yeah
did
we I'm not wearing
my I'm not wearing my glasses what you
say James hello yeah James yes me that's
the one what the
[ __ ] you do know he's my best mate
growing up you're kidding my best
growing up and now you're talking to him
on a monot I'm I'm not wearing my specs
and he's like oh my God can we not flip
him and just get him out
here do you have a story or do you well
yeah I did but it's please let it be
about Ed it is about Ed okay tell tell
your story then we'll flip you and then
with you okay tell you tell the story
tell the story Okay cool so um yeah as
Ed was saying this is so Random mate
it's really weird um yeah when we were
younger Ed used to come around to my
house and yeah like you're saying we
used to be quite good mates um and I
remember one time um
one time he was coming around for tea um
and I forgotten to tell mom who was a
vegetarian um at that point anyway and
um so mom cooked I think the sausages
mash for tea um and Ed said you know
after the meal these are the best
sausages I've ever tasted you know where
did you get them from and Mom had to lie
cuz she had no clue um and so yeah 16
years later I'm really sorry first time
I ever had meet and also the first time
I ever watched The Simpsons episode was
around your house as well yeah that's
right okay well done you we're going to
flip you now and then come in we could
be reunited backstage okay okay put on
the C okay okay there he
goes bring him up bring him on he wants
to meet him this I feel like Sila black
on surprise
surprise there he
is come on will you just will you will
you just say randomly some you know have
a seat have a seat have a seat too
sit down sit down sit down sit down sit
down hi what's your name sir my name's
Nick Nick lovely and where you from Nick
I'm from New Zealand but I live here oh
you live here next Wednesday what do you
do here I'm a paramedic a par a proper
job and everything we're glad you're
here yes
yes okay I'll you go with your story sir
uh so when I was a paramedic back in New
Zealand uh one Sunday afternoon I went
to a guy that chopped uh three fingers
off from the lawn m
and we packaged his hand up we had to
look for his fingers in the bush and the
Hedge and everything like that and we
rushed him to hospital cuz if they get
to hospital in time they can reattach
the fingers and on the way to hospital I
said you're 40 years old how do you know
not to put your hands at the bottom of a
lawn mow and he said I was driving home
one uh this afternoon and I saw that a
guy had picked up the lawn mower turned
it on his side and walked across the
front of his Hedge and he said that's a
brilliant idea I need do that so he did
his Lawns and then he did that and as he
turned up to hospital we walked into
recar to see the surgeon and we walked
past another person and he said hey
that's the guy I
saw and he cut off three of his you can
walk walk walk walk he made
it
hello
hello these are the easy bits and what's
your name sir uh my name is Brad bread
bread bread okay I feel I feel like a
barista at Starbucks I'm just ring bread
on the cup you go okay Brad sorry and
where you from Brad uh New Zealand of
course you are they're always from New
Zealand I don't know New Zealand must be
empty there's you must go to New Zealand
just the airport is deserted they're all
queuing for the red
chair okay Brad uh do you live here or
just visiting uh I'm living in London
what do you do here uh I'm working in a
marketing department for a university in
London oh s quite a proper job doesn't
it yeah well done Brad okay Brad I'll
you go with this story uh so I was in
Italy actually uh in Naples and um was
walking down the street and it was
obviously in a lightning storm and there
was a a hick of a lot of rain coming
down uh a very very kind old lady
offered me shelter in her house and uh I
went in she made me a coffee and she
offered me a change of clothing uh it
was when I was in the room next door
trying to put my leg through the
trousers that I tripped over uh I
knocked a bookshelf and the n on the top
of the bookshelf Came Crashing Down uh I
was still wet from the rain and as the N
hit the ground the ash went all over
me to make matters a little bit worse uh
as I uh Paul managed to pull the pants
uh up around my waist and started to
clean up the mess that I had made I saw
a photo and it was the lady's husband
well what looked like her husband uh and
he was wearing the same pants that I
had that was potentially the most
embarrassing and awkward that is a very
good
story excellent you the walk walk walk
you want be
[Music]